<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">


  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Lol!! xd Really Amusing ! http://t.co/ow1YGx8u</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @PatriotActionNW: BREAKING: Newt Gingrich Out… Will Suspend Campaign #tcot #teaparty #gop #newt http://t.co/glqpJ2AV</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Elections américaines : Newt Gingrich va jeter l'éponge la semaine prochaine selon CNN http://t.co/8xFyTstR</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Noticia: Newt Gingrich tira la toalla http://t.co/TD2FLluy</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @LOLGOP: Newt Gingrich really is a precocious, naughty child from a kids' book in a 70-year old serial adulterer's body.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich My dear gosh I'm perishing laughing halarious http://t.co/NBCW7hdd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Creates this change actually occur? http://t.co/NBCW7hdd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>http://t.co/mzoVvF1u NEWS Newt Gingrich ends campaign, Grand Rapids supporters will ‘get behind’ Mitt... http://t.co/UQHJBUe7 #TCOT #THEMBNG</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Any individual at any time make this happen? http://t.co/ow1YGx8u</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla - El http://t.co/EdFmHVfS (España) http://t.co/PrKhgqyn</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla - El http://t.co/ILPK8UR4 (España) http://t.co/myBZLHV3</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @thecajunboy: Newt Gingrich will wait until next week to end his campaign. There's more free donuts &amp; BBQ to be had on the campaign trail, after all.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich to suspend campaign http://t.co/Bz0iFzDb</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @michelleisawolf: Oh no! Newt Gingrich is leaving the presidential race?! What disease does it have??</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich will wait until next week to end his campaign. There's more free donuts &amp; BBQ to be had on the campaign trail, after all.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Newt Gingrich Out… Will Suspend Campaign #tcot #teaparty #gop #newt http://t.co/glqpJ2AV</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed this, watch a real interview #withNewt, Romney refused, but #NewtNow is the only true conservative http://t.co/q90TTojK</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @elpais_inter: Newt Gingrich anunciará que abandona su campaña rumbo a la presidencia de EE UU http://t.co/mtfr6zTq</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I had no idea Newt Gingrich was still running for president . . .</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Am Prospect Update: Newt Gingrich, Bridge Burner:   So much for a last stand. Newt Gingrich, who... http://t.co/QfRUqv1h Social(ist) Network</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Disalmanac: UPDATE: Newt Gingrich will leave the presidential race. Apparently, the presidential race has cancer.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I have to admit that I'm in favor of a moon colony, and other space exploration. I just wouldn't want Newt Gingrich in charge of any of it.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich ‘to quit campaign’ http://t.co/eMRuJO1x</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>http://t.co/eb26aZYF Newt Gingrich to end campaign Tuesday Newt Gingrich will end his presidential campaign next Tuesday.</text>
  </tweet>

  
  
  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla http://t.co/ZaTiyCgq @el_pais</text>
  </tweet>

  
  <tweet>
    <text>Washington (CNN) – Newt Gingrich will officially end his bid for the Republican presiden http://t.co/OSJWcshC</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Has anybody utilized this specific? http://t.co/v8eeg8ht Newt Gingrich Google Drive</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Disalmanac: UPDATE: Newt Gingrich will leave the presidential race. Apparently, the presidential race has cancer.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @someecards: Here's to Newt Gingrich finally treating his presidential campaign as if it was a sick wife. http://t.co/DoKNko6a</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @DebWilliams57: Newt says: &quot;I will stay in until Romney has 1144 - he doesn't have half that ! http://t.co/HWtDy9jr #withNewt #newtnow #ladybug #stopmitt</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pre candidato republicano Newt Gingrich se retira de carrera a la Casa Blanca. http://t.co/WuzxAnFM</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Oh no! Newt Gingrich is leaving the presidential race?! What disease does it have??</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I really need to understand why she did this Game 7 Newt Gingrich http://t.co/RX0tF0H0</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Disalmanac: UPDATE: Newt Gingrich will leave the presidential race. Apparently, the presidential race has cancer.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich drops out: His campaign was nearly dead so he's leaving it for a younger one. http://t.co/bn15lA94 #LOL</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich This is actually so cute http://t.co/J8QGR2GP</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT “@TheAtlanticWire: A visual history of Newt Gingrich's failed, photogenic campaign http://t.co/RZWIKQuT” sad yet #beautiful</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich ends campaign, Grand Rapids supporters will ‘get behind’ Mitt Romney http://t.co/lFP2YED3</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNNPolitics: BREAKING: @MarkPrestonCNN reports that Newt Gingrich to end White House bid. http://t.co/RrwalsvK</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney owes a debt of gratitude to Newt Gingrich--seriously. @mollyesque explains: http://t.co/q6s6UZE0</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Omfg!!! - this can be soooo crazy! http://t.co/J8QGR2GP</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla: El expresidente de la Cámara de Representantes abandonará la lucha... http://t.co/jj4TuN03 #TeamFollowBack</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla: El expresidente de la Cámara de Representantes abandonará la lucha... http://t.co/YeJYpP04 #TeamFollowBack</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;@JesseRodriguez: NBC: Newt Gingrich will suspend his campaign on Tuesday, May 1 in Washington, DC&quot;-- I thought he already did? (sarcasm)</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla http://t.co/BUl6BNPa</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich to Pull Out of Race: Newt Gingrich began taking steps Wednesday to shut down his debt-laden presidentia... http://t.co/wZ77l6FI</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Will Suspend His Presidential Campaign Next Tuesday, Aides Say - Newt Gingrich - Fox Nation http://t.co/YXMBOxFm</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>OH NO. Gingrich is dropping out! http://t.co/9DXR5sTP BUT WHAT ABOUT THE MOON COLONY?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich This really is really worth any discussion! http://t.co/J8QGR2GP</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich to suspend campaign http://t.co/c9R1weOk</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich to suspend campaign http://t.co/t3Ng9EPR</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt says: &quot;I will stay in until Romney has 1144 - he doesn't have half that ! http://t.co/HWtDy9jr #withNewt #newtnow #ladybug #stopmitt</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Omfg! I was surprised that this can be back again! http://t.co/bxLx6ZH5</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;WATCH&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;: Dave Wagner interviews Newt Gingrich http://t.co/dvKol1w6</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich reportedly set to quit Republican race: Former U.S. House Speaker Newt Gingrich is poised to end h... http://t.co/Tpo8X8Kw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich dropped out of the race as I predicted,clearing the way for President Romney</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich 'to quit campaign' Republican presidential hopeful Newt Gingrich will suspend his long-shot cam #uk #bbc http://t.co/ZsbYCgxm</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich is dropping out of the race, planning to endorse Mitt Romney and Bagel Bites.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @indecision: In the end, the one thing Newt Gingrich could not divorce himself from was reality.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NOLAnews: Newt Gingrich to end presidential campaign next week http://t.co/AXLp3Dfg</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now the comments that Newt Gingrich made earlier this year, make so much sense. #SlaveryByAnotherName</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Another one bites the dust. Newt Gingrich to bow out of presidential race.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Days after Newt Gingrich brought his campaign to Buffalo, he is expected to shut down his presidential bid http://t.co/sjWrL252</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>http://t.co/oocw5LlU - Newt Gingrich visszalép - Romney-t fogja támogatni - ATV</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Real Clear Politics: Commentaries-Newt Gingrich to Suspend Campaign http://t.co/IhpWJXpg</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich ends campaign, Grand Rapids supporters will ‘get behind’ Mitt Romney: Newt Gingrich's backers are ... http://t.co/doERfXEX</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich ends campaign, Grand Rapids supporters will ‘get behind’ Mitt Romney: Newt Gingrich's backers are ... http://t.co/GCzKCDcK</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Norsu2: Mitt Romney takes GOP control as Newt Gingrich concedes http://t.co/BMBSE9Yh via @guardian #tcot #2012gop</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Anteeker: #Newt a true Patriot made great sacrifice 2 restore American Dream We'll lose much if we lose Gingrich as R nominee. #2012GOP…</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @secupp: Newt Gingrich to suspend campaign next week. Aw, how come?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US election 2012: Newt Gingrich overshadows Mitt Romney's attempt to move on from primaries http://t.co/9Pvp5kYQ</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Now this actually helps make me personally excited http://t.co/CtGPZc3z</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @benearpphoto: Newt Gingrich talks to students at Thomas Jefferson Classical Academy. @shelbystar http://t.co/BvzAeoso</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich va abandonner la course à l'investiture républicaine: L'ancien président de la Chambre de représen... http://t.co/Wt3CckPa</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;@JohnFugelsang: Today Newt Gingrich is so disappointed in America he doesn't even feel like committing adultery.&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich Whoa -- a person gotta check this out http://t.co/CtGPZc3z</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich all but concedes his campaign is over: CONCORD, N.C. -- Republican presidential candidate Newt Gingrich... http://t.co/oHxW57G5</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Haha she got caught in the act! Newt Gingrich Complexe Desjardins Newt Gingrich http://t.co/qazZiD6K</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich may end his bid for the Republican nomination as soon as next week.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich ahahah i can't breath!!!! http://t.co/CtGPZc3z</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ron Paul still running but Newt Gingrich to end White House bid http://t.co/g3N4tTFD</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @TheFix: The most memorable moments of Newt Gingrich's campaign -- in one blog post. http://t.co/nJhBORuI</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich reportedly set to quit Republican race: Former U.S. House Speaker Newt Gingrich is poised to end h... http://t.co/BEZiWeiG</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich tira la toalla</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NotBillWalton: I am highly disappointed that Newt Gingrich suspended his campaign. I was really looking forward to seeing his glorious moon colony.</text>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>
<!-- (100) -->