<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's 25¢ Play of the Day app is Camera ZOOM FX! See the other 25¢ movies, music, and books at http://t.co/r8XGB6Uw</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Come by the #Android House at #SXSW to join our live Q&amp;A with Willem Dafoe starting now: http://t.co/8ePjrgMt</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's 25¢ Play of the Day app is Smart Tools! See the other 25¢ movies, music, and books at http://t.co/oHyoco9n</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Code lab starting at 3:00PM @ the Developer House at 83 Rainey St - 'Upgrading Your Android App For Tablets': http://t.co/x9Ht8hKD</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@Android is at #SXSW 2012 - if you’re in Austin, TX come check out the Android House at 97 Rainey St. @ 11AM: http://t.co/8ePjrgMt</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's 25¢ Play of the Day apps, books, movies and music includes Paper Camera! http://t.co/FohQFk24</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need a new font? Download Roboto, Android’s high-resolution typeface built for Android 4.0 #ICS: http://t.co/g11fmlyy</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's Play of the Day featuring a selection of apps, books, movies and music all for 25¢ http://t.co/0Sdo1kCd</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Enjoy over 450,000 #Android Apps now on Google Play - all the entertainment you love, anywhere you go. Learn more: http://t.co/S2A6fVi0</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our final #MWC 2012 wrap up video: http://t.co/baXUA9A3</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations to @googlemaps for Android for winning the &quot;Best Consumer Mobile Service Award&quot; here at #MWC 2012 http://t.co/9SAeDgDK</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video of day 3 at #MWC: a look at design and Android Beam from the Android booth http://t.co/wzjyqTaM</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch the full video of @ericschmidt's keynote at #MWC last night: http://t.co/8IbnWMOu</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Day two at #MWC: a look inside the Google Music zone and the Books and Music experience upstairs at the #Android booth: http://t.co/yT0l3Y39</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stay up to date on all things happening at the #Android booth with the Android MWC app: http://t.co/JOjrtdZR #MWC</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At #MWC 2012? A few Android engineers built Badge Scanner to let you scan/save badge info w/ your NFC enabled #Android: http://t.co/Gg2ygFnI</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video wrap up of our first day here at #MWC with some of the awesome developers at the Android stand: http://t.co/tx1svuJa</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New metrics from @Arubin at #MWC: total activations now past 300M w/ 850k per day, 450k apps now in Android Market: http://t.co/hSMBZrKX</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Remember to submit your pin designs before the end of Mon 2/27 (CET) and check out our video for a little inspiration: http://t.co/h1Kk3dxZ</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See our new Android Beam video and get a few new apps with Beam that developers will be showing off at #MWC: http://t.co/0bj9GM0a</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now that you’ve seen our #MWC 2012 Android pin designs, we want to see what your Android pin would look like: http://t.co/QY8oKBH1</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Android pin designs for #MWC 2012: http://t.co/mHYa8PDe</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In 5 days @Android will be heading to #MWC 2012! For a taste of what’s in store, check out this video from last year: http://t.co/F6SKoD4M</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@Android hits the ski slopes: http://t.co/LnNOqOvN</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Love is in the air and we’ve got some sweet deals in Android Market to help you celebrate: http://t.co/Iv41Mqtp</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Adding a new layer to #Android security: http://t.co/VF93ddI0</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today we’re releasing an update to Google Docs for #Android with offline access and an improved tablet experience: http://t.co/PZWLAvR4</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Busta Rhymes music video premiere feat. @youtube winners: http://t.co/sso2clGB. US users: free track on Android Market: http://t.co/FNdeEEPp</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US Android users, we just rolled out a few new Google Music features to make your experience even better: http://t.co/7mMW1heB</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#AndroidTip: Not sure what an icon means in Android 4.0? Just long-press the icon &amp; the description will display: http://t.co/fqtQmpUL</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See how Google Maps 6.0 for Android can help you get the ball rolling: http://t.co/cY0u6GdK</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global update to Google Search for #Android devices running Froyo (2.2) or Gingerbread (2.3) rolling out now: http://t.co/pYNw9vSP</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Notice a little something different on http://t.co/gC5L5vIE today?</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Create beautiful time lapse videos on your Android 4.0 #ICS device: http://t.co/4h8ZfwKZ</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did you know that Santa likes to use voice input and Google Translate on his Android device? http://t.co/5QF3d29T</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Heading out for a holiday break? Grab great games from EA, with sweet discounts on some of their most popular titles. http://t.co/u7UTPn2Y</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US only) LMFAO's &quot;Sexy and I Know It&quot; and 10 million other songs now for only 49 cents from Android Market http://t.co/JzFYXRiJ</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy holidays, from everyone on the @Android team: http://t.co/TFWpZ2T2</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US only) Celebrate with millions of 49c tracks and full albums for $4.99 for a limited time on Android Market. http://t.co/JzFYXRiJ</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Looking for some holiday entertainment? Several of the top movies in Android Market now $.99 cents for two weeks only: http://t.co/0iTqr7TY</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The final day of our 10 billion app celebration has arrived, big thanks to everyone who helped us reach this milestone: http://t.co/wZtGMoTB</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Time to get into the Holiday Spirit! Get seasonal tracks for 25c, full albums for only $3.99 (US only): http://t.co/NLWsShzT #googlemusic</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Looks like the weatherman totally missed the #Android snowstorm in Mountain View today: http://t.co/Ss7dGSwd</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This morning we announced some exciting upgrades to Google+ Hangouts including hangouts on Google+ Messenger: http://t.co/NIjIzaBA</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Only 2 days left of our 10 billion app downloads celebration, today’s 10 cent apps: http://t.co/Y8ZeQ4jF</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#AndroidTip: Control how apps use memory on your phone with the ‘Manage applications’ screen http://t.co/P8RnVRyO</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Day 8 of the 10 billion apps celebration is here and we have an excellent set of 10 cent #AndroidApps for you today: http://t.co/yv0tZ7EW</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Monday Android fans! Today we’ve got another great line up of 10 cent #AndroidApps to help get your week started: http://t.co/cq8LWwFI</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our 10 billion #AndroidApps celebration continues today with another great collection of 10 cent apps: http://t.co/Eo0zlxt2</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today we’ve got a little something for everyone in our featured collection of #AndroidApps at just 10 cents each: http://t.co/uw5jtHYt</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Friday Android fans! We've got another great batch of 10 cent apps today to get your weekend started: http://t.co/lUVaUzob</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Androidify yourself, family and friends with new winter &amp; holiday gear. (2012 party glasses anyone?): http://t.co/O3dYti2K</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Infographic: a closer look at where, when and how you downloaded 10 Billion #AndroidApps  http://t.co/VRAOa55J</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It’s apps o’clock again and we’ve got another great line up of 10 cent #AndroidApps for you today: http://t.co/JmuNyaIc</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On an Android tablet? Take a spin on the new carousel view for image search results: http://t.co/ovpMe27U</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Update to the Google+ Android app is rolling out now w/ new features like Search and higher rez photo uploads: http://t.co/wJGsHLAY</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today our 10 Billion app downloads celebration continues with a new set of premium apps for just 10 cents: http://t.co/i4bWEkPC</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do 10 billion #AndroidApps look like? See the graph:  http://t.co/oMqsTXUH</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>10 Billion Android app downloads! We’re celebrating with top premium apps for 10 cent apps for 10 days: http://t.co/Zo9aEcsH</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#AndroidTip: To place your phone in silent mode, just hold the volume down button for a few seconds to quickly turn off alerts and ringtones</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What does Android really dream of? Androidland of course, and today our little green friend’s dreams became reality: http://t.co/4PhovSb6</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US Google Music users: get Shakira's Exclusive single &quot;Je l’aime a mourir&quot; for free on #GoogleMusic http://t.co/86kVUnXM</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy December! Angry Birds Seasons has arrived in Android Market with 25 new levels of pig pummeling holiday fun: http://t.co/MQqxHC1E</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch @c_pruett &amp; @steptangent of @RobotInvader talk about the launch of their first game, Wind-up Knight, on #Android: http://t.co/03OnZanG</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With Galaxy Nexus you can chat face-to-face with up to 9 people, making it easier for everyone to stay on the same beat http://t.co/c4DKgD8p</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Take on Cyber Monday from the comfort of your couch with Google Catalogs, now on Android tablets: http://t.co/GNckWIzy</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#GoogleMusic next 24 hrs only new albums from Justin Bieber, Rihanna, Lady Gaga, Drake just $1.99 in Android Market http://t.co/265Eh9Dl</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Looking for some holiday entertainment? 12 of the top movies in Android Market now $.99 cents for the next two weeks: http://t.co/CaIF00oI</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exclusively in Android Market: Coldplay, Live in Madrid, free for 24 hours. Add instantly to your Google Music library. http://t.co/EXyNoTYG</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anyone notice a little something new on http://t.co/gC5L5vIE today? Happy Thanksgiving!</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Last week was an exciting one for the @Android team...so we celebrated with (what else?) ice cream sandwiches: http://t.co/55s40JkW</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Introducing Google Music. Buy now, listen now, sync never. http://t.co/bksrZwGm  #GoogleMusic</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The live stream on http://t.co/SxXf2tGG is about to start. Tune in now. #GoogleMusic</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The source code for Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich is now available at: http://t.co/uzR0y9QO #Android #ICS</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Want to kill time before Galaxy Nexus and #ICS drop? Try CONTRACT KILLER: ZOMBIES, free in Android Market: http://t.co/XuKvyVsU</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Android is now on Google+, add us to your circles: http://t.co/7bUxxUgo</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nice Android costumes @CleverReason and @MKblu. Any more out there?</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's almost Halloween! Here's our Android Pumpkin. Do you have one? http://t.co/bpYYtVTy</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch the extended 1080p demo video shot with a #GalaxyNexus by Android engineer @RomainGuy: http://t.co/vjt63zy1</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Which new feature of #ICS are you most excited to get a taste of? Reply @Android</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See more of what’s new in Android 4.0 #ICS. Check out the People app, Face Unlock, Android Beam and more at http://t.co/0GGZ9iOS</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Introducing Ice Cream Sandwich, the delicious new version of Android: http://t.co/kcZcN53U #ICS</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And we're live! Go to http://t.co/SxXf2tGG to tune in to our livestream for Android updates.</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Don't forget! Watch the #Android livestream starting in 2 hrs at http://t.co/SxXf2tGG</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tune in tomorrow at 7PM Pacific Time at http://t.co/SxXf2tGG for a livestream of what's new from #Android</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Thanks for the warm welcome and #Android RTs everyone! Have you Androidified yourself yet? Try it here: http://t.co/EgTsmxFA</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Something delicious is coming: http://t.co/kIK5Ih2E</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hello world! Android is now on Twitter.</text>
    <name>Android</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>