<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama: Killing of #Afghan civilians, allegedly by a U.S. soldier, &quot;outrageous.&quot; http://t.co/OmXyMjGm</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mental illness more likely behind Afghan shooting than PTSD, psychiatrist says. http://t.co/odRNulcz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Murdoch insider Rebekah Brooks arrested in hacking probe, British media report. http://t.co/EA4ue6HM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. to file trade case against China over mineral export restrictions. http://t.co/BkfZpnQz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. soldier could face death penalty in #Afghanistan killings, Panetta says. http://t.co/OmXyMjGm</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dozens missing after ferry capsizes in Bangladesh. http://t.co/mvbHmOoe</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>3 killed in suicide attack in Yemen, security officials say. http://t.co/yyzfQe0f</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hundreds protest in #Afghanistan over shooting of civilians. http://t.co/OmXyMjGm</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More than 8,000 have been killed during #Syria crisis, U.N. says. http://t.co/eM0uPW6F</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rains soak, flood southern Louisiana http://t.co/bSuFQHBQ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Egyptian official: Israel, Gaza agree to cease-fire. http://t.co/Er4AqgJp</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. soldier suspected in killings of 16 #Afghan civilians was diagnosed with traumatic brain injury in 2010. http://t.co/kdYSlcLz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Details of $26 billion housing settlement filed in court. http://t.co/YfdOb820</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama administration blocks Texas voter ID law. http://t.co/Watpiq39</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Washington base back in spotlight after Afghanistan shootings. http://t.co/kdYSlcLz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joe Paterno was fired for &quot;failure of leadership,&quot; Penn State trustees say. http://t.co/6VibT6z9</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>45 women, children killed in Homs massacre, Syrian opposition says. http://t.co/0vZu3JUw</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Israeli airstrikes hit #Gaza for 4th day. http://t.co/Er4AqgJp</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. soldier accused in Afghan killings served several tours, official says. http://t.co/rjUZAAjd</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. military official: Soldier detained in #Afghanistan shootings from Joint Base Lewis-McChord in Washington state. http://t.co/lOrzKLvE</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kentucky, Syracuse, North Carolina and Michigan State are No. 1 seeds for NCAA tourney. #Marchmadness</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tiger Woods withdraws from Doral with leg injury http://t.co/ZHIFtWkR</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Afghan official says 16 civilians were killed when U.S. soldier went house to house shooting people. http://t.co/lOrzKLvE</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Egyptian court acquits doctor accused of forcibly administering virginity tests on female detainees. http://t.co/RNpGznys</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>7 of the 15 Afghan civilians shot by a U.S. service member &quot;feared dead,&quot; government of Kandahar says. http://t.co/lOrzKLvE</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Five remaining inmates held in Mississippi pardon controversy have now been released from prison.</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Japan observes moment of silence Sunday to mark 1-year anniversary of deadly earthquake, tsunami http://t.co/9J5UwqOS</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney picks up half of Wyoming's 26 delegates after county conventions http://t.co/1D1lEOl2</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney wins 4 of 6 delegates up for grabs today in Virgin Islands to go with 3 already allocated http://t.co/86oAXQaF</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wash. state courthouse attack suspect found at mother's house after she called police http://t.co/h6O7PKlB</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Suspect in attack on judge, officer in Washington state captured, police say http://t.co/h6O7PKlB</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rick Santorum will win the Kansas caucuses, CNN projects. http://t.co/86oAXQaF</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Explosions at bus station in Nairobi, Kenya, kill at least 2, wound dozens, Red Cross says. http://t.co/4QDl8GsK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Airstrikes kill at least 15 Palestinians in Gaza; Hamas' armed wing says Israel &quot;will pay the price.&quot; http://t.co/uzupgsa2</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Minnesota girl sues school district, claims school workers searched Facebook, e-mail accounts. http://t.co/c2CIKRzb</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Canadian skier dies of head injuries after crashing in race in Switzerland. http://t.co/m2SDIzmh</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney wins unanimous vote among Guam Republicans to pledge all nine of their delegates to his presidential campaign. #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Suspect sought after judge stabbed, officer shot at courthouse in Washington state http://t.co/rmcPlDuy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Special U.N. envoy to Syria Kofi Annan to meet with al-Assad on Saturday http://t.co/YqXP6T3p</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Police identify gunman in shooting Thursday at Pittsburgh psychiatric hospital http://t.co/UwZUbFhI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. agrees to hand over control of #Afghan detention center. http://t.co/xwnLB2VV</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>German hostages released by Ethiopian rebels, authorities say. http://t.co/Ju7Zqcn0</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>5 still hospitalized after Pittsburgh hospital  shooting. http://t.co/UwZUbFhI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Al Qaeda group threatens to execute 73 captive Yemeni troops. http://t.co/kz7emLRF</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.N. relief chief submits aid access plan to #Syria. http://t.co/YqXP6T3p</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>China repatriated North Korean defectors, South Korean official says. http://t.co/Wvf8Fgzg</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. adds 227,000 jobs in February; jobless rate stays at 8.3%, government says. http://t.co/Fa0eO8HI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nigeria blames Islamist terror group for killing of Briton, Italian. http://t.co/UDU57PMr</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>China sends envoy to Middle East, Europe to lay out #Syria peace plan. http://t.co/YqXP6T3p</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Judge says entrance exam biased, orders NY Fire Dept. to hire 293 minorities  http://t.co/gPAZalOt</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Senate rejects measure to bypass Obama administration and build Keystone XL pipeline http://t.co/PvN5q7OT</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>2 dead, 7 injured in shooting at Pittsburgh psychiatric clinic, medical center says http://t.co/qqSaUXkD</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>University: &quot;Several injured&quot; in shooting at Pittsburgh psychiatric clinic http://t.co/qqSaUXkD</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lawmakers announce bill to prohibit indefinite detention in U.S. http://t.co/17BhOudM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>International pedophile ring busted; arrests in Italy, U.S., France, Portugal http://t.co/idMB2Qjh</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pardons issued by former Gov. Barbour are valid, Mississippi Supreme Court rules http://t.co/nvyqVNoW</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pakistan starts proceedings against bin Laden widows for allegedly entering country illegally http://t.co/gfjGPXci</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>House passes bipartisan bill aimed at helping small business start-ups. http://t.co/691PB8vM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Iranian envoy says country will &quot;never, ever&quot; suspend nuclear activities. http://t.co/PtjOpYtf</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. probes Afghan Air Force drug-running allegations. http://t.co/42bUfaxX</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Radiation from solar storms hitting Earth, space weather center says. http://t.co/VaXIxTzg</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>56 killed in #Syria violence, opposition network reports. http://t.co/qTBFQmBn</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A man identifying himself as the Syrian deputy oil minister says he is defecting http://t.co/tbO8ADHX</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dem Convention chairman Villaraigosa says same-sex marriage should be in party platform http://t.co/iHWUCbcf</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Toyota recalling about 680,000 vehicles http://t.co/bs2nFzEK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks bounce back a day after biggest one-day sell-off of 2012 http://t.co/9DGo51em</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>3 people, including a deputy, hurt in shooting outside Oklahoma courthouse http://t.co/ObXcdTUi</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anonymous claims it has shut down Vatican website http://t.co/RjCxtoLM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Murder charges dropped in Maryland against 2 doctors in abortion case http://t.co/QPsHQqVs</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple announces  new #iPad with a higher-resolution screen. http://t.co/tuBBXirC</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Real-time updates from Apple's #iPad announcement from @cnntech</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Peyton Manning parts ways with Indianapolis Colts. http://t.co/LCDh7417</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Too many immigrants in France, Sarkozy says. http://on.cnn.com/wjfn9P</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tropical Storm Irina kills 72 in Madagascar, U.N. reports. http://t.co/wO7p8evt</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.N. envoy visits #Syria to push for aid access. http://t.co/gbHIm1zR</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Norway mass murder suspect formally charged in 77 killings. http://t.co/126KPRVJ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>6 UK soldiers missing, feared dead in #Afghanistan. http://t.co/6KxjV0wu</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New delegate count from CNN: Romney 404; Santorum 165; Gingrich 106 and Paul 66 #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win Alaska caucuses, CNN projects #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO Live blog: http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sarah Palin votes for Newt Gingrich in Alaska caucuses, saying he &quot;best represent the ideas many Alaskans want to see. http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First votes being tallied in Alaska: Romney 424; Santorum 307; Paul 263; Gingrich 166 #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rep. Dennis Kucinich (D-Ohio) loses in redistricting-forced primary with Marcy Kaptur #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win Ohio primary, CNN projects #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO County-by-county results http://t.co/qJG4d7si</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win Idaho caucuses, CNN projects #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO County-by-county results http://t.co/g5Sta7Ue</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ohio remains too close to call as Romney, Santorum battle. Take a look at the county breakdown. #CNNElections http://t.co/BmlN7FCI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santorum will win North Dakota caucuses, CNN projects. #CNNElections http://t.co/mJYXVm6B</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 75% counted in North Dakota caucuses, Santorum 39%, Paul 28%, Romney 25%, Gingrich 8%. #CNNElections http://t.co/mJYXVm6B</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney to Americans: You have not failed; you have a president who failed you. #CNNElections http://t.co/ASZ2C3KH</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Updated delegate count: Romney 288, Santorum 106, Gingrich 73, Paul 52. Magic number is 1144. #CNNElections http://t.co/ggPNW2OI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santorum to Ohio supporters: I've never been for an individual mandate at a state or federal level. #CNNElections http://t.co/qJG4d7si</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rick Santorum will win Oklahoma primary, CNN projects. #CNNElections http://t.co/D4Z6iJ9i</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich to supporters: If I couldn't carry my home state of Georgia, I'd have no credibility. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich: I'm the tortoise of the GOP presidential field. #CNNElections http://t.co/q9zucLnv</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rick Santorum will win the Tennessee primary, CNN projects based on exit polls. #CNNElections http://t.co/D4Z6iJ9i</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN exit polls in Oklahoma: Santorum 38%, Romney 25%, Gingrich 24%, Paul 12%. #CNNElections http://t.co/zAY4A3NW</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN exit polls in Tennessee: Santorum 35%, Romney 28%, Gingrich 23%, Paul 11%. #CNNElections http://t.co/XJ6RIpRt</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN exit polls in Massachusetts: Romney 70%, Santorum 12%, Paul 9%, Gingrich 4% #CNNElections http://t.co/kr2jvRZc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Massachusetts, Oklahoma and Tennessee polls close. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win the Massachusetts primary, CNN projects based on exit polls. #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win Vermont primary, CNN projects. #CNN Elections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN exit poll in Ohio: Romney 40%, Santorum 36%, Gingrich 12%, Paul 11%. #CNNElections http://t.co/NyyxhNNu</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polls close in Ohio. 63 delegates at stake. #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win the Virginia primary, CNN projects based on exit polls. #CNNElections http://t.co/n0P1oFRG</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Vermont exit polls:  Romney 38%, Paul 27%, Santorum 23%, Gingrich 8%. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Georgia exit polls:  Gingrich 45%, Romney 26%, Santorum 20% , Paul 8%. #CNNElections http://t.co/3GvF4QbO</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polls close in Virginia, Vermont and Georgia. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Newt Gingrich will win the Georgia primary, CNN projects based on exit polls. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santorum campaign: If we go to the convention &quot;so be it.&quot; #CNNElections http://t.co/vv4ThccJ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Top 3 things to watch on Super Tuesday. #CNNElections http://t.co/FFwLZwJL</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Early exit polls out of Ohio and Tennessee show a hesitant electorate split in crucial contests. #CNNElections http://t.co/GjLARMTc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Democratic Sen. John #Kerry takes aim at Mitt #Romney over Iran. http://t.co/hbRdwoap</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The #Dow Jones industrial average fell 207 points, or 1.6%, to end at 12,759 -- the worst day of 2012. http://t.co/btoWXdDH</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>35 killed in #Syria as regime attacks escape route to Lebanon, opposition says. http://t.co/4TUXfBMr</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#LulzSec hackers arrested, source says. http://t.co/yq3WJax3</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Army recommends trial in soldier's death. http://t.co/kWloOHUT</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Have a Super Tuesday question? Join CNN's Election Roundtable at noon ET. http://t.co/68gVQX3Q</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seven suspected militants killed by security forces in #Pakistan. http://t.co/WkA7YlIX</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S., other countries offer to resume nuclear negotiations with #Iran, EU foreign policy chief says http://t.co/NvefhdKj</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>14 killed in #Syria as regime attacks escape route to Lebanon, opposition says. http://t.co/4TUXfBMr</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Iran offers nuclear inspectors access to Parchin military base. http://t.co/TcII8nqz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Ohio fire chief blames fatal nursing home #fire on secret meth lab http://t.co/m9QCIzzM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Passengers on #Eurostar rail that connects #Britain, #France left stuck in trains http://t.co/K2vbxjOZ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joe #Biden meets with Mexican President Felipe #Calderon; gun #trafficking discussed  http://t.co/FLBpUEC5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AG #Holder: Targeting American #terrorists abroad not &quot;assassination&quot; http://t.co/NPCPzNcr</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jason Young convicted by N.C. jury of #first-degree murder in death of pregnant wife http://t.co/UWhvQ0bE</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN/ORC poll: Ohio a dead heat between #Romney and #Santorum http://t.co/Pz7sJumC</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former New York #Mets star Lenny #Dykstra is sentenced to three years in prison  http://t.co/b5dtxoHN</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sen. McCain says U.S. should lead international forces in airstrikes on #Syria. http://t.co/TiI71aDI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sen. John McCain to call for U.S. airstrikes on #Syria. http://t.co/iC1J5dO5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reports: Iranian court overturns death sentence for American accused of spying. http://t.co/a4jDCSWP</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snow blankets tornado rubble, complicating cleanup. http://t.co/kq7OF4rK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Taliban link new #Afghan attack to Quran burning. http://t.co/4Ygya3eB</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Syria regime's attacks, raids and arrests spreading, activists say. http://t.co/WEhwiA01</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>USGS: 4.0 magnitude #earthquake strikes near Richmond, California. http://t.co/iC1J5dO5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Checkpoint attacks kill 23 Iraqi police, authorities say. http://t.co/F48DOT7A</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A toddler found alive in an Indiana field after #tornado Friday dies at a Louisville hospital. http://t.co/h0I2Thre</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Venezuelan President Chavez undergoing treatment for recurrence of cancer after surgery in Cuba last week. http://t.co/9dE3jk5s</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Explosions in Republic of Congo kill at least 60 people, wound hundreds, officials say. http://t.co/JMDTtuyF</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Israeli president accuses Iran of plotting to control Middle East, warns &quot;it will be stopped.&quot; http://t.co/eMC1HzQi</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bodies of journalists Marie Colvin and Remi Ochlik who were killed in Syria were flown to Paris from Damascus early Sunday.</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win Washington state GOP caucuses, CNN projects http://t.co/lBmQIfP8</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney leads early in Washington state caucuses; 40 delegates up for grabs #CNNElections http://t.co/lBmQIfP8</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Weather service: Tornado in Henryville, Indiana, was EF4 with winds of 166-200mph http://t.co/R7Z8CxS5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rush Limbaugh apologizes for &quot;slut&quot; comment http://t.co/CICKWbY8</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Correction: Death toll from Friday's severe weather currently stands at 31. http://t.co/miWIrgMK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Storm death toll climbs to 36. http://t.co/miWIrgMK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>32 people confirmed dead in Friday's severe storms. http://t.co/miWIrgMK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Death toll from Friday's severe weather rises to 31 in four states. http://t.co/miWIrgMK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rescue, recovery efforts under way after tornadoes tear through parts of Midwest, South; At least 28 reported dead http://t.co/miWIrgMK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>13 people injured in Arizona nightclub shooting; Authorities looking for 2 men who left scene.</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BP, plaintiffs reach billion dollar deal in Gulf oil spill http://t.co/aOm1h25u</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Officials say death toll from today's storms has risen to 14, with 1 dead in Ohio, 5 in Kentucky, 8 in Indiana</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>8 dead in southern Indiana after severe storms, state and local officials say http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Weather service: People trapped in damaged buildings after tornado in West Liberty, Kentucky http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Henryville Junior-Senior High School in Indiana &quot;demolished,&quot; emergency official says http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New Orleans Saints had bounty program to injure opposing players, NFL says http://t.co/SqsxYSop</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alabama governor: 7 hurt, 40 homes destroyed but no deaths from severe weather http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Local and state officials in Indiana now say at least 4 dead after tornadoes</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One death reported after tornadoes sweep through southern Indiana, Clark County official says</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As of 4:50 p.m. ET: 22 tornado warnings affecting 47 counties http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As of 4 p.m. ET there were 19 tornado warnings out, affecting six states http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>National Weather Service: Half a dozen reports of tornadoes on the ground across Kentucky, the South</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At least six people critically injured in Tennessee storms, officials say http://t.co/deWK2CYM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Major League Baseball adds one more wildcard spot to each league http://t.co/MZtv34mQ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aid workers barred from strife-torn neighborhood in Homs, #Syria, ICRC says. http://t.co/On9L9OMk</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>17,000 customers without power near Huntsville, Ala., after reported tornado. http://t.co/SZeVTdNV</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Widespread damage reported after powerful tornado strikes Madison County, Ala. http://t.co/SZeVTdNV</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>National Weather Service issues tornado emergency for Madison County, Alabama. http://t.co/SZeVTdNV</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apparent tornado touches down near Huntsville, Alabama. Damaged homes reported. http://t.co/ZXh7YJKJ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama says U.S. not bluffing on opposition  to #Iran nukes. http://t.co/NBSmHAUg</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Britain warns #Syria amid reports of executions in Homs. http://t.co/On9L9OMk</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Clashes between security forces, #Pakistan militants leave dozens dead. http://t.co/jFP0U1rL</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Another day of storms, possible tornadoes forecast for Midwest, South on Friday http://t.co/m9pvVzwp</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Passenger jet seconds from landing in Philadelphia forced to avert Jeep on runway http://t.co/ItwmTnWj</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Experts: Translated Toyota memo shows electronic acceleration concern http://t.co/cNT6Isl2</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. sees no &quot;fracturing&quot; of Syrian regime, and al-Assad &quot;looks to be dug in,&quot; official says http://t.co/T2eRzGtU</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michigan GOP reallocates delegates from Tuesday's primary: Romney 16, Santorum 14 http://t.co/EUGSlPXY</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Charges filed in juvenile court against suspect in Ohio school shooting http://t.co/OW5YBuCi</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Senate kills GOP plan to let employers opt out of health care coverage. http://t.co/sk45cESt</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Detained U.S., British NGO workers will leave #Egypt &quot;shortly,&quot; official says. http://t.co/74opgpLz</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One of two students stabbed at a Chicago school has died, police say. http://t.co/asSrblxG</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Army tanks move into besieged neighborhood of Baba Amr in Homs, #Syria. http://t.co/2SZoieQL</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Conservative blogger Andrew #Breitbart has died, attorney says. http://t.co/dGVwWod1</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>2 U.S. service members killed by gunmen in #Afghanistan, Afghan official says. http://t.co/OeqzZ7Pd</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.N. council condemns Syria's &quot;systematic violations of human rights.&quot; http://t.co/1HNQCYAM</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN estimates Romney will pick up 10 Wyoming delegates, Santorum 9, Paul 6 and Gingrich 1. #CNNElections http://t.co/79Lwm9BU</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 100% reporting in Wyoming, Romney -- 39%; Santorum -- 32%; Paul -- 21%; Gingrich -- 8%. #CNNElections http://t.co/79Lwm9BU</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney has won the Wyoming caucuses, CNN projects. #CNNElections   http://t.co/W2hKglJj</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At least 1 person has died in DeKalb County, Tennessee, as a result of violent storms moving through the area. #weather</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney and Rick Santorum will each get half of Michigan's 30 delegates, according to CNN estimates. #CNN Elections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>While Mitt Romney clearly won the popular vote in Michigan, CNN estimates Romney and Santorum splilt the delegates. http://t.co/NZBQcWMF</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Death toll in Midwest tornadoes rises to 9. Harrisburg, Illinois tornado was an EF4 with winds of 170 mph.  http://t.co/faNrbSs2</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former Monkees member Davy Jones dead, source says. http://t.co/4t5H7eRu</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At least 8 dead in severe storms, 6 in Illinois, 2 in Missouri, officials say. http://t.co/3XTXEVwQ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Death toll up to 7 in Midwest storms, authorities say. http://t.co/RxEWhxuS</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At least 5 killed as violent storms hit Midwest, authorities say. http://t.co/RxEWhxuS</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>N. Korea agrees to moratorium on missile tests and activity at nuclear plant. http://t.co/iC1J5dO5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Senior al Qaeda commander arrested in Egypt. http://t.co/io6zNqe9</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>3 missing, 1 dead in Coast Guard chopper crash off Mobile, Ala., source says. http://t.co/r7IHSFPX</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>3 missing after Coast Guard helicopter crashes off Alabama http://t.co/0ergwtFy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN projects Mitt Romney will win Michigan primary. #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#RickSantorum addresses supporters at  campaign headquarters in Grand Rapids, Michigan. #CNNElections Live: http://t.co/qvkLtzUP</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 60% reporting in Michigan, Romney 40%, Santorum 36%, Paul 11%, Gingrich 7%. #CNNElections http://t.co/MGH4Wyrs</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Delegate estimates to date: Romney--156, Gingrich--38, Santorum--37, Paul--27. http://t.co/ggPNW2OI</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 20% reporting in Michigan, Romney 41%, Santorum 38%, Paul 11%, Gingrich 7%. http://t.co/z0d4H8zR</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mitt Romney will win the Arizona Republican primary, CNN projects based on exit polls. #CNNElections http://t.co/z0d4H8zR</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 12% reporting in Michigan, Santorum: 41%, Romney 38%, Paul 11%, Gingrich 7% #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Early exit polls in Michigan's primary show frustration with the GOP field and hints of mischief among Democratic voters. #CNNElections</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Source: Republican Sen. Olympia #Snowe of Maine is retiring rather than seeking re-election this year. http://t.co/IIrWQ8Ry</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dow closes above 13,000 for the first time since May 2008 http://t.co/GSJL5emE</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>17-year-old suspect in Ohio school shooting to remain in detention, judge rules</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Some 9/11 victims' remains mistakenly sent to landfill, Pentagon report says. http://t.co/iC1J5dO5 #CNN</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A third victim has died after Ohio school shooting, hospital statement says. http://t.co/IbhLXJzK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More than 7,500 people have died in the uprising in #Syria, U.N. official says. http://t.co/aXOdchVj</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Attacks across #Iraq leave 8 dead, 9 wounded. http://t.co/02HY40Ny</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Assailants attack buses in #Pakistan, killing 18, official says. http://t.co/eqlB3l1b</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wounded French journalist Bouvier no longer in #Syria, President Sarkozy says. http://t.co/aXOdchVj</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Second victim has died after Ohio school shooting, official says. http://t.co/IbhLXJzK</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Matt Kenseth wins the 54th running of the Daytona 500 after a one-day rain delay and a two-hour fire delay</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Daytona500 red-flagged after Montoya slams into a jet dryer. http://t.co/ckSMXV6Y</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>California schoolgirl's death after fight ruled a homicide. http://t.co/OmR7e7cb</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#FHA to hike premiums on #mortgages. http://t.co/RjDa2YXC</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Part of #Keystone pipeline to move forward. http://t.co/XtYSq5Pv</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Standard &amp; Poor's downgraded Greece's credit rating to &quot;selective default.&quot; #greece http://t.co/CDgcriyY</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Opposition: 125 dead in #Syria violence, including 64 in &quot;horrifying massacre&quot; at a checkpoint in Homs province. http://t.co/doURFDpD</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Witnesses and a shooting victim ID gunman at #Chardon H.S. as T.J. Lane, according to Plain Dealer newspaper. http://t.co/mR8bz3oy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One student wounded in #Chardon High School shooting has died, police say. http://t.co/mR8bz3oy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Greenpeace: &quot;Xena&quot; actress Lucy Lawless arrested with 6 others after protest on drilling ship in New Zealand. http://t.co/WtlxdNeV</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Officials: 5 students wounded in high school shooting; suspect believed to be student. http://t.co/mR8bz3oy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Daytona 500 start time pushed back to 7 tonight due to rain. http://t.co/3Ez92xSW</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spain's best-known judge acquitted of abusing power, but remains under suspension. http://t.co/P2iOJsBJ</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yemen's ex-President Saleh leaving country for Ethiopia after handover, ruling party says. http://t.co/PpxAE2jG</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syria says new constitution approved; EU imposes new sanctions. http://t.co/doURFDpD</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At least 4 students injured in high school shooting near Cleveland. One suspect in custody. http://t.co/mR8bz3oy</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>2 gunmen shoot 3 or 4 students in Ohio high school, official says. http://t.co/dbadmDPw</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rupert Murdoch settles with singer Charlotte Church for a reported $952,000 in phone hacking lawsuit. http://t.co/7c9bK4vc</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;The Artist&quot; wins the Oscar for best picture http://t.co/BVFbAaT0</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Meryl Streep wins the best actress Oscar for her role in &quot;The Iron Lady&quot; http://t.co/BVFbAaT0</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jean Dujardin wins the best actor Oscar for his role in &quot;The Artist&quot;  http://t.co/BVFbAaT0</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Best Supporting actor #Oscar goes to Christopher Plummer for &quot;Beginners.&quot; At 82 he is oldest winner in history. http://t.co/BVFbAaT0</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The best supporting actress #Oscar goes to @octaviaspencer. http://t.co/FylFGZbb</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Santorum to get Secret Service protection. http://t.co/wlKb02JP</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Daytona 500 has been postponed until Monday at noon ET due to weather. #Daytona500</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two sources confirm to CNN that the Deepwater Horizon oil spill trial
will be delayed untl March 5. #BP</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FARC rebels say they will free and no longer hold Colombian police or military hostages. http://t.co/APPh5sGB</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>21.5&quot; Nepalese man shortest ever, Guinness World Records announces. http://t.co/E96IkpD5</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Demonstrators wound 7 U.S. service members in grenade attack, police in Kunduz, Afghanistan, say. No comment from NATO. http://t.co/f82vpc3H</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nelson Mandela released from hospital. http://t.co/3D2EMz3I</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. aid workers charged with fraud don't appear in Egypt court; Hillary Clinton says intense discussions under way. http://t.co/gpse3inG</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former South African leader Nelson Mandela likely to leave hospital Monday after hernia surgery, according to relative http://t.co/3D2EMz3I</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Official: Gunman in killing of 2 U.S. soldiers in Afghanistan identified as Afghan intelligence officer http://t.co/f82vpc3H</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A 5.9-magnitude earthquake struck southern Taiwan on Sunday, the U.S. Geological Survey reported. http://t.co/AjXd6KGu</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two Brazilian sailors died, one was injured in fire at a naval research station in Antarctica, authorities said. http://t.co/gvTzQbqN</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney, Santorum tout conservative credentials ahead of key contest in Michigan. http://t.co/KE8aPUYf</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nelson Mandela in &quot;satisfactory condition&quot; after hernia surgery, family member says. http://t.co/twJuwS9N</text>
    <name>cnnbrk</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>