<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Says Sorry To Cleveland: The Guns N’ Roses frontman has more to say about the band... http://t.co/34S2fbi6 http://t.co/mCaUAwQa</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Gossip #Hot #News Axl Rose Apologizes to Cleveland Fans http://t.co/xwAbtwCs #InstantFollowBack YGNews</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From Ch 3 News... Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland http://t.co/xaJU2sJ2 #TopStories #wkyc</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @RockPoetica: &quot;Quero me desculpar com Cleveland, Ohio, por não ter pedido desculpas a eles por não ter comparecido (RRHOF).&quot; (Axl Rose, Guns N Roses)</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose writes a letter to his fans in Cleveland http://t.co/g3oUMJdT</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Music stuff Axl Rose Says Sorry To Cleveland: The Guns N’ Roses frontman has more to say about the ba... http://t.co/3lBRBuOn #musicnews</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Says Sorry To Cleveland: The Guns N’ Roses frontman has more to say about the band’s induction to the R... http://t.co/7Db3DuDr</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Says Sorry To Cleveland: The Guns N’ Roses frontman has more to say about the band’s induction to the R... http://t.co/ql3kRSbw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Says Sorry To Cleveland http://t.co/n6DGKC77 #pollstar</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland after Hall of Fame snub – The Marquee Blog - http://t.co/dtdVQ4Ru Blogs http://t.co/j4CaxNaM via @cnn</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @RollingStone: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland for skipping the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction ceremony: http://t.co/Lcfc3iVw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose has apologized to Cleveland fans. Unfortunately it wasn't for Chinese Democracy. #TheAlbum</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @KeithRIVALS: Headline of the day, courtesy of http://t.co/DpgiirVd: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @gnrhispana: Carta en Twitter de Axl Rose para: Cleveland, Ohio, los fans de Guns N' Roses y a todos los que han demostrado apoyo http://t.co/ZOnMhAuL</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carta en Twitter de Axl Rose para: Cleveland, Ohio, los fans de Guns N' Roses y a todos los que han demostrado apoyo http://t.co/ZOnMhAuL</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Guns N' Roses plays without lead singer Axl Rose at Hall of Fame induction ... http://t.co/MB9ZO8ey</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>yea whatever axl...pfft. http://t.co/2ZQnKOek</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>He’s Back! Axl Rose pens another missive, apologizes to Cleveland and fans http://t.co/k4SSqHag</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Meanwhile, Silver Spring is still waiting...Axl Rose apologizes to his fans and Cleveland | http://t.co/K5hlylUY http://t.co/Mmm7HjII @tbd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame Snub - http://t.co/drENHlhd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Google #Hot #News Axl Rose writes apology to Cleveland http://t.co/M2Sl7rp0 #InstantFollowBack YCNews</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @KeithRIVALS: Headline of the day, courtesy of http://t.co/DpgiirVd: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MancowMuller: Axl Rose didn't attend the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction. For disappointing the locals, he was made an honorary Cleveland Brown.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Headline of the day, courtesy of http://t.co/DpgiirVd: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @rollingstoneBR: Axl Rose pede desculpa a Cleveland por não ter ido à festa do Hall da Fama do Rock; http://t.co/KmRtKu8c</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@ChemarieMonica : Axl Rose Apologizes To Cleveland After Snub - KVIA El Paso: The GuardianAx... http://t.co/45A5ep73 AsiaClassifiedToday</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose has apologized to Cleveland but Cleveland has yet to apologize to everyone else.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Tweets Apology To Cleveland Fans For Rock Hall Of Fame Snub http://t.co/m8BiATbj</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose sorry to Cleveland? Y say sorry? And Y won't Dee Snider get off the guy's nuts. It's G'n Roses not TRIXTER! GNR are street toughs!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @rollingstoneBR: Axl Rose pede desculpa a Cleveland por não ter ido à festa do Hall da Fama do Rock; http://t.co/KmRtKu8c</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Cleveland_Scene: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland for being an asshole http://t.co/Q402FGCp</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @ARTISTdirect: Axl Rose (@AxlRose) Pens Another Letter to Rock and Roll Hall of Fame + Fans http://t.co/ndtQ1Kxe - he apologizes to Cleveland...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @RollingStoneINA: Axl Rose Minta Maaf Kepada Warga Cleveland http://t.co/FMRdhlWg</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MonsterLyric: #musicnews Axl Rose pens new letter explaining Hall of Fame snub and says sorry Cleveland http://t.co/tZ9NAv3k</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @detikcom: Axl Rose Minta Maaf Kepada Warga Cleveland http://t.co/f4t7UoLL via @rollingstoneINA</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame Snub http://t.co/J5sBsfQD</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose (@AxlRose) Pens Another Letter to Rock and Roll Hall of Fame + Fans http://t.co/ndtQ1Kxe - he apologizes to Cleveland...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Gossip #Hot #News Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland after Hall of Fame snub http://t.co/ZHh5Nk9g #AutoFollowBack YGNews</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @WillSmithNews: Axl Rose Apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame Snub http://t.co/9Ddepmnk</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @DerekBrad: Not sincere and he is full of shit : Axl Rose Apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame Snub http://t.co/H78oBqNz via @rollingstone</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @guardianmusic: Axl Rose apologises to Cleveland over Hall of Fame snub http://t.co/MCRIskwN #music</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @ThatEricAlper: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame snub. His letter in full: http://t.co/HuGC7ifJ</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rocker Axl Rose is apologizing to his fans – and Cleveland – for snubbing then at the R&amp;R Hall of Fame. http://t.co/Rx1m5orC</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Apologizes To Cleveland http://t.co/5qK2a5YT</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @fox8news: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland, says city 'does in fact rock...' http://t.co/P4fA2JUv</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Apologizes To Cleveland, Fans Over Rock &amp; Roll Hall Of ... http://t.co/DPplDLH0</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose Apologizes To Cleveland, Fans Over Rock &amp; Roll Hall Of Fame Drama http://t.co/fQWEpqE2</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland for skipping the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction ceremony. Too little, too late? http://t.co/MOENh03o</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @ThatEricAlper: Axl Rose apologizes to Cleveland for Hall of Fame snub. His letter in full: http://t.co/HuGC7ifJ</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Letter From Axl Rose To Fans And Cleveland : Guns N' Roses http://t.co/uHQ3vLCP</text>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>
<!-- (50) -->