<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MartinxHodgson: Blinkin' EU red tape http://t.co/EQ8r31nC #Breivik: I shot Utøya victims because EU law made it hard to make bombs</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik: I shot Utøya victims because EU law made it hard to make bombs - The Guardian: The GuardianBreivik: I s... http://t.co/g81BDqAV</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik explains in court that he uses Bushido meditation and certain kinds of music to desensitize himself emotionally. #ABB</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Metro: Breivik wilde Brundtland onthoofden: OSLO - Anders Behring Breivik wilde aanvankelijk drie bomaanslagen in Oslo plegen voordat...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#NORWAY : #Breivik trained for massacre by playing 'World of Warcraft' for 16 hrs a day http://t.co/8PLVOkCS v @nydailynews #terrorism</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“@El_Enigma: Anders Behring Breivik, autor confeso de los ataques de Noruega, dice que entrenó con videojuegos”/ damn Halo !</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Blinkin' EU red tape http://t.co/xRWUcLMp</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik shouldn't be allowed to smile or laugh ever again. Link his facial muscles to an ass-mounted cattle prod.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @AlertaNews: Anders Behring Breivik, el extremista de derecha: &quot;El objetivo primario era matar a todo el gobierno noruego, incluido al primer ministro&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Europa - Anders Behring Breivik vroia sa ucida tot Guvernul norvegian - http://t.co/AYXo9MFd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@AlertaNews24 Anders Behring Breivik confirma que planeó atentar contra el Palacio Real y el Parlamento de Noruega</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik, autor confeso de los ataques de Noruega, dice que entrenó con videojuegos</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik voia sa ucida tot Guvernul norvegian http://t.co/cHGqme6T</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pour préparer son carnage, Anders Behring Breivik a aussi affirmé avoir utilisé des jeux vidéo, passant près d'un an isolé de la société.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ulkomaat: Breivik Utöyasta: Tavoitteena oli tappaa kaikki: Norjalainen joukkosurmaaja Anders Behring Breivik ker... http://t.co/jvOr4jnt</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik dice que practicó sus ataques en videojuegos: Anders Behring Breivik testificó que se entrenó hasta 16 h... http://t.co/kmnt6jxO</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik encore plus barré, froid, cinglé, psycopathe et diaboliquement intelligent que ce que je pensais ! #terrifiant #22/7</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik dice que practicó sus ataques en videojuegos: Anders Behring Breivik testificó que se entrenó hasta 16 h... http://t.co/vZugL6ui</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#NoowsNL - Breivik wilde Brundtland onthoofden: (Novum/AP) - OSLO - Anders Behring Breivik wilde aanvankelijk dr... http://t.co/n53cnYov</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik wilde Brundtland onthoofden: (Novum/AP) - OSLO - Anders Behring Breivik wilde aanvankelijk drie bomaansl... http://t.co/mFdD1aV3</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik wilde Brundtland onthoofden: (Novum/AP) - OSLO - Anders Behring Breivik wilde aanvankelijk drie bomaansl... http://t.co/mZoDVewI</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik voulait tuer tous les jeunes travaillistes sur Utoeya: Anders Behring Breivik, jugé pour la mort de 77 p... http://t.co/jcYM301K</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prozess: Breivik plante weitere Anschläge in Oslo: Anders Behring Breivik wollte nach eigener Aussage zwei weite... http://t.co/olVplLyQ</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @nydailynews: Madman #Breivik trained for #Norway massacre by playing 'World of Warcraft' for 16 hours a day http://t.co/C3UA17gn</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik et les jeux vidéo : un argument qui ne tient pas http://t.co/FxtbUhWu via @gyotoa</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NRK: Breivik: – Ville ikke la meg stoppe: SAL 250 (NRK.NO): Anders Behring Brevik ville drepe dem som kom i hans... http://t.co/7i8hBFjw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @nydailynews: Madman #Breivik trained for #Norway massacre by playing 'World of Warcraft' for 16 hours a day http://t.co/C3UA17gn</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CP24: AP: Confessed mass killer Anders Behring Breivik tells trial his original plan was to also bomb Norwegian royal palace, Labor Party office.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik 'planned three Oslo car bombs' http://t.co/5K5T8tp8</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The defendant, Anders Behring Breivik, 33, acknowledged an investment setback in December 2006, after which he m... http://t.co/HBWF2XB6</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @blessyrer: Det här med att ägaren av Megaupload kan få 20 års fängelse &amp; Anders Behring Breivik kan få 21 års fängelse.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Madman #Breivik trained for #Norway massacre by playing 'World of Warcraft' for 16 hours a day http://t.co/C3UA17gn</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik trained for mass killing with video games 'Call of Duty ...: Breivik says he wanted to at... http://t.co/yc2EAzvd</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>'Saldırı gününü Osmanlı seferinden seçtim': Norveç'te 77 kişiyi öldüren Anders Behring Breivik, başkent Oslo’da ... http://t.co/A8oy3pT9</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>'Saldırı gününü Osmanlı seferinden seçtim': Norveç'te 77 kişiyi öldüren Anders Behring Breivik, başkent Oslo’da ... http://t.co/GkZ36wE1</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breivik plánoval více pumových útoků: Oslo, Norsko, 19.4.2012 15:24, (ROMEA) - Norský terorista Anders Behring B... http://t.co/2DwpeXsA</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Stefana_Myers: Anders Behring Breivik brutally slaughtered 77 ppl in July &amp; hasn't been sentence yet :S. I think he should be thrown in Guantanamo Bay.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Norwegian Depicted as Loner in Thrall of Online Game: The defendant, Anders Behring Breivik, 33, acknowledged an... http://t.co/VSvCVLIG</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Norway's Anders Behring Breivik prosecution: A model for U.S. terror trials? http://t.co/R6HUcEgP RT @TheWeek #opinion</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik tells court he wanted to set off three bombs...: Anders Behring Brei... http://t.co/f6Ag5LrS #terrorism #security</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Great, Anders Behring Breivik played video games while planning to kill those people. I can't wait for the violence in video games stories.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>OSLO, 19 Abr 2012 (AFP) - Anders Behring Breivik, juzgado por la masacre de 77 personas el año pasado en Noruega,... http://t.co/Y2BdVNu4</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>gundem - Breivik, aşırı sağcı selamından vazgeçti: Norveçli terörist Anders Behring Breivik, müştekilerin ve yak... http://t.co/cH7eHZwG</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik says he used 'Modern Warfare 2' to train for Norway ... http://t.co/bMTjW6pU</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>WTF...Anders Behring Breivik, who killed 77 people in two attacks in Norway in last july. he will be jailed for at least 21 years?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @AlertaNews: Anders Behring Breivik, el extremista de derecha: &quot;El objetivo primario era matar a todo el gobierno noruego, incluido al primer ministro&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNNMex: Anders Behring #Breivik, autor confeso de los ataques de #Noruega, dice que entrenó con videojuegos http://t.co/vp4d6X9U</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNNMex: Anders Behring #Breivik, autor confeso de los ataques de #Noruega, dice que entrenó con videojuegos http://t.co/vp4d6X9U</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anders Behring Breivik, juzgado por la masacre de 77 personas el año pasado en Oslo, quería matar al conjunto del gobierno noruego</text>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>
<!-- (50) -->