<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Plastic Chelsea claiming they beat Barca. Haha. You were dominated at Stamford. Wait til the Nou Camp. #5times #LFC</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@joefooty will chelsea be able 2 beat barca ?/?what wud AVP thinkng?? is RBM better ??</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chelsea beat tottenham n barca but I only put a pound on it ill take £12 tho haa #Winning</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#chelsea fans ar happy coz dey were expectin barca to beat dem home n away. U escaped stanford bridge, don't worry camp nou is waiting.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anyone dat says chelsea played badly is a fucktard. Defending is an art too. Many hv tried n failed to beat barca. It is by no lean feat oo</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@Mivigliotti isnt madrid out?? And didnt chelsea beat barca</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Barcelona lost the CL semi final first leg 0-1 to Chelsea despite enjoying 72% possession! Barca will beat 3-0 or better at Nou Camp!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Barca Should Forget what happened to them against Chelsea and put Everything behind them in order to beat Madird Saturday! #NoRegrets</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MessiStats: Chelsea one of few teams to beat Barça http://t.co/KsTetJJn #fcblive [via @InfostradaLive]</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @emikesls17: Fans Barca gini mah bakal jd Liverpudlian, beat Chelsea #eh</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lool &quot;@eljefe39: Ure just talkin&quot;@Real_TMp: Lool! Issorai, sha beat barca sha &quot;@eljefe39: Leave am like that&quot;@Real_TMp: CHELSEA ======&amp;gt;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fans Barca gini mah bakal jd Liverpudlian, beat Chelsea #eh</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Chelsea fans I work wit are pricks #fact Ur not the best team in the world jus coz u beat barca. #fact</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @BazTweets: Free bet from paddy power because Chelsea beat Barca #Needed</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@syusyusyuhaibah haaa hok ni sedap ngat nk cakap ni . ho barca kaloh malam.lawan CHELSEA.aku kate dh kan only chelsea can beat barca haha:P</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chelsea beat Barca 1-0. :(</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All these #chelsea fans sef. You're not the 1st tam to beat #Barca oh!!! So please!! PUT A SOCK IN IT!!! You'll probably still get thrashed</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Barca wil beat chelsea at camp nou.up barcelona.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@oliviajgodfrey Sun shining in N. Ireland :) You should be happy after Chelsea beat Barca :)</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>crazy world ain't it, chelsea beat barca..I believe I can fly</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I think both 3rd and 4th spot will go down to the end of the season, and if Chelsea somehow beat Barca will be VERY edgy.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Free bet from paddy power because Chelsea beat Barca #Needed</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anyone else ready to admit that they are slightly nervous about playing a Chelsea side that just beat Barca?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aii aii will jus sit back and watch RT @Salih_Tadashii: Stop tripping G RT @BabshawlaR: Chill wait pause ....did chelsea jus beat barca :o</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Efizzy_no21: If Chelsea can beat Barca,den Panadol can cure AIDS</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ure just talkin&quot;@Real_TMp: Lool! Issorai, sha beat barca sha &quot;@eljefe39: Leave am like that&quot;@Real_TMp: CHELSEA ======&amp;gt; #Teamkickandfollow&quot;&quot;&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@RobBrooks2 @garydursley yet still, incredibly, Chelsea beat Barca with their 2.8% possession?!? Next week will be spicy, very spicy...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lool go sleepRT @chikaCEO: &quot;@BabshawlaR: Chill wait pause ....did chelsea jus beat barca :o&quot; *yawns*</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lool! Issorai, sha beat barca sha &quot;@eljefe39: Leave am like that&quot;@Real_TMp: CHELSEA ======&amp;gt; #Teamkickandfollow&quot;&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Noticed how Ashley got ridiculed in the press but cause Chelsea beat Barca no1 has mentioned how much time Drogba spent on the floor</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@WayneRooney game still in barca hand cz they are v tough to beat in there home ground...though im a chelsea fan..:D</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;@BabshawlaR: Chill wait pause ....did chelsea jus beat barca :o&quot; *yawns*</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stop tripping G RT @BabshawlaR: Chill wait pause ....did chelsea jus beat barca :o</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chill wait pause ....did chelsea jus beat barca :o</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The awkward moment when u look at the Chelsea score and they beat barca 1-0 haha get in there #blues</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @nollywoodxpres: Peter Of P-Square, Proud Chelsea Fan--We Would Beat Barca #Chelsea Football Club #Continue http://t.co/a1gwZNlw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;We showed MU how to beat Benfica, we showed Man City how to beat Napoli and we've shown the world how to beat Barca&quot; masih #Chelsea day!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @AlawokiGunner: Seems it worked o. RT AlawokiGunner: You start fasting cos you want Chelsea to beat BArca. #GodIsWatchingYou</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Omg chelsea beat barca haha!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MsFoyin: RT @KiDsLoW_OG: By scoring 1 goal :| RT&quot;@MsFoyin: Hw d fuck did Chelsea beat Barca???&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@piNgu_cOklat absolutely agree...barca still play with their own style..but chelsea improving their style to beat barca...fuhhhh...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @bigxghdotcom: Didier Drogba : Chelsea Was Lucky To Beat Barca …. But That’s Football http://t.co/461w6zOG</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Oh, and also good to see Chelsea beat Barca, what a result! #tadlate #uptheblues</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seems it worked o. RT AlawokiGunner: You start fasting cos you want Chelsea to beat BArca. #GodIsWatchingYou</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@DedeYaseen LOL.. I'm sure Mourinho would love to see Chelsea beat Barca, and he won't spare an effort to help.. @RiemannDwiek @fsadi</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@D_Parrella just shows how lucky you need to be to actually beat barca. Want chelsea to do it for england but I can't see it happening lad.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @BlAckH_keys: Jazz RT @MsFoyin: RT @RichardJ_JFM: &quot;@shegun_o: Luck&quot;@MsFoyin: Hw d fuck did Chelsea beat Barca???&quot;&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Didn't even tweet about Chelsea last night. Too busy savouring the moment. If we beat Barca Tuesday, I'm gonna go mad.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jamie Redknapp tipping up Arsenal to beat Chelsea 2-1 and @TerryGibson88 going 3-1 Barca in El Clasico. Will post links when shows r up.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An ideal scenerio wld be to beat barca another 1 nill on tuesday n Torres comes of e bench to Crown Chelsea in munich w an etra time strike</text>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>
<!-- (50) -->