<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">
  <tweet>
    <text>Honestly before the tupac hologram half of you couldn't name one song but now you're his biggest fan...</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tupac Hologram Performance Coachella 2012 Reaction http://t.co/8TTZL8Wq</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @_BeautyMoves_: The Hologram of Tupac could of played better than Bryzgalov and Bobrovsky.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LMAO you stupid RT @VennyDurr: Nas need to give that hologram Tupac the fade, with a laser gun or something.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tupac Alive At Coachella: Tupac Shakur Hologram Looks Too Real! [Updated Full 5 Min Performance] http://t.co/GcBI9YgZ</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @_MaLee: if a hologram Tupac concert is almost an exact equivalent of what an actual Tupac concert would've been, why wouldn't you go?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I bet Suge Knight was scared as shit when he seen Tupac Hologram. lol!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tupac's Coachella Hologram Inspires 'Holo-Pac' Memes http://t.co/SQjzA4HS</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Jackson to Get Hologram Resurrection Like Tupac Shakur http://t.co/SSQUqzHi</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @JeffreysWiifey: gekke shit hoor van dat 3d gebeuren hologram van Tupac,</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>just watched the tupac hologram performance and my body got cold that shit looked real af</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @denisleary: I wanna see Hologram Tupac tour with Hologram Biggie and then both get shot by the actual Suge Knight.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @NaomiTesfaye: Hologram Tupac needs to go on tour..</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dr. Dre -- I'd LOVE to See a Jimi Hendrix Hologram http://t.co/07JsQxFn pls retweet Follow @CelebNewsFast #celebrity</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Hologram Of Tupac #BlowsMyMind!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dr. Dre -- I'd LOVE to See a Jimi Hendrix Hologram | http://t.co/fmfq4fOf http://t.co/xwxxgY22</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Has anybody else seen the 2012 Coachella tupac hologram performance? That shit #cray</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tupac's followers made him appear by hologram; Jesus shocked his followers by appearing in person</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Skorpion Show: RIP Dick Clark, Britney &amp; X-Factor, Tupac Hologram, Basketball Wives &amp; E...: http://t.co/g5YSAKli via @youtube</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @VennyDurr: Nas need to give that hologram Tupac the fade, with a laser gun or something.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>if a hologram Tupac concert is almost an exact equivalent of what an actual Tupac concert would've been, why wouldn't you go?</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @ClintonLG: They shoulda made the Tupac hologram say &quot;Dave Chappelle, that ain't yo wife!&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>No lol its a hologram RT @TruLii_Zuly: Soooo I just finish watch the video for Tupac is he really alive??</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tupac Hologram Performance At Coachella &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hv u guys seen the video of the tupac hologram concert? #Sweet</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lol. “@VennyDurr: Nas need to give that hologram Tupac the fade, with a laser gun or something.”</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT http://t.co/aqfGev40 Dr. Dre -- I'd LOVE to See a Jimi Hendrix Hologram http://t.co/CsybteRN</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hologram tupac in coachella omfg thats awesome! Tour?! Lmao YES!!</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @Theskorpionshow: Please RT New Video RIP Dick Clark, Britney &amp; X-Factor, Tupac Hologram, Basketball Wives &amp; Extra Stuff http://t.co/NWUZuR7e</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hologram Tupac needs to go on tour..</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;You know who the *original* Hologram Tupac was?...Shakespeare.&quot;</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Tupac &quot;hologram&quot; at #Coahella2012 was Impressive but Just a Cool Optical Illusion - @arstechnica: http://t.co/dtt8NrOs #PeppersGhost #CGI</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So the word on the street is that Snoop Dogg is bringing Tupac hologram style to RiverFest.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#rip tupac,and thank you hologram technologies for bringing him back rapping on stage</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Tupac's at #Coachella Hologram And The Rise Of The Not... http://t.co/C3bUcmhr</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Wall St. Journal - Further Investigates Tupac's Hologram | Watch Hip Hop Music Videos &amp; New Rap. http://t.co/isR8M2Tm</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Saw the Tupac hologram on #HipHopPOV last night performing with Snoop. It looked convincing buuuut I wouldn't go to a concert tho.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I wonder how much money that Tupac Hologram got paid to perform at Coachella? #TheGreatOhendini</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>I just worked Hologram Tupac into my journal entry for today.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @dutchcowboys: Hologram Tupac is potentieel goud waard http://t.co/bbyn77Jw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Tupac #Hologram #lol #lmao #Wow http://t.co/fWC0o55a</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RIP Dick Clark, Britney &amp; X-Factor, Tupac Hologram, Basketball Wives &amp; E...: http://t.co/csJVyI5M via @youtube @makael86 @theskorpion</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This tupac hologram is just getting us ready for the real tupac to come back</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @VennyDurr: If you'd go to a hologram Tupac concert, you are a dumbass.</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>COMING FROM A TRUE TUPAC FAN DIS BROUGHT CHILLS THRU MY BODY Tupac Hologram Live @Coachella 2012 ( HQ ): http://t.co/DXnOTdXG via @youtube</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @dutchcowboys: Hologram Tupac is potentieel goud waard http://t.co/bbyn77Jw</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;I don't c the big deal with Tupac's hologram concert...I used to have #pokemon cards that were hologram...&quot; -Anonymous</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>( http://t.co/TePKb6Vv ) Dr. Dre -- I'd LOVE to See a Jimi Hendrix Hologram: Dr. Dre says he... http://t.co/EEYviKKU http://t.co/9qx66TU0</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dr. Dre -- I'd LOVE to See a Jimi Hendrix Hologram: Dr. Dre says he's THRILLED with the way his ... http://t.co/xIVGeLy8 #TeamFollowBack</text>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @WilIyWonkaa: I bet @kimkardashian has already blown the Tupac hologram.</text>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>
<!-- (50) -->