<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Registration for Code Jam 2012 (http://t.co/xRq4mP8u) is now open http://t.co/S9u1ql02</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eric Schmidt spoke to @60Minutes about how online @khanacademy is revolutionizing education by &quot;flipping the classroom&quot; http://t.co/6TUU4yvR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Registration for Google I/O 2012 opens March 27. Details at http://t.co/OUEsMdsb #io12 (via @googledevs)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chocolate at your doorstep? Yum! How one online bakery is finding success w/ Google ads &amp;amp; analytics http://t.co/eMFvu65c (via @sacbee_news)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@businessinsider lists 11 Google EDU classes http://t.co/0DBVKZq2 &amp;amp; 11 job titles at Google you won't believe exist http://t.co/U37AF9WI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In Belgium, reviving the memory of the Mundaneum project &amp;amp; its creators http://t.co/FkOPHnGq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today Syrian citizen journalists were awarded the @rsf_rwb 2012 Netizen Prize (sponsored by Google) http://t.co/OtjFpS1r</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch uncut video from one of our search quality meetings (for the first time ever!) http://t.co/y53oAAx0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrate the Diamond Jubilee of Queen Elizabeth II w/ an interactive online gallery from @Historypin &amp; @googlemaps http://t.co/meOtbYmt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Launching a new program, Women Entrepreneurs on the Web, in India w/ some admirable, determined &amp; creative women http://t.co/jrjDb0hI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're heading to New Orleans next week for New Orleans Entrepreneurship Week. Here's more on our work in the Big Easy http://t.co/QJD8t1TG</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#ProjectReBrief re-imagines 4 iconic ad campaigns for the modern web http://t.co/VHkdyKYP</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrating Colossus, the world's 1st programmable electronic computer. Video: http://t.co/jre3ZTK2 Blog post: http://t.co/NsMzYOyq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get the scoop on our food program from @GourmetLive, who visited the Googleplex for their &quot;California Dreaming&quot; issue http://t.co/523loZAL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy International @womensday! http://t.co/bNilrrWl</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Curious about @johncarter? Director @andrewstanton is at Google today for a live Q&amp;A @ 12pm PT. Watch here: http://t.co/VrIguskH</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Track #SuperTuesday results from all 10 states w/ this map from @GooglePolitics &amp; @AP http://t.co/mgzhACnb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All the entertainment you love, anywhere you go. Google Play is here. Learn all about it here http://t.co/fzvCvr1Z</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@businessweek talks to us about wind vs solar when it comes to investing in &amp; using renewable energy http://t.co/hJLIVYiQ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@googlescifair update w/ a new @CERN video &amp; info on a G+ Hangout w/ http://t.co/cldUT5EX (@iamwill) http://t.co/ByVXvsK5. Deadline April 1.</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get tips on how to make the web work for your business in our new Learn with Google webinar program http://t.co/wXkFjUph</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Only 2 weeks left to #Doodle4Google. Your child’s art could appear on http://t.co/8Ca4FJ0F &amp; win big prizes http://t.co/zZdHbNf6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>OER are educational resources you can share, reuse &amp; remix - learn more this week during Open Education Week 2012 http://t.co/uwBIxHoU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Weight loss, revenue gain: @detnews shows how a personal trainer's business took off w/ the help of Google ad tools http://t.co/FIlSaciA</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Backed by @GoogleVentures, @23andMe is doing inspiring work with genetics to accelerate Parkinson’s research http://t.co/oTEcI2qX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An update on our work w/ the European Patent Office to translate patents using AI - now at 6 languages &amp; counting http://t.co/U9UuUEjg</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google Fellow Ben Gomes talks to @JonMwords of @RWW about &quot;the brains behind the system&quot; of Google search http://t.co/x1KkFdvp</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@nytimes talks to engineer Arvind Jain about how to make the web even faster. More on why every millisecond counts http://t.co/NodER0ZU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Versus: a series of global debates via Google+ Hangouts &amp; streamed on @youtube. 1st debate re: war on drugs is Mar 13 http://t.co/aAhqwrSr</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sat on @youtube: live stream of 8, a play about Prop 8 directed by Rob Reiner &amp; performed by an all star cast http://t.co/RGX7MIDI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our updated Privacy Policy takes effect today, March 1. More info about what this does: http://t.co/EKR14ds4</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @WSJ takes a look at the growth of our NYC office. We hired ~750 ppl in 2011, many of them engineers http://t.co/EBF6gqAT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Doodle4Google, our logo contest for kids, is underway &amp; here's a behind-the-scenes video w/ our doodlers to inspire you http://t.co/yKskuUcP</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch the full video of @ericschmidt's speech at #MWC yesterday http://t.co/4hVUqjqT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Barber of Seville portrayed by a cast of frogs - our way of celebrating both Rossini's b-day &amp; leap year http://t.co/0lBaNFLi</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Inspirational @kqed perspective from 16y/o artist Gabriela http://t.co/GqdYFYnp Know a young artist? Tell them to enter http://t.co/mdMBUGIU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Checking in w/ web users w/ disabilities at CSUN 2012 this week http://t.co/g0TShTxT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>For #SXSW 2012, we're bringing a taste of the Googleplex to you w/ Google Village &amp; Live from the Lot http://t.co/Bv9Qk1kE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Partnering w/ Catlin Seaview Survey in their plan to create an underwater virtual tour of AU's Great Barrier Reef http://t.co/YWtUCrfi</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can search trends foretell this year's Oscar winners? We won't know until Sunday, but our predictions are here http://t.co/Yr5B9AEh</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Famous novelist Anne Rice talks about her new book, The Wolf Gift, live on YouTube in 30 minutes http://t.co/hFpZqMZV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CERN Physicists are exploring the origins of the universe - follow their progress up close on @youtube &amp; Google+ http://t.co/XrZ6D1jF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Preview w/out clicking through: hover over links above Image Search results &amp; a panel pops up w/ images http://t.co/q9BwPYI5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Understand Esperanto? It gets easier starting today w/ Google Translate - we've added Esperanto as our 64th language http://t.co/V1FdV53m</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You can now edit documents on the go w/ the updated Google Docs app for Android http://t.co/I9wtinWl</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Catch some pre #Daytona500 action: chat w/ @Tbayne21 &amp; 4 @RoushFenway drivers tonight @ 7pm ET via Google+ Hangout http://t.co/w38UAGw6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Find flight information quickly while on the go: our Flight Search feature is now available on Android &amp; iOS devices http://t.co/CbC4gtNZ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's wavy doodle celebrates Heinrich Hertz, who proved the existence of electromagnetic waves cc: @GoogleDoodles http://t.co/oVpiLWBk</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snow, celebs, gigs: see what happened when we brought 8 bands to Sundance to launch the Google Music artists' program http://t.co/kR0ymacK</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today @ 11am PT, join a Google+ Hangout w/ @UNICEF &amp; @MiaFarrow live from the Congo to discuss human rights http://t.co/6ExWS8bq #MiaCONGO</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In @mashable: @googlemaps lets you explore stunning underground sights in Japan http://t.co/ljXFVNCV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google Goggles now recognizes more than 45,000 types of currency from 300+ countries http://t.co/efMcyNi5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cool to see Google Translate help break down language barriers in critical situations http://t.co/J2DnSSgF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In @sfgate: A.I. program Dr. Fill will take on human champs at crosswords—w/ some help from Google http://t.co/reWKsZdB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jeremy Lin's star rises: searches for the Knicks point guard beat out sports stars Beckham, Bryant, Brady &amp; Woods http://t.co/CMNbKc5b</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mobile search data shows passionate procrastinators turned to mobile for last-minute Valentine's Day gifts http://t.co/heKzN1Fc</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In 30 min, join a Hangout w/ @CERN to see where the world’s highest-energy particle experiments take place &amp; ask Qs http://t.co/GDntMz1s</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Unlimited Access to http://t.co/enwHdRJ2 + smartphone apps for 16 weeks, 62% off (US only/online) from @googleoffers http://t.co/USLDoVgO</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;We want the Internet to be instantaneous&quot; - @bi_enterprise interviews our director in charge of making the web faster http://t.co/ViQhPK4l</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Launched 2+ years ago, Google Public DNS is now the largest public DNS service in the world, handling 70B+ requests/day http://t.co/A5InMkeI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Before running off to buy a dozen roses, read our Valentine's Day tips &amp; search trends &amp; really impress your sweetheart http://t.co/W1aLzjDT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wishing you all a happy Valentine's Day, in video doodle form http://t.co/wuC0DQ3W</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This year, we're bringing you the sights, sounds &amp; energy of Brazilian Carnival directly from the streets of Salvador http://t.co/XP5dJjbn</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Job search tips &amp; tricks. Rule #1: Do your research. Here's how, using Google &amp; other online tools http://t.co/9qlEYsP3 (via @WSJ)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dined out in SF in the last year? Vote in @Zagat’s San Francisco Restaurants Survey to get a free guide http://t.co/8z50nlUc</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@theamitsinghal talks to @mashable about building the future of Search with a 'knowledge graph' of real-world entities http://t.co/XzjH5grt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The European Commission approved our proposed acquisition of Motorola Mobility, moving us closer to closing the deal http://t.co/1XJKvMFR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>For Valentine's Day, how @googlemaps can connect you to the people &amp; places you love, even @ the country's biggest mall http://t.co/H39WJcwT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We hosted the first Ship Wars Programming Competition at Google Waterloo recently. More on our virtual battleship http://t.co/RADQwOkb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrating Black History Month at Google offices &amp; communities around the U.S. http://t.co/D4mRZJZe</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An update on the Google navigation bar http://t.co/i0q8TUNq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congrats to @theamitsinghal on election to NAE. Search wouldn't be the same without you http://t.co/sQcNMPjb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On @MindShiftKQED: How search by color can find the right football pic, narrow results to just diagrams &amp; find a book http://t.co/ItvkJjnG</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Thanks to Greenpeace for ranking us #1 today. There's more work to do, and we hope others also find ways of going green http://t.co/SAmyzje3</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Anne Rice is coming to Authors@Google. Ask a q &amp; have the queen of modern gothic answer it on 2/24 http://t.co/vzkCYP0y</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@BostonGlobe looks at @GoogleVentures' unique ability to loan A-list technology talent to companies in its portfolio http://t.co/mTJbwke9</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Search lead Amit Singhal tells @markprigg of @standardnews how our search algorithms can be a &quot;source of knowledge&quot; http://t.co/kaLbOnvx</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We hope our Charles Dickens 200th birthday doodle meets your Great Expectations. Cheers to a legendary storyteller. http://t.co/AJD1iRSX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We started celebrating technology &quot;moonshot&quot; ideas at Solve for X http://t.co/23QBcnsd. Join the conversation at http://t.co/F1IJ7FnV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Philly fans, @Zagat's Philadelphia Restaurant Survey is open. Tell 'em what you think &amp; your review could be in print http://t.co/ThrIHbYq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A new collaboration btw Google &amp; French business school HEC trains student entrepreneurs in digital business http://t.co/OAYn6YOa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Preferred the ads to the football? Join NBC Sports for an exclusive Super Bowl ad hangout on Google+ at noon ET http://t.co/RQxv8lnF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Taking a look at some top Super Bowl search trends - who took home the coveted &quot;most searched for&quot; honors? http://t.co/zeoN3jTy</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Unicode is now over 60% of the web http://t.co/bNbMtEhp</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Admit it, it's the Super Bowl commercials you're most excited for. Vote for the best w/ @YouTube's AdBlitz http://t.co/Y3S97QjR (cc @Adweek)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A group of Israeli Googlers start the &quot;Mind the Gap&quot; program to encourage more girls to study CS http://t.co/RW49VZ0m</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Touchdown! Our Game Day w/ Google Playbook has all the Google tips you need to make the most out of Super Bowl Sunday http://t.co/EXlIRm3C</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A @youtube manager gives @nbcchicago some smart marketing tactics to reach consumers w/ online video http://t.co/gD1So7lX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @gmail We're working with the industry to land another blow against email phishing #DMARC http://t.co/uwwTs6jM</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Read our blog post &amp; letter responding to questions about our privacy policy changes http://t.co/2XKKEfFE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President Obama answers your questions via Google+ hangout, in 1 hour at 2:30PT. Watch live at http://t.co/KDthNLMb #askobama</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Busta Rhymes music video premiere feat. @youtube contest winners http://t.co/sAYaADlb. Track is free on Android Market http://t.co/xfSxzZ2a</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Confederacy of lunches: eating at all 398 @Zagat-rated New Orleans restaurants http://t.co/WGBxa0uk (via @NOLAnews)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our 2012 RISE (Roots in Science &amp; Engineering) award winners, changing STEM education worldwide http://t.co/3jvTJWrR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here's an uplifting story for a Friday--how Chromebooks helped one student find a voice http://t.co/CVM0xAtF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two new studies demonstrate the growing economic impact of the web - worldwide http://t.co/ss2coJ4N</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cor blimey! @Zagat's 2012 London Restaurants Survey is now live. Details (&amp; what's in it for you): http://t.co/BZwh1ycI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Calling all student photographers: just 5 days left to get your entries in for the Google Photography Prize http://t.co/0k6BlTV2</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Public Alerts for weather, public safety &amp; earthquakes now on @googlemaps http://t.co/EuH5xJZB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New educational resources for teachers, edu nonprofits &amp; admins from Google in Education (http://t.co/4R1Chbnw). More @ http://t.co/W3GWniOX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reading @cnnmoneytech on Alma Whitten &amp; Google's &quot;culture of privacy&quot; http://t.co/pS6F6siL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More people in US, UK, GE, FR, JP use a mobile phone than a computer. New Google/IPSOS research: mobile is mainstream http://t.co/6mRDrhB8</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SF &amp; NYC teachers &amp; parents: Give an 8th grader the chance of a lifetime by registering your school for CAPE http://t.co/bfDA0D4x</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tracking down the history of one of our favorite quotes &quot;the future has arrived--it's just not evenly distributed yet&quot; http://t.co/elT1xMud</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're updating our privacy policies &amp; TOS. This stuff matters—please learn more: http://t.co/SJ8vC0Pu</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Paragliding, GPS tours &amp; poetry -- @tnooz looks at @googleearth for adventure travelers http://t.co/Hz60gejE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Highlights from our event in Brussels today, focused on how the Internet can drive economic growth http://t.co/aSRfMKpT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live in Charlotte, Kansas City, Milwaukee, San Antonio or Tampa? Lucky you! Google Offers is now live in your city http://t.co/usnSZFbJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Love is in the air... on the new @Zagat blog. See the results of their Valentine's Day survey &amp; more foodie news http://t.co/n6ZlffzP</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Year of the Dragon! We kicked off the Chinese New Year festivities w/ this doodle http://t.co/lCNsQujN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;My other car drives itself&quot; - @wired on our self-driving car project http://t.co/nDMYY9zb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Going somewhere &amp; looking for a place to stay close to the sights you're seeing? Now find hotels by travel time http://t.co/jfRd77sI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A new milestone for @YouTube: 60 hrs of video uploaded every minute &amp; 4 billion video views a day. Wow! http://t.co/4tW9F0hZ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@BBCNews asks if TV &amp; the web are a match made in heaven &amp; calls @GoogleTV the &quot;most ambitious attempt to reshape TV&quot;
http://t.co/hAnkwSsg</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Googlers hopped on board Jagriti Yatra, a train trip for entrepreneurship, in India this year http://t.co/t06goIxz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Google is A-OK with Oklahoma&quot; - a video peek at one of our data centers, from @fortunemagazine http://t.co/gzQ9i1JV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Data Journalism Awards now accepting submissions - due Apr 10 http://t.co/bf8waXt5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Easily browse @GoogleVentures' portfolio companies on a new page http://t.co/QpBmrUjs</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;YouTube has done a lot of good so far. And it’s hoping to do a lot more.&quot; @TechCrunch on social good efforts @YouTube http://t.co/5ILzgLek</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our Q4 and fiscal year 2011 results: http://t.co/HPBJUIDY Tune into the webcast at http://t.co/YUbbSFrf</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All our U.S. owned/operated data centers are ISO 14001 &amp; OHSAS 18001 certified—a 1st for a major Internet services co. http://t.co/H6i5EHeo</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Don't forget - watch our live stream w/ David Beckham, 9am PT http://t.co/zEZLrWRc then Hangout w/ him @ 10:30am PT http://t.co/uIwDJ7UD</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In the US, 7M+ took the time yesterday to petition Congress to stop #SOPA &amp; #PIPA. Keep +1ing, tweeting &amp; sharing http://t.co/zlj2BFCU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're #1 on @FortuneMagazine's Best Companies to Work For list! Read the Q&amp;A w/ Larry: http://t.co/0sIAbYMT</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Robert Kyncl, a @YouTube VP, discusses the opportunity for video on the web at #CES last week http://t.co/sm4rJhaa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>K-12 students in the US: start your creative engines! 2012 Doodle 4 Google begins today. Details &amp; deadlines: http://t.co/BBjLWss0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Help protect the web. Sign the petition against SOPA &amp; PIPA: http://t.co/zlj2BFCU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Space may be the final frontier, but for #SpaceLab finalists, it could be the start. Your vote decides http://t.co/VIuKx2h3 (via @YouTube)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Move digital journalism forward: Only 10 days left to apply for the AP-Google Journalism &amp; Technology Scholarship http://t.co/PfdmDral</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joining the Internet Society &amp; several major Internet companies in the World IPv6 Launch on June 6, 2012 http://t.co/JSleHSM6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today in the U.S. we're kicking off Good to Know, a consumer education campaign focused on safety on the web http://t.co/G7rAAXQX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. Googlers celebrated MLK Day of Service by lending a helping hand in their communities http://t.co/iwMDQejG</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our doodle to mark Martin Luther King, Jr. Day in the U.S. http://t.co/nbjJgDbI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Got questions for David Beckham? He may answer them next week at Google or in a hangout http://t.co/qGycl2Ma</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Welcoming Diane Greene to our board of directors! http://t.co/UQBqs00i</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Getting there is half the fun: find your way thru the world maze w/ @googlemaps. Video: http://t.co/EcnuEevb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The 2nd annual Google Science Fair is now open at http://t.co/3l9aqgnk. Everyone's got a question: What's yours? http://t.co/FHUiZUqr</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google Body is now Zygote Body, &amp; we’ve open sourced the code http://t.co/HA6mnzow</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BBVA is switching to Google Apps - our largest customer to date, w/ 110,000+ employees http://t.co/VOhyBxyK #gonegoogle</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's doodle celebrates Nicolas Steno, often considered the &quot;father of modern geology&quot; http://t.co/8HWyuyS0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@WBEZ shows Chicago residents how to remap wards w/ @GoogleFT &amp; @googleearth (shape files &amp; data sets, too) http://t.co/xMqurkWD</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>University &amp; college campuses from around the world now available in Street View http://t.co/mULCvInX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@hemispheresmag chats w/ Mike Cohen on our data-driven approach to speech recognition around the world http://t.co/DEz8NuvX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Speed issue of #thinkquarterly is out. Read thoughts on how we'll keep pace in a world that moves at web speed: http://t.co/uoXDHelI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Last year's @googlescifair winners became scientific rock stars; get inspired by their talk featured today on http://t.co/L0yM5Fmu</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First time ever: find your personal stuff in Google Search results http://t.co/55VE5xwZ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Help @Zagat w/ its NYC Shopping Survey at http://t.co/WqgKkPro. Details (&amp; what's in it for you) http://t.co/xi5Z3VHW</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Where to find Google &amp; @YouTube at #CES this week http://t.co/5jzZjHdS</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Computer Science 4 High School (CS4HS) applications for universities are open; help bring CS to your local schools http://t.co/mdDCZ99j</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy birthday Charles Addams, cartoonist &amp; creator of the Addams Family. More on our blog http://t.co/gI3tVdkn http://t.co/K3cSMQys</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who was the first cartoon to hunt Daffy Duck? The surprising answer &amp; 30 search improvements, w/ their codenames http://t.co/89Z19zLg</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Vote for your favorite restaurants in the @Zagat Chicago Restaurants Survey, open until Jan 16 http://t.co/JCPTi641</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A warm Google Apps for Government welcome to the City of Pittsburgh http://t.co/ns3SfIhr &amp; @usnoaagov http://t.co/VzaxDIhL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>http://t.co/BKwZFxFl is our 2012 U.S. election hub w/ all the news &amp; data for politicians, journalists &amp; citizens http://t.co/TPcxweNP</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our annual look at the year in Google blogging (and beyond) http://t.co/rHeGqxQ7</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Welcoming 2012 with a festive doodle. Happy New Year! http://t.co/aUx8Be5v</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US only) The Android Market music sale is ending soon. 800,000+ albums for $4.99 and 10 million songs for 49c http://t.co/8FyU8kaU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A new crop of videos are going head-to-head in our latest @YouTube Slam. Play, vote &amp; help discover the next big thing http://t.co/2bgLfDBs</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US select markets) Today @GoogleOffers features @JambaJuice: $5 for $10 towards smoothies &amp; food http://t.co/86vjAuWR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US only) Coldplay's new album and 800,000 others only $4.99 for a limited time in Android Market http://t.co/8FyU8kaU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's jolly musical doodle has us jingling along. Happy holidays! http://t.co/jNmEKFuS</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Track Santa's journey from the N Pole with Google Earth &amp; NORAD Dec 24 @ 2am ET on http://t.co/pWgVOoZp. More info http://t.co/ZLOSOJGZ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(US only) Hits from pop sensation LMFAO &amp; 10 million other tracks now for only 49 cents from Android Market http://t.co/8FyU8kaU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santa was poking around the Android office this week, and he even made it snow in California http://t.co/usS5UqNH</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Duck, aim, draw &amp; throw - have an interactive snowball fight w/ DoubleClick Rich Media http://t.co/s3I63egU. Happy holidays from @rmgallery</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>8 craaazy nights - a Googley Hanukah menorah made of lava lamps at our Mountain View HQ http://t.co/N4T9Rjde</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reading @poynter: &quot;How journalists can use Google Refine to clean ‘dirty’ data sets&quot; http://t.co/Qdr2Tge0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It was a great yr for Computer Science for High School (CS4HS) in EMEA. Recap on @googlestudents &amp; how to apply in 2012 http://t.co/K1AGclBy</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our global online marketing challenge is now open for professor registration http://t.co/tfLqYiJN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Test your creativity (&amp; your funny bone) w/ our new search caption contest. Vote for the best &amp; they'll rise to the top http://t.co/E5yz1QSE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>MT @gmail Update: Send custom video messages from Santa at http://t.co/dUWSE2jL to anywhere in the world http://t.co/dh64nIGi</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've signed a new agreement to be the default search provider for the Firefox browser http://t.co/6zLHateq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Thoughts from the enterprise team on how cloud, mobile &amp; social are transforming the way we work http://t.co/7topqeos cc @GoogleAtWork</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Some Google product tips to make your life easier this holiday season http://t.co/oqxZQDNL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In the ad world, 2011 was the year of mobile. A great by-the-numbers infographic is on @mashable http://t.co/pMWQflhl</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>2011 Rewind: The most popular @YouTube videos of the year http://t.co/GCSmEl5Z</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A new $94M investment in solar projects brings our portfolio of clean energy investments to $915M+ http://t.co/hVoobUfQ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @metmuseum has provided 76,000 images to Google Goggles so your phone can get better at ID'ing artwork http://t.co/Sit0P0KC</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've created a Crisis Map http://t.co/xyupHh3W &amp; Person Finder http://t.co/QNqi1qQs to help those in the Philippines after the typhoon</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A few Googlers created a holiday search tips rap video to help Santa w/ his big flight this year. Watch it at http://t.co/ihyq0DUC</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Create your own 2011 Green Scrapbook with top green trends this year - from red panda to backyard chickens http://t.co/DECRjVYI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fine-tune your stream, get more useful notifications, add managers to pages &amp; enjoy a redesigned Lightbox in Google+ http://t.co/fOKGICB2</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An exciting holiday deal w/ @Overstock is up for grabs on @googleoffers today in the U.S. Hurry! http://t.co/tn8d3BJQ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santa's on the line this holiday season - send a personalized msg from him, or call him from @gmail http://t.co/7Bb9VRRL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Recent updates from the Apps elves include improvements to @gmail iOS 4+ app &amp; saving screen space in Calendar http://t.co/XQkhnA5A</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch @ericschmidt take CNN's @erinburnett on a behind-the-scenes tour of our NY office http://t.co/sbnYLi1y</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Holiday cheer is here! Hurry for your chance to snag today's fun deal for @ToysRUs on @GoogleOffers (US/online only) http://t.co/iHIFpVL0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A follow up to yesterday's Zeitgeist, this time looking at local trends in cities across the U.S. http://t.co/X95OwxNP</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Browse, watch or play w/ all your favorite Google doodles on our updated site http://t.co/Uq2xxH9B</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @googlepubpolicy Watch the #SOPA hearing live now on http://t.co/P00sroFK - read Sergey's perspective http://t.co/Vh3Ad20X</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zeitgeist 2011: How the world searched this year http://t.co/RaiqLHRV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Search weather report: no major Panda updates until the new year. Context: http://t.co/nDkj74ou</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How Google Search &amp; Translate took one foodie from Las Vegas to Japan to discover real wasabi http://t.co/ZzXEXgQc #searchstories</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A bunch of updates to Google+ Hangouts, incl. starting hangouts from posts &amp; wider availability of Hangouts On Air http://t.co/iASA1Hoi</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This holiday season, we're making $40M in grants to support education, tech &amp; the fight against modern-day slavery http://t.co/5VKkXEoe</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Free calling in @gmail within the US and Canada through 2012: http://t.co/ZSHSD2ZK</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prospective &amp; current college students, here’s a new site with some tips &amp; tools to help you organize college life http://t.co/oRiOE3fO</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Panoramic imagery of the tsunami-affected areas of Japan is now available through Street View
http://t.co/VaDCYiGs</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bloggers: you can now share your posts directly to your circles on Google+. Learn more: http://t.co/5P8OSC2F (via @blogger)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our microchip doodle today is for Silicon Valley pioneer Robert Noyce on what would have been his 84th birthday http://t.co/aEqpijlN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've revamped Public Data Explorer (http://t.co/9sNMl8o9), a tool that organizes and visualizes public statistics http://t.co/23dupbtf</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Office Hours on Google+ starting at 1pm PT. @khanacademy &amp; Stanford profs discuss online education &amp; you can join http://t.co/3HETmJX5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Got what it takes to be 2011 Angry Birds College Champ? Prove it on Google+ this Sunday http://t.co/JdCnjgqH (via @googlestudents)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Everyday heroes will be spotlighted this Sunday on @CNN. Continue to donate to their causes online w/ Google Wallet http://t.co/2VXH2py9</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big Tent highlights w/ Eric Schmidt, Hillary Clinton &amp; others discussing free expression today in the Hague http://t.co/phHKXWFk</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Increased bargain hunting &amp; other holiday shopping trends on the web, plus the season's hottest gifts (on @WSJ) http://t.co/dOuE7zbu</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google Currents, a new reader app for Android &amp; iOS, gives you new ways to explore online content: http://t.co/6gDiJP4q (via @GoogleMobile)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@marissamayer at Le Web: “we save two years, every day, of idle time [by] using Google Maps and Navigation&quot; http://t.co/A6aeJ85t</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@HuffingtonPost lists 3 reasons for businesses to start a Google+ Page: connections, collaborations &amp; circles http://t.co/HlX6dmyG</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Feliz cumpleaños to Mexican artist &amp; muralist Diego Rivera. Our doodle today is in honor of his 125th birthday. http://t.co/NIIbWOet</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@ericschmidt, Hillary Clinton &amp; Dutch Foreign Minister address free expression in the Hague. Big Tent live stream at http://t.co/jct8SosJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations to Googlers Amit Singhal, Peter S. Magnusson &amp; Amin Vahdat who have been elected ACM Fellows in 2011 http://t.co/C2zz4MVX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google Goggles 1.7 for Android has continuous scan mode, text recognition &amp; better search results http://t.co/Ys00I00v</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our Politics &amp; Elections blog has the latest search data on Republican candidates, w/ Newt Gingrich out in front http://t.co/qPR1uzoW</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The places that benefit from the web are smaller than you might think. Saluting Europe's eTowns: http://t.co/yfNQNG8H</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Show your love for your favorite charities this holiday season on Google+. More about #CauseILoveEm: http://t.co/t8Eaxy2m</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sebastian Thrun shares his vision for self-driving cars w/ @nytimes http://t.co/sBsXInRH &amp; @huffingtonpost http://t.co/UpZaDyfy #18ideas</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today w/ President Sarkozy, @ericschmidt inaugurated our new French headquarters at an event in Paris http://t.co/41okKmav</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big Easy, Big Ideas. We supported Drew Brees' Trust Your Crazy Ideas Challenge for student entrepreneurs in New Orleans http://t.co/MjGqyKsE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The latest round of Google Research Awards for faculty funds 119 awards for a total of $6 million http://t.co/fmT9WaNg</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plot mathematical functions right on the search result page--type in a function and instantly see an interactive graph http://t.co/vBvxsmwX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Future scientists &amp; engineers in Western NC revved up their engines to compete in our inaugural soapbox car race http://t.co/qva2KT5Z</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now you can get flight info right in your Google search results on certain searches (US only right now) http://t.co/FC8ejrCa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In @bostonmagazine: how Google Boston is &quot;sort of like the Celtics&quot; &amp; our plans to expand our office there http://t.co/Dv6yoNDq</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A partnership w/ Sciences Po in Paris on an award for digital journalism http://t.co/1Avrm38X</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. CSEdWeek starts on Sun. Teachers, parents &amp; students--get involved with CS education. Find out how http://t.co/pEiKFKxA</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Searches for [black friday deals] were up by 30% from last year. More insights from the year's biggest shopping weekend http://t.co/VITYXrwL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Moving forward w/ our acquisition of Admeld http://t.co/7NvATM8k</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@youtube introduces a new homepage, Channel design and a fresh coat of digital paint http://t.co/QL052PwX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Search quality highlights, a new monthly series on algorithm changes, debuts on our Inside Search blog http://t.co/rKDn8A3H</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santa's back! Track his journey from the North Pole using @googleearth &amp; @googlemaps on http://t.co/pWgVOoZp. More at http://t.co/Fy2LsE3H</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@kingarthurflour began in 1790. 200+ years later, the VT flour company is an int'l business thanks to the web http://t.co/xtKymjC9</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our new Google bar inspired us to put together a brief history of Google’s navigation on our Google+ page http://t.co/gFsFRK3y</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tom Sawyer tricked his friends into helping celebrate Mark Twain's 176th birthday w/ a panoramic doodle http://t.co/3ponPAvE</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The next stage of our redesign—a new Google bar that will enable you to navigate quickly among our services http://t.co/ghvefZbe</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video: Director of Research Peter Norvig speaks @ComputerHistory Museum on the challenges &amp; promise of AI http://t.co/hvEcGbRF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cyber Monday sale from #GoogleMusic: new albums from Rihanna, Bieber, Gaga &amp; Drake $1.99 in @Android Market http://t.co/BxWf7mTG (U.S. only)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How the web is helping Egyptian voters become better informed &amp; enabling politicians to reach electors http://t.co/TTBdaBQ5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New dates for #io12: June 27-29. Keep up with I/O news on our Developers +page http://t.co/y9GoAdif</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's Cyber Monday, but before you whip out your credit card, read our 5 tips for stress-free holiday shopping http://t.co/Fzgew7L5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two contests to help stimulate innovation in digital journalism http://t.co/zFX2FFiA</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get your geek on w/ @Newegg special @GoogleOffers - $20 for $40 of gadgets, gizmos &amp; more. US only - shop now! http://t.co/C7dpHjse</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A new video shows you the evolution of search in 6 minutes, incl how far we've come &amp; what we think lies ahead http://t.co/Hed1hdTF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yesterday in Berlin, we held our 2nd Big Tent event, focused on online privacy. Highlights from the discussion: http://t.co/C54YHUOz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've made some updates to Google Product Search to make online shopping even easier http://t.co/HjHlJjcu</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A search story from an Aussie pilot who used Google Maps for Mobile to help his countrymen after Cyclone Yasi http://t.co/tQerpYMg</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As some of us prep for Thanksgiving, we've got some turkey day tips from the search team up on our Inside Search blog http://t.co/n2LeTqJt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bono &amp; Presidents Bush &amp; Clinton take questions in a special World AIDS Day event Dec 1. Ask yours now: http://t.co/tpeKHL90 (via @YouTube)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've got all the action from our student Lego robotics tournament, held at our headquarters last weekend http://t.co/xX0RICfb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy almost-Thanksgiving! Create your own &quot;hand turkey&quot; doodle &amp; share it on Google+ http://t.co/ArbI2JU2 http://t.co/sdiaRJm1</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>1000s of online accounts are hijacked daily. Add 2-step verification http://t.co/iX0zkAAw to your Google Account. More: http://t.co/NPCgS7Cc</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here's a fun one from @GoogleVentures: recommend what you like best w/ @StampedApp, founded by former Googlers http://t.co/4PM6rCMa.</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A complete redesign for the Google Search app for iPad. More interactive, more visual, &amp; easier to find what you need http://t.co/wEUBZmNS</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's time to hit the slopes-pick out your next ski destination with our Street View collection, ski &amp; snow edition http://t.co/w6KVyLbo</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tiny weather report: Minor Panda algorithm data refresh (affects &amp;lt;1% of searches). Context from Feb: http://t.co/uNvE7tJZ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Recent updates to Apps: easier scheduling in Calendar, @gmail app for iOS, 24/7 support for Apps customers &amp; more http://t.co/dVoSHaR8</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Use @googleearth to follow 4 wave-powered robotic gliders as they attempt to cross the Pacific ocean http://t.co/jdt9n0aN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New guides to help you connect w/ your community on Google+ http://t.co/Fimb4Y20</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Smile for the camera, or rather, the daguerreotype. It's Louis Daguerre's 224th birthday &amp; we've got a doodle http://t.co/Jnp4OvLV</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Students interested in open source can register now for our Google Code-in contest, which starts Mon 11/21 http://t.co/0HiPipOJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrating LEO, the world's first business computer, which took on its first office job 60 years ago today http://t.co/gmx9DgYt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tap, pay and save at Gap Inc., our latest merchant to accept Google Wallet  http://t.co/AkEcwhsa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tune in to http://t.co/TjPQ0zMF today at 2pm PT for a rockin' livestream. Make sure to turn up your volume to 11.</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Show us what you can do to get students excited about STEM and CS: applications now open for Google RISE Awards http://t.co/L6HEr3Qz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>5 Google tools tips every journalist needs from @jaclyntrop on @mediabistro http://t.co/lk62i6if</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Verbatim: a more deliberate way to tell Google to search using your exact terms. More on the Inside Search blog http://t.co/IzEmfmWn</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How Orabrush became a multi-million dollar business using @youtube  http://t.co/L8prggG4</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Learn how to bring your company &amp; customers closer together using Google+. Join our webinar on Wed, 2pm EST http://t.co/Uzu0z3Qe</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Explanations of 10 recent changes to our search algorithm on our Inside Search blog http://t.co/IVH0Ul1P</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What better place to start helping businesses go mobile than in Mobile, Alabama? http://t.co/YqLuqChC</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On Veterans Day, here are some tools &amp; platforms to help servicemembers &amp; their families http://t.co/YOUvNZOC. Thank you for all you do.</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Everyday people are changing the world - and you can help. Donate to @CNN Heroes through Google Checkout http://t.co/gd3lMzJp</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Googlers marked Breast Cancer Awareness Month w/ the Pink Pin Initiative &amp; other office events http://t.co/7AZZYITS</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're partnering with @startupweekend to help developers and entrepreneurs around the world launch new startups: http://t.co/tIBvr9ml</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Score one for Mona Lisa: The +1 button is now available for Google Images http://t.co/lDMqy270</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Looking for the photography stars of the future: Introducing the Google Photography Prize for students http://t.co/iIAc3oKd</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Think Insights with Google is out of beta, w/ new trends, facts &amp; tools like the Real Time Insights Finder http://t.co/erDE0ruB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our L.A. office opened last week and we've got some great photos up on our Google+ page http://t.co/po4qfX0g</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@googleoffers now in more cities across the US. See the latest deals in LA, Chicago, Atlanta, Houston &amp; Brooklyn http://t.co/dJsyCZyA</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In time for the holidays, Martha Stewart drops in to discuss her new book, how tech shaped her empire &amp; turkey tips http://t.co/IQ6Xay3s</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Visit our new Google+ page, add us to your circles &amp; find a list of other pages from Google http://t.co/e6doAU1Q</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Working w/ the U.S. Dept of Veterans Affairs to build a custom job search engine to help veterans &amp; their families http://t.co/mUukI28W</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>43% of online adults would give up beer for a month to keep their smartphone. More stats for mobile marketers via AdAge http://t.co/bv708B81</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A doodle for Nobel Prize winner Marie Curie, who brought us radioactivity, polonium &amp; radium, on her 144th birthday. http://t.co/pQz0hzWz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>David Lawee in @sfgate on what makes a successful acquisition: &quot;Come in, execute huge, go be big, &amp; run the company&quot; http://t.co/BYQwVkwH</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @GoogleAtWork The horns are hooked! Welcome UT Austin to the Google Apps for Edu family http://t.co/utWjt6J3</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You can now watch the annual Islamic ritual of the Hajj live from Mecca http://t.co/SCrR2tNa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Shipping the Google in Google+ with @youtube &amp; @googlechrome integrations http://t.co/U9La252f</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Curious about #mobile marketing &amp; mobile analytics? @avinash shares examples &amp; best practices: http://t.co/Mm79ZWri</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A freshness algorithm tweak better predicts which results you're looking for, today's, last week's, or last year's http://t.co/poMY3qGS</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SVP Advertising Susan Wojcicki in @TIMEIdeas: careers in technology can be a great growth opportunity for women http://t.co/y8PlPrOY</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We want to showcase our @SketchUp users, designing everything from bridges to robots. More on how to share your story http://t.co/snkf79x7</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hail to the Victors - the University of Michigan has #goneGoogle w/ Google Apps for Education http://t.co/fNFLnRqO</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An improved local search experience: a righthand panel now displays place info like map, pics &amp; summary http://t.co/fALAChud</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A director for Search discusses the nuances of personalization in search results w/ @stonetemple http://t.co/hi6INRDN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New from @googlecse: Thumbnail images in search results - no work required http://t.co/wRp3uSkz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now in Street View: some of the world’s most beautiful parks, including Kensington Gardens &amp; @highlinenyc http://t.co/HZSJ63yb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Don’t ask for the meaning, ask for the use. &quot;A look at the fascinating world of Google Translate from @Slate http://t.co/osd6hGbJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An in-depth overview of @gmail's new design http://t.co/GCsrDT62 To try it, look for &quot;Switch to the new look&quot; in Gmail soon</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Put a stop to pinching &amp; zooming. Grow your business with a mobile-friendly website http://t.co/IVvxbS5A #gomobile</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Providing greater transparency &amp; choice re: the ads you see on search &amp; @gmail http://t.co/rndGbxTr</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Life in a Day is coming home to @YouTube - watch it in its entirety for free http://t.co/CmzFJcX8</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Halloween! To create this year's video doodle, the team hand-carved 6 truly giant pumpkins http://t.co/kLQtNQhl</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Has there ever been a perfect game during the #worldseries? Maybe we'll see one tonight ;) /cc @MLB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>When it comes to Halloween costume searches, this year is the battle of the birds http://t.co/J96ZllUx</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>via @GoogleTV An update to #GoogleTV is coming http://t.co/RFJRSOKy - see the new website http://t.co/YhtLqZZI</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google+ has gone ghoulish for #gplushalloween. Spook-ify your profile w/ the new Creative Kit http://t.co/WjBjLcEX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More local deals in @googleoffers thx to new deal provider partners. Plus, new personalization options http://t.co/1g9RCkS1</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our Aussie engineers went to the Outback &amp; Great Barrier Reef to test #voicesearch. Watch the experiments: http://t.co/bx91YknU</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Helping SMBs connect w/ experts who can help them make the most of their online advertising campaigns http://t.co/fusWDIH5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Let freedom (from servers) ring! Celebrated 15M users, new schools &amp; new apps integrations at #Edu2011 http://t.co/QAWphhpC</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We launched a landing page &amp; earthquake map to share up-to-date info on the earthquake in Van, Turkey http://t.co/PYzcuVm7</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congrats Lorraine Twohill, @adweek Brand Genius. Her take on marketing: &quot;know the user, know the magic &amp; connect the 2&quot; http://t.co/0kF6OOgL</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're on a roll: @googleoffers comes to 4 new cities today: Baltimore, Minneapolis, San Diego &amp; San Jose http://t.co/eFJn5JJR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More apps &amp; a brand new look for the #ChromeWebStore + a new stable release of @googlechrome http://t.co/VJwDnli6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See how many government requests we got for the first half of 2011 on the Transparency Report http://t.co/4p3AhbWQ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>via @googlepubpolicy Silicon Valley Human Rights Conference starts tmrw. Speeches &amp; panels livestreamed @citizentube http://t.co/urPSBfdC</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reading @jtemple's Q&amp;A w/ @GoogleVentures' Bill Maris - investing in companies doing &quot;uncomfortably difficult&quot; things http://t.co/4b2Xv12P</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Person Finder launched in Turkish for people looking for their loved ones following the earthquake http://t.co/XpZaK7zB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Recent updates to Apps: presentations reloaded, better @googledocs on Android tablets, charts in Sites &amp; more http://t.co/fcRPO196</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's &quot;It's a Small World&quot;-inspired doodle celebrates Mary Blair, Disney animator/artist http://t.co/WV12UXV5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Online platforms including @youtube are playing a part in Tunisia's upcoming free elections http://t.co/mfgqlfXa</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Peruse the famous Neiman Marcus Christmas Book on Google Catalogs for customizable cupcake cars, mermaid suits &amp; more http://t.co/Vp0ekEaJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A music teacher turned millionaire by pitching the perfect game, which he taught himself how to do entirely online http://t.co/adMyCUci</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Media folks: @ijnet names 5 Google tools journalists don't use but should http://t.co/9L4Ga3R8</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congrats to our own search star, Amit Singhal, for his UBM Outstanding Achievement in Science &amp; Tech award! http://t.co/eLtxygkR</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Street View trike takes to the train tracks to capture the stunning Swiss Alps http://t.co/LuFf84iM</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hold the phone. Cool stat via @googlemobileads: Click to call ads generating millions of calls/week for businesses http://t.co/kt3BiVgt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Just in time for the first pitch of the World Series, some baseball playoff search trends http://t.co/J0PCrAyM</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New Visitors Flow &amp; Goal Flow in @googleanalytics enables you to analyze site insights graphically &amp; instantly http://t.co/F44eyb28</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How scientists combined gene sequencing technology w/ @googleearth to map the spread of typhoid in Nepal http://t.co/0Pcojzty</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Keep up w/ the places that matter to you, http://t.co/EuK1HoUh is now available in 43 new languages  http://t.co/STbjgDrt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch the live stream of Vic Gundotra &amp; Sergey Brin at #w2s (in progress now) http://t.co/H34XS7S0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On Nov 2, @Avinash Kaushik hosts a webinar on how mobile advertising + analytics = awesome. Register: http://t.co/qpaw5LQh #knowledge</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Mo-mentum&quot; - new mobile search ad formats to help businesses benefit from mobile advertising http://t.co/7eHHhLs0</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Working w/ the European Patent Office to use our translation technology to process patents into 32 languages http://t.co/68ZF36jr @signalmag</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mondo Media becomes 19th company to join the 1 billion views club on @youtube. @mlhumph3 chats w/ the CEO on @Forbes http://t.co/nEE9Kwo8</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Introducing Ice Cream Sandwich, the delicious new version of @Android on Galaxy Nexus http://t.co/SEz94iS5 (cc @googlenexus)</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In 2 hours (7PM Pacific Time) tune in for a live stream of what's new from @Android - http://t.co/TjPQ0zMF</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Travel legend Arthur Frommer on the best Google Maps &amp; Translate tools for local &amp; travel info on &quot;The Travel Show&quot; http://t.co/wwB6i1H9</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Designing a virtual bookcase for the digital world http://t.co/hlzdJrmm, play w/ it on our Chrome experiments page http://t.co/JsuKUAIh</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Making search more secure with SSL by default for http://t.co/nD6f8OlP  http://t.co/r1QOHCUc</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rob Pike http://t.co/ymFaUTlB &amp; Alfred Spector http://t.co/83hEc0fd remember Dennis Ritchie, creator of C &amp; co-creator of UNIX</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@washingtonpost on our Amazon Street View trip &amp; why a village expected a famous TV host, not a group of Googlers http://t.co/y3eJr0vM</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@youtube Merch Store: buy artists’ merchandise, digital downloads, concert tickets &amp; more directly on their channels http://t.co/6dNV3YPz</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Previewing a new version of @googledocs presentations w/ more collaboration &amp; 50+ new features http://t.co/PfFrhzXm</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At select stores you can not only pay, but redeem coupons &amp;/or earn rewards point w/ a single tap in Google Wallet http://t.co/T4jL3ci5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Save the date for @googleio 2012, now scheduled for April 24-25 http://t.co/6MpcGQX5 #io12</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Good to know: Practical guidance on safe passwords, keeping online accounts secure &amp; more on a new site http://t.co/I6ySTLL6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The buzz from our 2nd annual honey harvest at our &quot;Hiveplex&quot; in Mountain View, CA http://t.co/YstR6DFt</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Thailand faces its worst flooding in 50 yrs. For local info, resources &amp; ways you can help, CrisisMap &amp; info pg here http://t.co/Off6yBfc</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Director of Research Peter Norvig talks to @stonetemple about how search is evolving, thanks to AI algorithms http://t.co/wmryiI2H</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On @HuffingtonPost Claire Hughes Johnson, VP, global online sales, lists 5 easy ways for businesses to move into mobile http://t.co/N1zbqy3R</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#googlewallet meets NY &amp; SF at @american_eagle @Walgreens @macys &amp; @DUANEREADE. It's a hit! http://t.co/BnTbKnbd #whereiswallet</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get a deep dive into your blog's metrics by connecting your @googleanalytics account with your @blogger blog http://t.co/CBwBOZm4</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Give a warm Twitter welcome to @Android... &amp; a new friend who arrived on campus today: http://t.co/Lbf5W4fB</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Let's chat: Conversation Mode on Google Translate for Android expands to 14 languages + more features http://t.co/G3mBoKh5</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our third quarter 2011 financial results http://t.co/VysGGm7K</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It’s on us today! Find #googlewallet in Union Square SF or Times Square NY &amp; tap to get a free @cocacola #WhereisWallet</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CIO Ben Fried @ Web 2.0 Expo in NYC - why IT needs to embrace user choice and the cloud to stay competitive http://t.co/rLHRNwaT #w2e</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've brought WebGL to @googlemaps for 3D buildings, smoother transition to Street View &amp; more. Video &amp; info here http://t.co/L8yxUG8N</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@googlebooks is at @bostonbookfest - visit us at our Google eBooks Petting Zoo + panels http://t.co/QadahiT6</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now you can manage your Custom Search Engines from within Webmaster Tools http://t.co/MnhxJJ31 via @googlecse</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How can Google Docs &amp; Voice Search satisfy your hunger? @sacbee_news explains how to use technology in the kitchen http://t.co/ao5AFRax</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Claire Hughes Johnson explains how small businesses can get into mobile marketing on @HuffingtonPost http://t.co/CjORnolN</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Making @gmail more accessible in places lacking easy access to computers/smartphones http://t.co/Dik0vQs9</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's a Google Wallet tapping spree at American Eagle Outfitters in Times Square in NYC this October http://t.co/yqs85HAG</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@cbsmoneywatch shares some tips &amp; tricks to help maximize your job hunt w/ Google Search http://t.co/fl1fmsiJ</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy birthday to Art Clokey, creator of Gumby! Click on today's doodle for a stop motion clay animation homage http://t.co/gQY7jOfn</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get your e-commerce site ready for this holiday season's mobile searchers w/ Google Commerce Search http://t.co/1KJu8gqH</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We sponsored the 2011 Green Flight Challenge to help create more efficient aircraft - read about the results http://t.co/uavaQECb</text>
    <name>A Googler</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>