<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">
  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Fed stress test results to be released today at 4:30pm ET</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sources: Bank of America Passes Fed Stress Test; Bank of America Hasn't Asked for New Buyback or Dividend Increase - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(More) JPMorgan Buyback: $12B Approved for 2012, $3B approved thru end of Q1 2013</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(More) JPMorgan: Fed Did Not Object to Firm's Capital Distributions.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>JPMorgan Boosts Dividend to $0.30 from $0.25, Announces $15B Buyback.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Goldman to pay $7M to CFTC for  supervision failures in handling accounts.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CFTC sues MBF Clearing for allegedly failing to segregate customer accts. MBF: Placed funds in acct. to protect cstmrs from Lehman collapse.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FOMC: Voted 9-1 For Fed Funds Rate Action - Economy Has Been Expanding Moderately - Oil And Gas Prices Have Increased; Inflation Subdued</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Fed Leaves Interest Rates Unchanged - More on @CNBC -TV and http://t.co/lvqIzbia http://t.co/efq1jsNH</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>WSJ: Dell To Pay About $1.2B For SonicWall - Sources</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Fitch upgrades Greece to B- from 'restricted default'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Walt Disney Co. shareholders reelected 10 members of the board during the company's annual shareholder meeting.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nassim Taleb tells CNBC he owns stocks because he doesn’t trust Treasury bonds. Watch full interview: http://t.co/oLHaXDFr</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama: We will work every day to give U.S. businesses a fair shot, our trade cases against China have helped</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama: China' handling of rare earths violates the policy it agreed to; U.S. manufacturers need fair access to China's rare earths.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama: Newly signed bill will help fight unfair competition in global markets: new trade case vs. China involves rare earths.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama: I'm confident that we can continue meeting objectives in Afghanistan.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama: We have strategy to responsibly wind down Afghanistan war.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pres. Obama to make remarks on trade with China shortly. Live coverage on @CNBC and http://t.co/hCq4Rp1S.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>S&amp;amp;P, Dow, &amp;amp; Nasdaq all looking at new closing highs. Homebuilder rally continues. $MAS among CYC leaders, up 4.8% in Mar. (via @BobPisani)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@SouthwestAir doesn't expect to report a profit this quarter due to fuel prices. Last time Southwest didn't report a profit was Q3 2009.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: January business inventories increased by 0.7%, above expectations for a 0.5% rise.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market update: Just after the open today, the Vix dropped to 13.99. The Vix hasn't been that low since June 20th, 2007.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Murphy Oil Chairman William Nolan Passes Away At Age 72</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks to Watch: Tuesday's early morning movers http://t.co/ZTpzF0QH via @peterschack</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: February retail sales up 1.1%, the largest rise since September.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jefferies ups Apple price target to $699. Says &quot;evidence of commercial iTV production is startling.&quot; Sees Q4 launch. (via @carlquintanilla)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: NFIB Survey finds small business optimism up for 6th straight month http://t.co/SdfPHKcU</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pre-market report: Futures pointed to a higher open ahead of the Fed's statement on interest rates. http://t.co/8DYZIozK</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNBCSquawkSt: TODAY: The Black Swan returns! Tune into @CNBCSquawkSt at 11am ET for Nassim Taleb's first @CNBC interview since 2010.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tomorrow @ 10pET on @CNBC. Watch #60Minutes for an inside look at Carl Icahn. Video: http://t.co/EZ5oC4Y5</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you #watchingcnbc? What do you think of the &quot;Gold&quot; premiere? Follow @CNBCOriginals for more about the #Gold documentary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Go inside the #Gold mines of Johannesburg, South Africa. Watch @CNBC tonight at 9pET/PT. http://t.co/9oQPEMTQ #WatchingCNBC</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US Airways Registers Multiple Internet Domain Names Suggesting Possible American Air Transaction  $LCC  http://t.co/xqfikyOc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>EIA: U.S. Gasoline Prices Up 3.6 cents to $3.829/Gallon in Latest Week</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook Re: Yahoo Lawsuit:  &quot;We will defend ourselves vigorously against these puzzling actions.&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook re: Yahoo Lawsuit:  &quot;We're disappointed that Yahoo's effort to engage with us was limited to a few short phone calls&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Earnings Alert: Urban Outfitters (URBN) Q4 EPS $0.27 vs. $0.29 Est.; Urban Outfitters (URBN) Q4 Revs. $731m vs. $740m Est.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. markets at the close: Dow Industrials +0.29%, Nasdaq -0.16%, S&amp;amp;P 500 +0.02%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lawsuit: Yahoo sues Facebook over 10 patents and says has long history of innovation - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CME Group: CEO Craig Donohue will step down when contract expires in Dec. 2012; President Phupinder Gill new CEO as part of succession plan.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kazuo Okada Countersues Wynn Resorts; Okada Alleges Wynn Board Violated Fiduciary Duties - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. budget deficit rose in February, on pace to top $1T again - AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple to CNBC: &quot;Customer response to the new iPad has been off the charts and the quantity available for pre-order has been purchased&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pacific Gas &amp;amp; Electric agrees to pay $70M restitution for 2010 pipeline blast that killed 8 - AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ALERT: $25B Mortgage Servicing Agreement Filed in Federal Court</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global Update: European shares dip as euro zone debt concerns moved west to Spain &amp;amp; other peripheral countries. Story: http://t.co/SpwGL0GM</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ALERT: The Volatility Index hit a low of 15.23 in today’s trading session, its lowest level since July 1, 2011.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ALERT: The Greek Finance Ministry says it has lightened the country's crushing debt load by completing a swap of bonds worth €177.2 billion.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Japan’s Asahi Kasei will buy U.S. medical equipment maker $ZOLL Medical for $2.21 billion. Story: http://t.co/wkdoId7u</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Would you know the value of this #Goldbar? Make sure to watch @CNBC today, for your chance to guess and win! http://t.co/3vCbimNC</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Youku To Buy Rival Tudou For $1B+ In Stock  http://t.co/7AQX0PhC</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Euro Zone Ministers To Sign Off On Greek Deal Today.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>PepsiCo Announces Executive Moves http://t.co/SXyClHNF</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Employers should brace themselves for a less-than-productive Monday. Story: http://t.co/fL28VBXH</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Instagram's Kevin Systrom says app is coming to Android &quot;very soon.&quot; Also, &quot;We're shooting for (900M active users).&quot; http://t.co/VMN5gCAM</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today marks the one year anniversary of the devastating Fukushima earthquake: http://t.co/c8F4ftb1 Japan observed a minute of silence.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Would you know the value of this #Goldbar. Watch @CNBC on Monday, for your chance to guess and win. Photo: http://t.co/c3IQ4aOi #Goldbar</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tomorrow @ 10pET on @CNBC. Watch #60Minutes for an inside look at Carl Icahn. Video: http://t.co/EZ5oC4Y5</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you always looking for new ways to &quot;Better your Business&quot;? Find out more here: http://t.co/uZOW6PdT</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Mitt Romney the projected winner in Wyoming - GOP Caucus</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Rick Santorum as the projected winner in Kansas - GOP Caucus.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Make sure to watch CNBC Monday, for a chance to win a prize. Follow @CNBC for more details. #Goldbar http://t.co/c3IQ4aOi</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On March 12th @ 9pET, @CNBC reveals unprecedented access to the #Gold industry. http://t.co/2Ohf69He #CNBCGold</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNBCoriginals Make sure to watch CNBC Monday, for a chance to win a prize. Follow @CNBC for more details. #Goldbar http://t.co/c3IQ4aOi</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight @ 8pET on @CNBC. Watch @ApprenticeNBC and @realDonaldTrump. More about the show: http://t.co/DoZoKT1K #watchingcnbc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Federal Energy Regulatory Commission approves proposed merger of Exelon &amp;amp; Constellation Energy. $EXC $CEG</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Moody's Considers Greece to Have Defaulted, Will Revisit Greece's Rating &quot;In Due Course&quot; to Reflect Bond Swap, Rating Unchanged</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GE CEO Immelt's 2011 Compensation Rises to $21.6m from $21.4m in 2010.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roubini live on @CNBCClosingBell: Eventually we'll see risk of a hard landing in China rising.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roubini live on @CNBCClosingBell: Portugal likely the next country in need of restructuring.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roubini live on @CNBCClosingBell: Eventually, Greece will be the first country to exit the Euro Zone.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roubini live on @CNBCClosingBell: Oil prices likely to continue rising and U.S data is mixed; continue to see anemic global recovery in 2012</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roubini live on @CNBCClosingBell: Don't expect systemic event out of today's Greek credit event; Greek announcement is a positive.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IMF's Lagarde on Greece: Intend to recommend €28B arrangement under EFF to support Greece's ambitious economic program over next four years.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Comscore: Yahoo lost web search market share for 6th straight month in Feb.; Yahoo search market share at 13.8%, down from 16.3% in Aug.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. markets at the close: Dow Industrials +0.11%, NASDAQ +0.60%, S&amp;amp;P 500 +0.36%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US regulator approves Capital One purchase of HSBC credit card portfolio - DJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First On @CNBC- ISDA CEO Pickel: Hard to say if we'l get additional defaults going forward; this was fully expected. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ISDA CEO Pickel LIVE in a First on CNBC interview: People will read what's happened as a default for Greece. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ISDA CEO Pickel live on @CNBCClosingBell reacting to Greek credit event: What we've decided today is something we anticipated for a while.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Robert Pickel, ISDA CEO, is live on @CNBCClosingBell right now with reaction to the Greek credit event.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>STORY: Greece Default Is Official; Insurance Payouts Triggered. http://t.co/JwTgwUMG #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ISDA: Vote on Greek credit event was unanimous after sovereign debt restructuring. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(More) ISDA: Auction related to outstanding CDS transactions to be held on March 19. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ISDA: Greece Restructuring Triggers Credit Event. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crude oil settle up $0.82 at $107.40/barrel.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President Obama appoints Todd Park as Chief Technology Officer.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>EPA to retest Wyoming water said tainted by fracking - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FTC Increasingly Unlikely To Block Express Scripts-Medco Deal, Sources Say - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations to @ejmoosa, winner of @CNBCSquawkSt’s #nailthenumber contest!</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>California jobless rate falls below 11% for the first time since April 2009 - AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF Managing Director live on @CNBCSquawkSt: Investors in European debt will have to do more careful risk analysis.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF Managing Director live on @CNBCSquawkSt: Unfortunate that prior Greek bonds did not have CACs.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF Managing Director live on @CNBCSquawkSt: The voluntary, negotiated nature of this deal is notable.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF Managing Director live on @CNBCSquawkSt: Too see so many bondholder cooperate in Greek debt swap is quite remarkable.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF Managing Director live on @CNBCSquawkSt: Pleased with the outcome of the Greek debt swap, would call it &quot;successful.&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First on CNBC: Managing Director of the IIF, Charles Dallara, talks to @MCaruso_Cabrera LIVE on @CNBCSquawkSt now.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GE's Immelt: Increased Dividends A Top Priority For GE's Excess Cash; $30B In Available Cash Over Next Few Years - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Greek Cabinet Approves Activation Of Collective Action Clause - DJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>63% of wealthy Americans think the U.S. is still in a recession. Poll results here: http://t.co/To2n2ZRc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: El Paso shareholders vote to approve $23B acquisition by Kinder Morgan</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Fitch cuts Greece rating to &quot;restricted default&quot; over debt swap</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First on CNBC Alert: @MCaruso_Cabrera speaks w/ Charles Dallara, Managing Director of the IIF today at 11:30am ET - http://t.co/zuFxr2qk</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“I think we’re at a bottom, I really do. I think we’re gonna have a rally.” – Mark Haines, 3 years ago today. http://t.co/EPwWdhV1</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @jimforkincnbc: Hearing has been added in the case of the Madoff Trustee v. the Mets owners.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Unemployment rate remains flat at 8.3% even as payrolls grow 227,000. Full story: http://t.co/VzboRt3u #jobsfriday</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. trade deficit $52.57B (January) vs. $50.42B (December)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>January nonfarm payrolls revised up from 243k to 284k. December nonfarm payrolls revised up from 203k jobs to 223k jobs.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>February Employment Report: Nonfarm Payrolls up 227,000. The unemployment rate comes in at 8.3%. #breaking</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks to Watch: Friday's early morning movers http://t.co/cB0P2TqS</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polls are closing soon! Cast your vote in the #nailthenumber contest on @CNBCSquawkSt. Winner gets a tote bag signed by @jimcramer.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ann Inc. Beats Estimates http://t.co/rBBrVoVr #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Interested in what goes on behind the scenes of @CNBC documentaries and series? Follow @CNBCOriginals for exclusive content and show updates</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you watching Pill Poppers on @CNBC? Were you surprised to see that many drugs can now be used to treat multiple medical conditions?</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight at 10p ET/PT on @CNBC. Watch &quot;Pill Poppers&quot; for an inside look at the pharmaceuticals industry. Learn more: http://t.co/mLazdTFP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Citigroup to nominate Roche’s Humer to Board</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wynn Dispute: Judge rules Okada can see some financial information; Wynn Resorts seeks to oust Okada from board.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Starbucks CEO: Verismo machine will compliment Green Mountain; Verismo will make Starbucks-quality espresso beverages.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Starbucks CEO: Starbucks announces single cup machine called Verismo; Starbucks started working on Verismo 3 years ago</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Earnings Alert: Aeropostale Q4 Revs $808M vs. $804M est., Q4 EPS $0.44 vs. $0.32 est.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Everyone's talking about the same thing at this year's Montgomery Tech Conf: The #FacebookIPO effect. Here's why: http://t.co/7Yc63Fma</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Texas Instruments cuts Q1 guidance; Texas Instruments sees Q1 EPS $0.15-$0.19 vs. $0.31 est., Q1 Revs. $2.99B-$3.11B vs. $3.16B est.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AMR Asks Judge for 6-Month Extension of Exclusivity Period; AMR's Exclusive Rights to Field a Reorganization Plan Ends on Mar. 28 - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Green Mountain Coffee shares slide 21% after Starbucks announces new premium coffee initiative. $GMCR</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Senate Democrats reject Republican bid to fast-track Keystone XL pipeline project - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Greek Govt Official Tells @CNBC Debt Swap Participation Rate Exceeds 90%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SEC Charges Former Executive at Coca-Cola Bottling Company with Insider Trading $KO</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Verizon Wireless to Close Several Customer Service Centers -As Many As 3,175 Employees May Be Affected by Verizon Closures - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Participation Tops 85% in Greek bond Swap - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Photo-Sharing App Instagram Close To Raising $40M At $500M Valuation-Fundraising Comes Despite Skepticism About Revenue Potential –WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Check: Stocks up for 2nd day. S&amp;P and Nasdaq have erased all of their Tuesday losses. http://t.co/Nxt8sWXm</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Colgate-Palmolive Raises Quarterly Dividend To 62 Cents/Share From 58 Cents $CL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up on @PowerLunch Robert Kindler, Global Head of M&amp;A, Morgan Stanley  http://t.co/P3RHFHDm</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wells Fargo to begin charging some customers $7/month fee. New fee can be avoided with minimum balances &amp; direct deposits. - @AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>House passes the Jumpstart our Business Startups Act (or JOBS Act bill) by 390-23 margin. The Senate is working on its own version.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Q4 consumer credit rebounds to $2.5T; highest level since Q1 2009.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Household debt up by .25% in Q3. This is the first gain since Q2 2008.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(More) Morgan Stanley: We continue to investigate allegations against the broker. No charges have been brought against the broker.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Morgan Stanley broker connected to alleged madam placed on leave. Broker maintains he had no involvement with criminal activity.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bill Ackman shares his economic outlook &amp; investment strategy w/ @andrewrsorkin LIVE from the Tulane M&amp;A Conf. VIDEO: http://t.co/pCxACs70</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nice set-up, thx for watching! MT @JesseLammi: Perfect set up @CNBC watching the market between classes #uofm  http://t.co/q3FBQivI</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Greek Govt Official: Debt swap take-up now above 70% - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Manufacturing jobs abound, yet it's hard for companies to find skilled workers. The story: http://t.co/oNtd52yZ (via @Lebeaucarnews)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Slideshow: Suze Orman's Rules for Lending Money - http://t.co/778uqfZc (via @SuzeOrmanShow)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BMW Group 2011 net profit jumps 51.3% to record $6.38 Billion. (via @Lebeaucarnews)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNBCSquawkSt: Big Friday jobs report means one thing: #NailTheNumber! Guess nonfarm, win this very handy (see avatar) and signed tote!</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ECB's Draghi hints ECB may be done with long-term liquidity injections (LTRO), sees &quot;signs of stabilization in the Euro area economy.&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why a Greek Debt Deal Won’t End the Greek Saga http://t.co/SDUAzhtX</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch LIVE video of the ECB Press Conference: http://t.co/ZmdWKoog</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: New claims for unemployment benefits increased 8,000 to 362,000 for week ended 3/3.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>McDonald's February Sales Short of Estimates http://t.co/RloioCPA</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ECB leaves benchmark interest rates unchanged at 1.0%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gov officials increasingly worried about market moving data leaking to traders. @EamonJavers explains http://t.co/J7yQoeFY</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CHALLENGER: FEBRUARY JOB CUTS DIP TO 51,758 vs. 53,486 In January</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Challenger Report: Job Cuts Down 3% In February</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bank of England Leaves Rates Unchanged</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Smithfield Foods Beats Estimates http://t.co/QD5s3aXg #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Williams-Sonoma Beats Estimates http://t.co/Y4nOQwVd #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you #watchingcnbc? What do you think of tonight's episode investigating Raj Rajaratnam and his insider trading ring?</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch an all new #AmericanGreed tonight @ 10p. See how Raj Rajaratnam made millions with inside information. http://t.co/T2xLWnJc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight @ 10pET on @CNBC. @AmericanGreedTV investigates Raj Rajaratnam and his insider trading ring. Clip:http://t.co/T2xLWnJc #watchingcnbc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>S&amp;P Announces Crown Castle $CCI to Replace Constellation Energy $CEG in S&amp;P 500</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook To Open a $5B Credit Facility at LIBOR + 1% Rate - Facebook Opening Bridge Facility For Up To $3B #FacebookIPO</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook Amends IPO Filing -Additional Facebook Underwriters include: @CitiBank , Credit Suisse,Deutsche Bank, RBC &amp; Lazard #FacebookIPO</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US Treasury: Launching $6B Offering Of AIG Common Stock  $AIG</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook's short-term facility would cover RSU obligations of ~$2.5B. New credit facility would expand existing $2.5B facility. (2/2)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNBC's @kaylatausche: #Facebook seen sealing 2-part $7.5B+ credit facility. (1/2)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pfizer Rejects Novartis Bid For Animal Health Unit - Novartis Offered $15B-$16B for Pfizer Animal Health Unit-WSJ  http://t.co/Miftjdlk</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Consumer Credit Surged 8.6% In Jan, 2nd Largest Gain Since 2004</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The new iPad's name? &quot;The new iPad&quot;.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple shares have turned lower for the first time today. Quote: http://t.co/kzPLADfb $AAPL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More on iPad pricing: Apple's new 4G LTE iPad starts at $629. $AAPL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple says new iPad to start at $499 for 16GB, available on March 16. $AAPL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More iPad features: HD video recording at 1080p, video stabilization, voice dictation, 4G LTE. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More details on the new iPad: 44% greater color saturation, A5X chip is quad core. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tim Cook has now returned to the stage, says Apple TV is still $99, available next week &amp; you can order today. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There is a new Apple TV box that supports 1080p. Eddie Cue taking stage to demo Apple TV - an update to the $99 box. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tim Cook: iCloud has over 100m customers &amp; now supports movies. You can redownload movies &amp; TV shows w/ 1080p support. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tim Cook says the iPad is outstripping the wildest of predictions. 76% of revenues came from post PC devices last year. (via @jonfortt)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Let the Apple live tweeting begin: @JonFortt reports that Tim Cook has taken the stage. $AAPL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We are minutes away from big Apple announcement. You can follow @jonfortt's live blog here: http://t.co/3pDkcvkU $AAPL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Colts choose to release Peyton Manning instead of paying him $28 million bonus. (via @DarrenRovell) VIDEO: http://t.co/mSSQwG8J</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Peyton Manning released by the Colts. Team to retire Manning's Number 18.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @PowerLunch: Counting down to the #Apple event - 1 hr to go! @JonFortt will give Power Lunch live updates from inside the event.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>European Market Close: Shares closed up on renewed confidence about Greece's bond swap offer to private creditors. http://cnb.cx/xwm20m</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Birthday, Art Cashin!</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Check: Stocks rebound after yesterday's sell-off helped by better-than-expected ADP report. http://t.co/7AzsCYXF</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>VIDEO: Watch @MittRomney's full interview on @SquawkCNBC -  http://t.co/WjQgswQe</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Follow @SquawkCNBC for a live tweet of the @MittRomney interview happening right now on @CNBC.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@MittRomney on @CNBC: We think we'll get the necessary delegates before the convention. There will not be a brokered convention.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@MittRomney on @CNBC: I know people will attack me on personal level. I'm prepared for it.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@MittRomney LIVE on @CNBC: President can't control gas prices, but he can keep the money in the U.S.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ADP private sector payrolls up 216,000 in February. ADP shows 25th consecutive monthly gain in private employment.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mortgage Applications Fall 1.2%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GE Confirms Outlook For Double-Digit Growth http://t.co/WoNdvMEP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A big morning coming up on @SquawkCNBC : Cong. @ericcantor,@lululemon CEO Christine Day, &amp; @MittRomney. Tune in to @CNBC !</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News calls Mitt Romney the apparent winner in Ohio GOP primary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News projects Mitt Romney has won Idaho GOP caucus.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @JohnJHarwood: Team Romney says outstanding Cuyahoga County (Cleveland) vote can put him over top in OH</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@CNBC Exclusive tomorrow morning: @MittRomney on @SquawkCNBC at 8:45a ET.  #YourMoneyYourVote</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Rick Santorum as the projected winner in North Dakota GOP Caucus</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Rick Santorum the projected winner in Oklahoma.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Rick Santorum the projected winner in Tennessee.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@MariaBartiromo and @JohnJHarwood are live on @CNBC right now with #YourMoneyYourVote coverage of &quot;Super Tuesday&quot; 2012. Tune in now!</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares the Tennessee GOP Primary as 'Too Early to Call'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares the Oklahoma GOP Primary as 'Too Early to Call'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares @MittRomney the projected winner in Massachusetts GOP Primary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Mitt Romney as the projected winner in Vermont GOP Primary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News source: Newt Gingrich to start receiving Secret Service protection tomorrow.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares the Ohio GOP Primary as 'Too Close to Call’</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Mitt Romney as the projected winner in Virginia GOP Primary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Asia Stock Markets Open Down 1.0-1.5% following Wall Street Sell-Off</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Newt Gingrich the projected winner in Georgia.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares the Virginia GOP Primary as 'Too Early to Call'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares the Vermont GOP Primary as 'Too Early to Call'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Down 15%. RT @JBoorstin: Pandora CEO tells me that $P is 2nd only to Google in terms of Mobile Ad Revenue. QUOTE: http://t.co/6qHe70yy $GOOG</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alert: Pandora Media plunges after quarterly results are worse than expected. Quote Here: http://t.co/RuujPr22 $P</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pandora Media: Q4 Revs $81M vs. $83M Est. | Q4 Loss Per Share $0.03 vs. Loss of $0.02 Est. QUOTE: http://t.co/6qHe70yy $P</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Update: Stocks log biggest drop in 2012. Story: http://t.co/fknyLrx8</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prior to today, Dow saw 45 straight days w/o a triple-digit decline. Dow's recent streak w/o a triple-digit decline was longest since 2006.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alert: Crude oil settles down $2.02 at $104.70/barrel.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. House voted in favor of legislation that restores govt's ability to levy billions of dollars in tariffs on imports from China &amp; others.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Senior Greek Finance Ministry Official tells @CNBC that PSI (Private Sector Involvement) deal will finish on time.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President @BarackObama says it's a question of when, not if, Syrian President will fall.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President @BarackObama: 'The world is unified. Iran is politically isolated. Iran situation can still be solved diplomatically.'</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama: Congress should pass Buffett Rule... We're cutting refinancing fees for FHA loans &amp; taking steps to help homeowners who are veterans.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President Obama holds new conference now, live on CNBC TV, on homeowners’ relief for veterans who might have been wrongly foreclosed &amp; more.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Update on #StanfordTrial: Jury finds Allen Stanford guilty of conspiracy and obstruction; not guilty of wire fraud. -Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Verdict in #StanfordTrial - Allen Stanford found guilty of conspiracy. Live coverage on CNBC TV and http://t.co/lvqIzbia.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Verdict in #StanfordTrial to be announced at 12:45PM ET. (via @ScottCohnCNBC) Tune into @CNBC for live coverage.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Dow falls more than 200 points in mid-day trading. STORY: http://t.co/fknyLrx8</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>European shares extended losses to close down, as worries over Greece &amp; global economic growth weighed on markets. SEE: http://t.co/XpaiCl3S</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gas prices not likely to hit $5 this summer: http://t.co/RqXaqTlF (Follow @sharon_epperson &amp; @pattidomm who are in Houston for #CERAWeek!)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jobs Friday is 4 days away. @CNBCSquawkSt's#Nailthenumber contest returns! Guess the jobs # &amp; win a @CNBC tote bag signed by the anchors.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Dow, S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq have biggest one-day drops in nearly 3 months. (Track here: http://t.co/phfCy7Kx)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch LIVE on @CNBC: Former Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill discusses the economy &amp; taxes with the @CNBCSquawkSt team.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Check: Stocks decline 1% amid ongoing Greece concerns. Dow on pace for 1st triple-digit loss of 2012. http://t.co/fknyLrx8</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Alleged members of hacking group @LulzSec arrested, charges to be announced later today.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks to Watch: Tuesday's early morning movers http://t.co/r0ltEFZj</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Midwest tornadoes caused an estimated $1B - $2B in insured losses according to Eqecat.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dick's Matches Estimates http://t.co/Qfq5b1rz</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Merck Q1 Below Estimates, Reaffirms Full Year  http://t.co/t5aU2lyg</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chesapeake, KKR Partnership Official http://t.co/BCHzkRNp</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Missed the premiere of #LuxuryBoom? Tune into @CNBC on March 11th at 8pET for the re-air. Info on doc here: http://t.co/4Qf8CaGt</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reporter @CourtReagan is live on @CNBC's Facebook page now to answer your questions on #LuxuryBoom. Ask away here: http://t.co/7yZUKewv</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dallas Fed's Fisher: Markets hooked on monetary morphine. (via @pattidomm) #ceraweek</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up at 9pET on @CNBC: The premiere of #LuxuryBoom! Don't miss the live  Facebook Q&amp;A with @CourtReagan @ 9:30pET: http://t.co/7yZUKewv</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>61% of luxury shoppers are newcomers that didn't spend a penny on luxury pre-recession. Who are they? CLIP: http://t.co/yWzC8u7s #LuxuryBoom</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stanford Jury says unable to reach unanimous verdict on all counts-Defense asks for &quot;Allen charge&quot; instructing jury to keep deliberating.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Skullcandy Announces Resignation of Mitch Edwards, CFO &amp; General Counsel - Stock Down 8% http://t.co/lWbFMSBu $SKUL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>- @AllState Joins Companies Pulling Ads On @RushLimbaugh Radio Show http://t.co/EedduWjN $ALL $CCO</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Founder of Ohio-based tech company says that Mark Zuckerberg stole their invention. STORY: http://t.co/ZgHoj3dP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Despite Apology, Advertisers Abandoning @RushLimbaugh http://t.co/G9H4omMd</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ALERT: Former NY Mets star Lenny Dykstra sentenced today to three years in state prison.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ALERT: Applied Materials ups dividend by 13% to $0.09 and announces $3B buyback. $AMAT</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>- @LifeLock to @CNBC: We do not agree w/Rush Limbaugh's recent comments-we are not making any changes to our advertising program</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wall Street Bonuses Seen Falling Nearly 25% For 2011 - NYC Budget Office</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fed's Fisher:Wall Street Has Preoccupation &quot;Bordering On Fetish&quot; For QE3-Trillions Already Lying Fallow, Not Being Employed In Real Economy</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>European shares extended losses to close down; traders citing concerns Greece might activate collective action clauses: http://t.co/KZDiHCzu</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NEWS ALERT: Picard case against @Mets owners Sterling Equities to proceed to trial. - Judge</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple makes attempt to quantify how many American jobs can be credited to the sale of its products: http://t.co/D1Khkshj</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Check: Major averages down for 3rd time in four sessions; Dow has biggest drop since Feb 15, S&amp;P has biggest drop since Feb. 10.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up on @CNBCSquawkSt 10:40a ET a David Faber exclusive with Gary Loveman, Caesars Entertainment Chairman, CEO &amp; President...</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Factory orders fell 1.0% in January, the biggest decline since October 2010.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ISM Nonmanufacturing Index 57.3 (February) vs. 56.8 (January)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@GreycroftVC's Alan Patricof says NYC is the &quot;hottest&quot; place in the country for entrepreneurs. Full interview: http://t.co/fsuFnI9d</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Open: Stocks lower amid reports showing slowdown in European private sector &amp; after China cut growth target. http://t.co/BFu1ZYh4</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IIF: Steering committee members to take part in Greek bond swap</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yahoo preparing &quot;massive restructuring,&quot; thousands could be laid off - @AllThingsD. Quote: http://t.co/dkhh0lzh</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>China cuts 2012 growth target. How will the U.S. markets react? http://t.co/vSiMaETG</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks to Watch: Monday morning's early movers http://t.co/KTKZQs7i</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join @CourtReagan tomorrow at 9pET, as she takes over CNBC's facebook page for a live Q&amp;A on the #luxuryboom premiere. http://t.co/mDK5hED6</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exit polls cited by state television: Vladimir Putin has won Russia's presidential election.  - AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Mitt Romney the projected winner in the Washington Caucuses</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can’t get enough @CNBC? Follow us on Tumblr-&amp;gt; http://t.co/WuI4cBCN</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What’s the most expensive luxury item you have bought recently? Tweet #luxuryboom for a chance to see your tweet on-air Monday at 9pET.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@heathernaut88 we use get glue for some primetime programs like @TheKudlowReport and docs. Thx for the recommendation.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New milestone for @CNBC. We hit 700k followers today thanks to all of our @twitter fans out there. Thanks for following!</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Apple announces 25 billion applications have been downloaded from the App Store as of late Friday.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Judge: BP, plaintiffs reach settlement in Gulf oil spill case - AP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Top #Ferrari clients own 5+ Ferraris! Watch CNBC's @CourtReagan Monday at 9pET, as she reveals the new big spenders! http://t.co/iyAA1pxt</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight at 8p ET on @CNBC... Donald Trump returns with “The Celebrity Apprentice”. http://t.co/DoZoKT1K #watchingcnbc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CBOE says it is the target of an SEC probe for the way it oversees its markets - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>(More) Moody's: Very high likelihood of Greek default.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can’t get enough @CNBC? Follow us on Tumblr-&amp;gt; http://t.co/WuI4cBCN</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Moody's downgrades Greece to &quot;C&quot; from &quot;Ca&quot;; Moody's has not assigned an outlook to the ratings.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ally Financial says Chief Technology and Operations Officer Cliff Skelton left company in January - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today was NYSE's lightest volume day of the year with roughly 3.2B shares changing hands. Avg. daily vol. in 2012 is 3.7B shares.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook IPO Getting More Underwriters; Deutsche Bank, Credit Suisse, Citigroup Likely Becoming Facebook Underwriters - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Citigroup's Belda &amp; Collins Also Plan to Leave Citigroup's Board - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Citigroup expected to elect Michael O'Neill to Chairman - WSJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>WSJ: Citigroup Chairman Parsons To Step Down.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polypore down 2.5% on report GM will halt Volt production for 5 weeks; Polypore makes components for lithion ion batteries used in hybrids.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Express CEO Chenault's 2011 total compensation up 17% to $24M.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GM to temporarily lay off 1,300 Volt workers for 5 weeks;.GM Volt production to be put on hold March 19-April 23 - Detroit Free Press</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Treasury agrees to pay Bank of America, JP Morgan $171M in withheld foreclosure-prevention incentives - DJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crude oil settles down $2.14 at $106.70/barrel.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Rapid Rise of @Pinterest Boosts Small Business Sales: http://t.co/QbdiUQEv</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wynn Resorts resumes trading after mistakenly filed 8K. Quote: http://t.co/2onB3Hyd</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Top luxury brands including @Burberry &amp; @LouisVuitton have been targeted in counterfeiting scheme, 26 people charged. http://t.co/PYKN9q7Q</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yelp CEO Jeremy Stoppelman on @CNBC: We think of ourselves as the @Amazon of local. $YELP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@Yelp CEO Jeremy Stoppelman: We're not worried about competition from Google. We're generating more word of mouth content than anyone.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sources To CNBC: AIG exits $500M stake in Blackstone Group. AIG sold stake in block trade pre-open. (via @kaylatausche)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>$YELP shares open at $22 after pricing above expectations at $15. Now trading at $24, up 63%. (via @BobPisani)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@Yelp opens for trading. Track the stock here: http://t.co/pUT6GZBC. $YELP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All of you waiting for @Yelp shares to trade, but sure to tune into @CNBC at 9:50aET for our interview w/ Yelp CEO Jeremy Stoppelman.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Marc Andreessen on @CNBC: Sarbanes-Oxley &quot;has almost killed the Tech IPO.&quot; Watch full interview here: http://t.co/vwlRJKzN @a16z</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks to Watch: Friday's early morning movers http://t.co/n3eT53gN</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alert: Justice Dept. uncovers alleged $325m counterfeit goods smuggling ring. Several dozen arrests have been made.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global Markets Update: European Markets Flat Ahead of U.S. Open  http://t.co/9qErQV7f #globalmarkets</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big Lots Beats Estimates http://t.co/agzt5cMp #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you #watchingcnbc? We want to know what you think of #WikiLeaks: Secrets and Lies? http://t.co/SflOk6Gb</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tomorrow, @Yelp CEO Jeremy Stoppelman will be on @CNBCSquawkSt at 9:50aET to discuss the company's IPO.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @kaylatausche: Source: Yelp $YELP prices at $15/share, a dollar above range. Adds 50K shares to the offer as well.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Leaked emails from @wikileaks shine rare light on Stratfor. Watch #WikiLeaks: Secrets and Lies tonight at 10pET. http://t.co/wygyc5mm</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Several investors have sued to block proposed IPO by owner of Empire State Building, saying it unfairly vales their interests - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Earnings Alert: Foot Locker (FL) Q4 EPS $0.55 vs. $0.51 Est.; Q4 Revs. $1.50B vs. $1.49B Est.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Diplomat: EU leaders agree to make Serbia a candidate for European Union membership - Reuters</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@Shutterfly up 9%, to buy Kodak Gallery online photo services business for $24m. Quote: http://t.co/MYmnsiSm</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>February auto sales rate 15.1m, highest level since February 2008 - Autodata</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Saudi Oil officials say report about pipeline attack untrue - DJ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crude oil jumps over $110 in electronic trading. The last time crude traded above $110? May 4th.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: Crude oil jumps over $110 in electronic trading. Crude oil surges on report of pipeline explosion in Saudi Arabia.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zynga has just announced the &quot;Zynga Platform,&quot; a new destination for people to play games. $ZNGA shares up 5%. http://t.co/KxgYfZY9</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Republican Presidential Candidate @RickSantorum: Manufacturing has tremendous impact on wealth of community; creates a ladder for success.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Republican Presidential Candidate @RickSantorum tells @CNBC: We have to compete against direct international competition.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why Greece hasn't defaulted on its debt - so far. http://t.co/c2fhUan9 by @MCaruso_Cabrera</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@GM sales conf. call: &quot;We are not revising 2012 sales forecast higher. We'll be at high end of our estimate.&quot; (via @Lebeaucarnews)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If you don't want to miss a single headline from Bernanke's Senate testimony, follow @CNBCSquawkST for live tweets.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nat gas prices plunge below $2.50 after EIA reports weekly storage withdrawal in range of estimates (down 82 BCF) (via @sharon_epperson)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch LIVE: Fed Chairman Ben Bernanke speaks before the Senate banking committee http://t.co/ZmdWKoog</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Construction spending dipped 0.1% in January, first drop in 6 months (via @AP)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ISM Manufacturing Index 52.4 (February) vs. 54.1 (January)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Publisher/Author Andrew Breitbart Dead At 43</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ford February U.S. sales up 14.4% slightly below estimate (up 18.2%). (via @Lebeaucarnews)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Econ Data Recap: New jobless claims steady, personal income rose about in line w/ expectations, spending gained 0.2%. http://t.co/e1HCmTev</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Apple stock hit $1,000? Steve Wozniak believes so. http://t.co/0vAQbEPf by @SullyCNBC#cnbcexclusive</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Walmart CEO Mike Duke: &quot;We have high expectations for fiscal year 2013...Our core Walmart U.S. business is back on track.&quot;</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wal-Mart increases annual dividend 9% to $1.59/share from $1.46. Quote: http://t.co/eZA01Knr</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Initial Jobless Claims (week ending 2/25) down 2,000 to 351,000</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wendy's Beats Estimates http://t.co/ynUMFeFy</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chain Store Sales: Limited Brands (LTD) February Comps. Up 8% vs. Up 6.2% est. http://t.co/5zAyXglE</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global Markets Update:  Europe Shares Rise After ECB Funding Results  http://t.co/SAsxqcf6 #globalmarkets</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Go @InsideFerrari FF with the President of #Ferrari North America Marco Mattiacci! http://t.co/oPgprEqT #luxuryboom</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>9pm ET tonight on @AmericanGreedTV on CNBC- See how Kenneth Starr’s fraud affords him the good life-until he’s caught: http://t.co/9uppAz2B</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tomorrow at 10pET on @CNBC. Watch @wikileaks: Secrets and Lies, as Julian Assange is interviewed. http://t.co/9DBHOqva #watchingcnbc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News Alert: Greek Parliament approves healthcare cuts, reforms.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Facebook has some new tools for businesses as it gets ready for an IPO. Story by @JBoorstin: http://t.co/iVH5Nc7B</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks closed in the red as Bernanke dashed hopes for further monetary stimulus; S&amp;P logs best Feb. since 1998. Story - http://t.co/spkk5iHA</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@GM to take 7% stake in Peugeot. PSA to issue shares worth 1 Billion Euros. (via @Lebeaucarnews)</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@GM &amp; Peugeot to share vehicle platforms &amp; components as part of alliance, to develop common platform w/ vehicle launch in 2016.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GM &amp; Peugeot have officially agreed to an alliance, target $2B in savings annually within 5 years.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>European market close: Stocks pared gains to close slightly down, tracking losses in the U.S. market. http://t.co/YNnngYHm</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bernanke: Subdued inflation to persist, despite temporary rise in gas prices.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bernanke: Critical fiscal &amp; financial challenges remain in Europe, global financial market strains pose significant downside risk to outlook</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch LIVE: Fed Chmn. Ben Bernanke testifies before House Financial Services Cmte. http://t.co/ZmdWKoog</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nasdaq goes above 3,000 for the first time since December 2000.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: February Chicago PMI 64.0 compared to 60.2 in January.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Market Open: Stock higher following a better-than-expected GDP report &amp; ECB injection http://t.co/spkk5iHA</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rupert Murdoch: James will continue to assume variety of &quot;essential corporate leadership mandates&quot; with focus on pay-TV &amp; intl. operations.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: James Murdoch resigns as Chairman of News International.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Q4 GDP Revised To + 3.0%</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fmr. Bear Stearns CEO Alan Schwartz is live on @SquawkCNBC for the next 2 hours in his 1st interview since Bear Stearns' collapse.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mortgage Applications Fall 0.3% For Week Of 2/24</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exclusive: Facebook co-founder Eduardo Saverin says Facebook is in the &quot;very early beginnings.&quot; http://t.co/otzmMyBQ #yposummit</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global Markets Update Europe Shares Rise After ECB Funding Results  http://t.co/SAsxqcf6 #globalmarkets</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Up next on @CNBC, @SullyCNBC interviews #Facebook co-founder Eduardo Saverin in a rare exclusive. #yposummit http://t.co/DJ36v7Rq</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joy Global Short of Estimates http://t.co/R8QcxVHY #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Staples Beats Estimates http://t.co/LlBnAK3H #earningscentral</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Global Markets Update: Markets Await Liquidity Measures http://t.co/yiyfMpNh #globalmarkets</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@InsideFerrari @MBUSA &amp; @BMWGroup all hit record highs in #luxury car sales. CNBC reveals this #luxuryboom http://t.co/iyAA1pxt</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News declares Mitt Romney as the projected winner in the Michigan GOP Primary.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you #watchingcnbc? What do you think of #60Minutes? Have you switched to #facebook's Timeline yet? http://t.co/MuvIDkzL</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up next on @CNBC... @60Minutes: The Billionaires. http://t.co/MuvIDkzL #60minutes</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBC News: Mitt Romney Is The Projected Winner In The Arizona GOP Primary- Michigan GOP Primary Too Close To Call</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight at 10p ET on @CNBC.  Watch @60Minutes as reporters speak with #facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg http://t.co/MuvIDkzL #watchingcnbc</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hewlett-Packard Plans Layoffs In WebOS Group-H-P To Lay Off About 275 Employees-   http://t.co/xwGtTus3 $HPQ</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Goldman Sachs Gets Wells Notice from SEC Related to Subprime Mortgage Deal $GS</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @CNBC2012: NBC News confirms Sen. Olympia Snowe (R-Maine) will not seek re-election.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nasdaq OMX gives CEO Bob Greifeld a 5-year contract extension; Greifeld to receive base salary of at least $1M.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @TheKudlowReport: 7p ET TONIGHT: Rep. @EricCantor talks to @larry_kudlow about taxes, jobs, and more! http://t.co/IKBUhvGP</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple's market cap hits $500B in after-hours trade, becomes the 6th stock ever to hit $500B.</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dow closes above 13,000 for the first time since May 2008 http://t.co/EjC5FBHI</text>
    <name>CNBC</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>