<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">
  <tweet>
    <text>Controversy is &quot;good for business, especially if your business is satire.” Doonesbury comic on Texas abortion law: http://t.co/ai3RQYSY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Unemployment down but still above 10% in four states: Calif (10.9%), Nev (12.7%), NC (10.2%), RI (10.9%) http://t.co/2K3qC2yE</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SEC alleges a group scored more than $1.8 mil in illicit profits on tips gleaned after an AA meeting http://t.co/RrhdQGnF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Singapore: manicured gardens, clean tap water, chewing gum-free streets, and the world’s “unhealthiest” country? http://t.co/2Er3Eup3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Fed takes no new actions and offers few hints about future programs to bolster the economic recovery.  http://t.co/J5lC5CI3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Australian mining billionaire says kids not fit to mange fortune, in their best interest &quot;to force them to go to work” http://t.co/cV5pLqiQ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is today the real Super Tuesday? The 119 delegates up for grabs may finally add clarity to the GOP race. http://t.co/7mnJFuw7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mild winter temps are triggering an early release of pollen from trees, leading to a longer, intense, allergy season http://t.co/xb1edylI</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UCLA anthropologists say American kids are more dependent and helpless than peers. Join a live chat at 12:30p ET http://t.co/eLu66YY2</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Time is running out to make a #MarchMadness Blindfold Bracket. Pick teams by stats, not bias. Win a WSJ dot drawing 
http://t.co/M2NOas6y</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Could you tell me what viral means?&quot; WSJ reporter’s mom reviews Grand Forks Olive Garden, sets social media abuzz http://t.co/8rC5AB3f</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is Pinterest the next Napster? Courts are far behind in copyright law in areas where the hot site could present issues. http://t.co/CFk1UEd3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How do US working parents' views of &quot;family time&quot; affect stress levels? A Q being studied for research on middle class
http://t.co/Bhrt433P</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Frmr News Corp exec Brooks and husband among 6 arrested by British police investigating journalists over phone hacking http://t.co/CDqPo3jp</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Over four days, Israel's &quot;Iron Dome&quot; missile defense system downed 23 militant rockets, saw 90% hit rate. http://t.co/G6FpdmWY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You know that Olive Garden reviewer? WSJer @JamesRHagerty on how his mom went viral. http://t.co/8rC5AB3f</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;The Hunger Games&quot; held its premiere in Los Angeles tonight. We have photos. http://t.co/1Ut5hFkz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bentley Motors counts the Queen of England and the Sultan of Brunei among its clientele. Up next: Soccer moms. http://t.co/r45iIxy3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A section of a new high-speed rail line in China has collapsed months before it's scheduled unveiling. http://t.co/6z8qlCU7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's time to fill out those NCAA brackets again - blindly. Our second annual Blindfold Brackets. http://t.co/M2NOas6y</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The iPhone 4S's Siri is “at best, a work-in-progress” says a false-advertising lawsuit filed against Apple. http://t.co/8tb43klu</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CNN is in discussions about a possible acquisition of online social-news aggregator Mashable. http://t.co/miZs4H5O</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fixing the link. Here's the handy rundown of the remaining GOP candidates on key campaign issues: http://t.co/JgkhSbIN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A handy rundown of the remaining GOP candidates on key campaign issues:
http://t.co/CIt3xISL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A $2,555-a-month infant education program? Ten NYC children - still in utero - are signed up http://t.co/Au0LQ2qe</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google and Facebook to stand trial in India for charges that they failed to censor objectionable content http://t.co/E7oG4Uuc (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mark your calendars for May 5. A &quot;super moon&quot; 14% larger, 30% brighter than normal full moons will be in the sky. http://t.co/85J8usYI</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Time is running out to use up any money from 2011 in your FSA. Get that new pair of glasses. Stock up on Band-Aids. http://t.co/VxpYd4bq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are creative types born or bred? Join a live chat at 1 p.m. today with WSJ's @jonahlehrer. Ask your Qs now. http://t.co/c7Szc6tF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks are riskier than you think. Here’s why: http://t.co/Zwd3ToPu</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are you the creative type? It doesn’t matter, writes @jonahlehrer. Why anyone can innovate: http://t.co/Mxe0xZhO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How to win your own WSJ dot drawing: Create a #MarchMadness Blindfold Bracket. Pick teams using stats, not bias http://t.co/M2NOas6y</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Taliban vowed revenge after US soldier allegedly killed 16 civilians in Afghanistan, torched bodies http://t.co/TnXWbcqe (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Student loan debt has surged to $867 bil — more than credit card debt or car loans. Borrowers not paying down balances
http://t.co/B2v0waVN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A U.S. soldier opened fire on Afghan villagers Sunday, killing 16 people http://t.co/XTtwyF2P</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Mitt Romney wins the delegate vote at Republican county conventions in Wyoming, the Associated Press repor... http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video: WSJ's White House correspondent @laurameckler on what it's like to cover an Obama road show. http://t.co/Xn7A7vfp</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What are you giving up when you check the donor box on your license?  http://t.co/ka5cjSLq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Winners and losers from this week in business and M&amp;A. http://t.co/mPMDOhWt @WSJDealJournal</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More #March11 coverage from Japan Real Time: http://t.co/cgdHUoV0</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A look at Sendai, Japan one year after an earthquake and tsunami tore through the city.  http://t.co/2scAk3hK #march11</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Despite the attention, Ugandans are criticizing the #Kony2012 movement. http://t.co/6eeLzoQG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney’s electoral “footprint” in some primary states resembles that of Obama's in 2008. What that means: http://t.co/8WqLBalO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The #Kony2012 video about the alleged atrocities of the rebel leader has been criticized by a cross section of Ugandans http://t.co/6eeLzoQG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney's electoral &quot;footprint&quot; in some states bears a striking resemblance to that of  Obama in 2008. http://t.co/p6EIyhap</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Could our feelings towards words be shaped by how they are typed? The QWERTY effect: http://t.co/TN0aF7Do</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live Chat: Discuss the impact of #Kony2012 with @emilysteel and WSJ intl editor Eduardo Kaplan. Ask your Q's now. http://t.co/3EZt1fi9</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check out before-and-after photos of areas affected by the devastating March 2011 earthquake and tsunami in Japan. http://t.co/ujlG9Juk</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apparently, the sky isn’t the limit for Angry Birds. The cult bird-throwing game is headed for space. http://t.co/Y4cQBMxR</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming next month: the first appearance of the &quot;Transition&quot; flying car http://t.co/VyrE3ZRR</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sunday marks one year since the tsunami in Japan. See updates on the stories we've been following http://t.co/RXTHiVtY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Still waiting for a tax refund? You're not alone. IRS efforts to combat ID theft = delayed tax refunds. http://t.co/4xsoSG1j</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>German painter Gerhard Richter last year outsold Monet, Giacometti &amp; Rothko - combined. A case-study of his rise: http://t.co/geF7wnBs</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In the middle of scruffy Detroit, construction will start on a swank Whole Foods. Calculations of the biz decision: http://t.co/gyNvYvf0</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After he was caught, an influential computer hacker &quot;literally worked around the clock&quot; to help federal agents http://t.co/3ZoivG6J</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yawn! See a slideshow of China's sleepy delegates dozing off during a National People's Congress meeting http://t.co/Jmx15zij</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The average U.S. home insurance premium cracked $1,000 for the first time ever:
http://t.co/EiNPppJ3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video about fugitive rebel leader #Kony has generated 70+ mil views, the fastest growing viral campaign in history http://t.co/SvU4OooP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: The U.S. economy added 227,000 jobs in February. The unemployment rate held at 8.3%.  http://t.co/ot6WKPKd</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Greece says 85.8% of private investors holding the country's bonds are participating in Friday's deal. Bon... http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Japan's Nikkei Stock Average broke through the 10000 mark for the first time since Aug. 1.  http://t.co/2rl746MV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations, iPhone 4S owners. If you use AT&amp;T, 3G is now called 4G. http://t.co/y7Lb5Q2u</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Do you know who Joseph Kony is? More on the viral video that has generated 40m+ views since appearing on YouTube.  http://t.co/SvU4OooP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>IRS efforts to combat tax cheats is showing a side effect: delayed tax refunds for many legitimate filers. http://t.co/1cyLQv8D</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Vote and comment for possible inclusion in an upcoming Big Issues special report: Should the SBA be abolished? http://t.co/JAGykY53</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Instagram close to new funding that will value the service at up to $500m or 20x its value one year ago. http://t.co/tFjZ42K7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S., Jordan developing plans to secure what is believed to be Syria's stockpile of chemical weapons. http://t.co/jibnquDI (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The #Kony 2012 video has @rihanna, @alecbaldwin, @justinbieber &amp; the White House talking. How it caught fire: http://t.co/tkEyT2rs</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@Alta_LMSW Not at all. Just a daily Journal tradition: The A-Hed. http://t.co/hce6KAvK</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@BradFollmer Not at all. Just a daily Journal tradition: The A-Hed. http://t.co/hce6KAvK</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The cost of living for single retirees' is 40-50% higher than that of married couples. Tips on retiring single: http://t.co/dUxMZU0k</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With no radical changes in the “new iPad”, @srussolill wonders: Will investors demand more from Apple? http://t.co/uyPR0GfC</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In New Zealand, 600 sheep shearers from 26 nations competed for the title of world's best shearer. http://t.co/AKdLy4Jc</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Russia, w 12 million immigrants, is the 2nd-most-popular destination for immigrants, followed by Germany. http://t.co/MiB25vRr</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See photos of the massive solar storm that reached Earth at about 6 a.m. ET today http://t.co/7EMHQl8D</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Organized religions have a level of discipline and managerial genius that any CEO should envy, writes @alaindebotton http://t.co/wSPoH3Xr</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The states with the largest number of residents with a net worth of $2 mil or more: California, New York, Florida http://t.co/wl14DGvI</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Greek government official says 75% of private-sector investors have agreed to the debt restructuring. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney campaign had $7.3 mil in cash on hand after raising $11.5 million in Feb.  83% of donations for $250 or less http://t.co/NSu6apP9</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The next generation of McDonald's franchisees grew up in an era of &quot;Super Size Me.&quot; The impact: http://t.co/w4Cc1Vee (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In a matchup against Obama, Ron Paul trailed by 8% points in a recent poll, a better showing than Santorum or Gingrich http://t.co/dYkVN7pq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Largest solar storm in 5 years due to arrive on Earth today, could disrupt utility grids, flights, satellites, GPS http://t.co/TT2UL98h</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UN report cites &quot;alarming increase&quot; in executions in Iran, from fewer than 100 people in 2003 to more than 650 in 2011 http://t.co/Nw2dlko3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Citi's new hire: Watson, the IBM supercomputer of Jeopardy fame. Is this the end of human employment at banks? http://t.co/BWbyvFih</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Justice Department threatens lawsuits against Apple and 5 major publishers, alleging collusion over e-book pricing http://t.co/cHYqueel</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: European Central Bank leaves its key interest rate unchanged. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Bank of England leaves its key interest rate and quantitative-easing policy unchanged. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Switching off electronic devices is the No. 1 spark for unruly behavior on airlines, flight attendants say. http://t.co/u39Fl5gh</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New NPR and Netflix deals, an expanding digital-books service: Is TED, the conference, becoming TED, the media company? http://t.co/T1UWMpTw</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why is the new iPad called &quot;the new iPad&quot;? &quot;We don't want to be predictable,&quot; says Apple. http://t.co/jGhAzjIS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A 20-hour phone call? @waltmossberg tests out Motorola's Droid Razr Maxx. http://t.co/AFud1wIQ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pfizer rebuffs Novartis $17B bid for its animal-health unit. http://t.co/tVcNhL6X (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>DJIA, S&amp;P, NASDAQ all up as Fed data shows U.S. consumers increased their debt by $17.8B. http://t.co/bC8pOxj3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alabama may not be friendly territory for Mitt Romney, but at least the former governor is behind him. http://t.co/5xYFZjLz #2012</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What our Twitter followers are saying about the new iPad: http://t.co/iXvsaphJ (Thanks for all of your responses!)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Biggest solar storm in 5 years racing toward Earth, threatening to disrupt power grids, GPS, airplane flights http://t.co/jtYkeBbE</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do you think about Apple's new #iPad? Will you buy it? Reply w tag #wsj. We'll feature on http://t.co/JjUEpV9O http://t.co/0eYWzrGn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple's new #iPad: sharper display, 4G capability, 5 megapixel camera. Starts at $499. Available March 16. http://t.co/PSw7DlQU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AmEx cardholders will be able to sign up for deals via Twitter from merchants including Best Buy, Whole Foods, Amazon. http://t.co/7vbiiO3Z</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple's iPad event is minutes away. For live streaming coverage, visit: http://t.co/0eYWzrGn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama has netted about $137 mil for his campaign, more than the combined fund-raising of the 4 major GOP candidates.
http://t.co/J5ezI1yS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: The Indianapolis Colts announced the end of quarterback Peyton Manning's career with the club. Live coverage: http://t.co/p0MMCeLY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Colts are set to release Peyton Manning from his contract. Live video of the press conference: http://t.co/p0MMCeLY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple is expected to unveil its latest iPad at 1 pm ET. Tune into our live streaming coverage: http://on.wsj.com/xrFWmj</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Women are tilting more Democratic, men more Republican. The trend is growing in strength. The impact is profound http://t.co/ZJ0DoFCX</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Democratic registration in 8 battleground states fell 5.5% since 2008 election compared to a 1.9% drop for GOP
http://t.co/J5ezI1yS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>World powers accepted Iran’s offer to restart nuclear negotiations. Congress is preparing a new round of sanctions http://t.co/IH6VuLAl</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The alleged informant in the FBI’s computer hacking investigation is a 28-yr-old who lived in a NYC housing project http://t.co/qoYyElDC</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple’s new iPad could be a boon for Verizon Wireless because it will support a new wireless broadband technology http://t.co/NIRzq8z4</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exit polls from Ohio show GOP voters are tepid on candidates. 4 in 10 voters had doubts about their primary pick http://t.co/bB77amM7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Private-sector companies added 216,000 jobs in the U.S. in February, according to ADP.  http://t.co/X7T7IhYZ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney eked out a win in Ohio extending his delegate lead, but a swift end is unlikely in the Republican race. http://t.co/bB77amM7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Romney wins Republican presidential primary in Ohio. http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>North Dakota goes for Santorum despite heavy campaign push from Paul. Full coverage: http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Colts’ QB Peyton Manning will be released by his team says a report. What might his future hold? http://t.co/9xxU2CUI via @WSJSports</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santorum wins GOP presidential primary in Oklahoma, the AP reports.
http://t.co/bB77amM7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#SuperTuesday is turning out to be a nail biter. Have Qs for our political team? Use the tag #wsjlive http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Santorum wins GOP primary in Tennessee http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney wins Republican presidential primary in Massachusetts. Fox calls Oklahoma for Santorum. Full coverage: http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Va. Gov. McDonnell, Frmr NYSE CEO Grasso, RNC Chair Priebus to appear on our live coverage. Have Qs? Ask w tag #wsjlive http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Romney wins Vermont Republican primary, AP reports.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Have #SuperTuesday Qs for our political team? Ask here, using the tag #wsjlive, and we'll answer some on air. http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google has consolidated its online bookstore, music service and software apps into a single site called “Play.” http://t.co/Lt6mgrYV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney wins Virginia primary. #SuperTuesday coverage:  http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Newt Gingrich wins Georgia Republican primary, the AP reports. http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Super Tuesday: Romney may emerge transformed from front-runner into presumptive leader after today. http://t.co/bB77amM7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“@wconnors: An oil rig fire in Nigeria raged for 46 days before Chevron extinguished it. Few noticed. http://t.co/JD9XEqoB” (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Since skiing came to Afghanistan, it has been pretty much all downhill. http://t.co/L0XEvgMP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A study shows that in the first year of the current “recovery”, the 1% captured 93% of income growth. http://t.co/wbiKOKgG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>US charged 6 people described as important members of the computer-hacking groups Anonymous and LulzSec. See court docs http://t.co/IRrfe9Wy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Old get richer, young poorer. Net worth of older households up 42% from 1984 to 2009. For younger households, down 68% http://t.co/IulNfxHz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GOP voters used words such as &quot;disillusioned&quot; and &quot;frustrated&quot; to describe the nominating process. #supertuesday http://t.co/eSfZX6T6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Average hourly wage for male college graduates 23 to 29 down 11% in past decade to $21.68 in 2011. http://t.co/YabcDehK (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama to Romney: &quot;Good luck tonight. Really.&quot; http://t.co/I4eUI9iz #SuperTuesday</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>When nude pics of famous ppl hit the Internet, ppl who talk &amp; tweet about it fall into two camps. Which side are u on? http://t.co/KeDPh1KK</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama: Unilateral action against Syria would be a mistake. Watch live: http://t.co/TnSHjuWy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live Video: Obama is holding his first press conference of 2012. http://t.co/TnSHjuWy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dow now down more than 200 points, at 12754. http://t.co/apyJ4Op3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Jury convicts Texas financier Allen Stanford on 13 of 14 charges in $7 billion Ponzi scheme, according to AP.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. charges six w computer hacking, the latest development in a global crackdown on high-profile computer attacks
http://t.co/qoYyElDC</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video games can change your brain, boosting creativity, vision, decision-making. Ask Qs in a live chat today at 1p ET http://t.co/V5ozsaUy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The average bonus in NY’s financial industry this year was slashed 14%. Wall Street profits fell more than 50% in 2011 http://t.co/JBa9Krtq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An AK jury found a man guilty of murder, but the conviction was thrown out. A juror had been tweeting during the trial. http://t.co/xSEfG8b4</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A $30 bag of raw popcorn could be worth $3K to movie theaters. Class action filed against AMC over concession prices http://t.co/S5JGrDN8</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ever tackled your own car repair? How did it turn out? @gwendolynbounds will include some of your response during Lunch Break at noon</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Videogames change your brain, often for the better. Gamers are faster decision makers, better multitaskers http://t.co/R7HRj7l5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What should pro-active spouses do when their partners won't seek help? Live chat today at 11a ET w/ @EBernsteinWSJ http://t.co/iozh7cTz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Couples therapy for one. Some spouses are going alone to couples counseling to fix their marriages. http://t.co/KceweAQ7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The period between Apple product launches and their actual sale has seen an average gain in the stock of 4.53% http://t.co/WTlXRzWO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Steve Jobs’s widow, the Palm Pilot inventor and other tech titans are funding efforts to help undocumented students http://t.co/vkr3KERq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>For up-to-the minute coverage from the campaign trail, follow our list of political reporters: http://t.co/SJLWkW6O</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's Super Tuesday, and some 437 delegates are at stake. See our live streaming coverage all day: http://t.co/rvENFvf6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>North America has become China's top region for oil and gas deals investing $17B since 2010. http://t.co/fnUZlkJd</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The DJIA is having its best start to a year since 1998. So why are things so quiet on the IPO and M&amp;A front? http://t.co/T9sQBxq5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tech titans are funding efforts to help undocumented youths attend college, find jobs, stay in the country. http://t.co/BdWQTbNb</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The owners of the NY Mets were ordered to return as much as $83 mil they withdrew from Madoff's firm http://t.co/WlfB72W9</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Remember http://t.co/M0tkni3m? A new litter of Web pet supply stores is emerging, and the economics have changed http://t.co/pggDDIML</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Unfriending&quot; is increasing on Facebook. FB friendship break-ups leapt from 56% in 2009 to 63% in 2011. http://t.co/OfSPP1KF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As stocks have become more volatile, does the 4% rule for retirement withdrawals still hold up? http://t.co/K1qqqNTZ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Forget http://t.co/M0tkni3m. A new crop of Web-only pet stores aims to prove that the pet category can work online. http://t.co/US5HPBeq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A lawsuit over a $1,000 1-bedroom apartment (cheap for NYC!) could upend the city’s powerful rent regulations: http://t.co/ukup4xcH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tech stocks slip led by a drop in shares of social-game developer Zynga following a J.P. Morgan downgrade. http://t.co/PrVYeqRS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Phone-line problems continue for United Airlines after the switch to Continental Airlines' reservation system http://t.co/KDipWSsH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Baby boomers have a big problem when it comes to retirement investment returns: the sheer number of other boomers http://t.co/lx45L4Do</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney is up, Santorum is down. That’s the takeaway from the latest state polls on the eve of #SuperTuesday. http://t.co/UBwHVNp8</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Opposition rallied in central Moscow, a day after Putin returned to the presidency amid reports of vote fraud. http://t.co/dmKv8S5P</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Could job gains stick this time? 82 of the 100 biggest metro areas saw year-over-year job growth through Dec. http://t.co/FkKIcBPE</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The question for newspapers: are paywalls too little, too late after years of subscriber and advertising erosion? http://t.co/yNZLZMIa</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama to grab some of Super Tuesday spotlight from GOP rivals by holding first news conference of 2012 on Tuesday http://t.co/Et9YMejk</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The divorce rate for people ages 50+ has doubled in the past two decades. What are the risk factors?
http://t.co/De3WqqUL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After the NFL accuses the Saints of paying to injure players, news of similar behavior on other teams surfaces http://t.co/bWurPNrF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“@MtthwRose:Not since 1996 has party's likely nominee been viewed negatively by plurality of Americans: http://t.co/5eldJWDo” (subscription)</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tour an Eva Airways plane transformed into a Hello Kitty Jet. Themed head rests, fish cakes, soaps and more. http://t.co/v8OMXQsd</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Potential criminal environmental penalties against BP could reach $17 bil to $40 bil.
http://t.co/nFUyrCuq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GOP tries to move past Limbaugh furor, sparked after he said law student a &quot;slut&quot; for views on contraception coverage http://t.co/niZtak6t</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Russia's opposition is preparing for a mass rally in Moscow tonight after Putin claims a disputed victory http://t.co/AaRdUE35</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In one small Indiana town, residents weren’t asking how to rebuild after the tornado, but whether to try at all. http://t.co/NjUNcX5g</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live: China's last big political event before the 2012 leadership transition starts today http://t.co/4mjLzAfG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Vladimir Putin appeared on track to win Russia's presidential election, according to exit polls and ea... http://t.co/pXEdgVlQ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A fake tweet briefly stirred diplomatic drama between the U.S. and #Russia as Russians vote in presidential election http://t.co/53nrez2A</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Romney wins Washington state caucuses. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@evan_p Glad you liked it.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There were some 20 &quot;books of revelation&quot;. So why did St. John the Divine's version make it into the Bible? http://t.co/ejfuQTI0</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Authorities reporting at least 14 deaths in southern Indiana, 12 in Kentucky, one in Ohio. Storm coverage: http://t.co/CM8R78FG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking:  BP and Gulf Coast spill plaintiffs agree to settlement.  http://t.co/4lk5uUfF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In 1990, 1 in 10 of all divorces were by people ages 50+. By 2009, they accounted for 1 in 4. http://t.co/De3WqqUL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wal-Mart, Target and other retailers are uniting to develop a mobile-payments system that makes plastic obsolete. http://t.co/ctvvuwCE</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video: Watch footage of the tornado damage in Madison and New Market, Alabama. http://t.co/mlx7idSU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Death toll of storms in southern Indiana and northern Kentucky now at six. http://t.co/CM8R78FG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Map: Stretching from the Gulf Coast to the Great Lakes, the reported tornado strikes since Tuesday. http://t.co/vPAh4TR3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New Orleans Saints players allegedly paid for injuring opposing players. Payoffs for &quot;knockouts&quot; &amp; &quot;cart-offs&quot;. http://t.co/J5KxD91B</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yelp soared in its debut, finishing at $24.58 or 64% higher than its $15 IPO price. How other web IPOs have fared: http://t.co/keEo4QuT</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An estimated $715.3B in negative equity, or &quot;underwaterness&quot;, ails the housing market. http://t.co/N2g4uiBN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From learning how to drive to first dates, here are some of your Datsun memories: http://t.co/sljQapAC To share more, use the tag #wsj</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Powerful storms stretching from the Gulf Coast to the Great Lakes flattened buildings in several states http://t.co/CM8R78FG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Citigroup is expected to name Michael O'Neill chairman.  http://t.co/WhbiDXoV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tax breaks in Romney’s latest plan would cut government revenues by at least $3.4 trillion in the coming decade http://t.co/WpNltZEg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The latest from the Rutgers spying trial: Tyler Clementi's dorm-room date noticed the webcam pointed at the bed. http://t.co/yst9H5Ax</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>MLB is getting another round of playoffs with new 10-team tournament. http://t.co/KZ9AumCn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Addendum to our retweet: More than 1 in 5 in Washington DC are on food stamps. http://t.co/mbqYzyGH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Scorsese and Spielberg have one. Top-of-the-line screening rooms worth up to $2m are becoming a Hollywood fixture. http://t.co/mxsGlsiM</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Send your favorite Datsun memories, pictures and videos to us, using the tag #wsj. We'll share your stories on http://t.co/JjUEpV9O.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nissan is considering reviving its iconic Datsun brand. What's your favorite Datsun memory? http://t.co/przRt3QG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Instead of buying airtime on TV or radio, an outside political group to spend $5m campaigning on FB, Twitter. http://t.co/kc7JfptT</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A group of NYC mothers are donating their breast milk to twins whose mother died hours after their birth http://t.co/tjp3JYLe</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The stock market is surging, but individual investors have pulled $8.3 bil out of U.S. stock funds so far this year. http://t.co/nDAfXfw1</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>1st-class mail volume has fallen 25% since 2006. The Postal Service predicts annual losses exceeding $18 bil by 2015 http://t.co/kOJulBBn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is kissing illegal in India? Indians might not find out till Dec. 11, 2013. http://t.co/8JqJZytm</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama on Iran: “as president of the United States, I don’t bluff.” http://t.co/j84kBZg3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Yelp shares rise 67% at $25.11 in debut.  http://t.co/vPeAePDA</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AT&amp;T pulled the plug on its unlimited data plan. One way to avoid the throttle: Use Wi-Fi. For other tips: http://t.co/joqDpIDA</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Splunk, Workday and ServiceNow: part of the new wave of start-up getting ready to hit the stock market. http://t.co/UB4ijAAu</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Video: Take a tour of the futuristic R&amp;D lab behind Apple's Siri http://t.co/cNxLnZrH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. stocks may be surging, but investors have pulled $8.3B out of stock funds in 2012 and $10.6B into bond funds. http://t.co/nDAfXfw1</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Photos: Instagram portraits of the #Yankees. http://t.co/1hkHKy3V</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. household income not &quot;headed in the right direction.&quot; Declined by 1.3% from $50,673 in Dec to $50,020 in Jan. http://t.co/4cHEZrOZ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Massachusetts moderate baloney.&quot; &quot;Pennsylvania big labor baloney.&quot; Why Gingrich said &quot;baloney&quot; 11 times in Atlanta. http://t.co/dDwq2sbg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Groupon/LinkedIn/Zynga/Yelp/Facebook. Now another class of Internet IPOs is getting ready to hit the stock market. http://t.co/UB4ijAAu</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What does AT&amp;T's new data-plan policy mean for customers? We've put together a Q&amp;A. http://t.co/zdeLoYgG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AT&amp;T is effectively ending unlimited data plans. What that means for customers and how to avoid getting throttled: http://t.co/zdeLoYgG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AT&amp;T is effectively ending unlimited data plans, penalizing customers who use more than a set amount of data per month http://t.co/joqDpIDA</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Turning point for the active ETF market.&quot; Bill Gross' new active fund debuts, down slightly. http://t.co/wgVVESeT $TRXT</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A federal judge in Montana apologizes for forwarding an email with a racist joke directed at President Obama. http://t.co/T5XgkIa6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The standard 25,000-mile domestic frequent-flier ticket is going the way of the in-flight meal. http://t.co/dDc1FzXq @middleseat</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>50% of adults used a sick day or vacation day to wait at home for a service or delivery. 25% lost wages while waiting. http://t.co/Wg4zRrVb</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: The Senate has defeated an attempt by Republicans to overturn Obama's policy on contraceptive health coverage</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A debate over paid sick leave intensifies. Should small biz be required to provide all employees w paid sick days? http://t.co/qe5IMgfW</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Obama: “I knew about Jeremy before you did, or everybody else did…I’ve been on the Jeremy Lin bandwagon for a while.” http://t.co/HXp2F9YV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do biz schools look for in applicants? What mistakes should you avoid? Join a live chat at 1 p.m. ET. Ask Qs now. http://t.co/fd7BixHO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Curious to hear Bob Costas talk yoga? @jasonWSJ writes about the growing push to make yoga an Olympic event http://t.co/dS2YdMy5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fannie Mae lost $16.9 billion during 2011. Each American household’s share of Fannie, Freddie Losses: $1,300. http://t.co/hhcVRs6c</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An executive at a Connecticut brokerage firm says that his $350,000 salary just isn’t enough. “I feel stuck.” http://t.co/Tu68nHwM</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Violent Midwest storms killed at least 12. As many as 300 homes in Harrisburg, Ill. were damaged or destroyed. http://t.co/y5BpsORi</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Conservative media publisher and activist Andrew Breitbart has died at the age of 43. http://t.co/TKoru0lQ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Only 12% of applicants made it into Harvard Business School last year. Meet the woman who reads the applications: http://t.co/qSEJWdQt</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bank of America working on changes that would require checking account users to pay monthly fee unless they bank online http://t.co/VQ6uaF6w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Jobless claims fell by 2,000 to 351,000 in latest week.  http://t.co/VDGEFFYH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Personal incomes rose 0.3% in January, while spending rose 0.2%.  http://t.co/VDGEFFYH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Greek credit-default swaps won't be triggered as no credit event has occurred, International Swaps and Der... http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: The euro-zone unemployment rate hit 10.7% in January, the highest since the euro was established in 1999. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rick Santorum's 'Google Bomb' problem has gone away. Here's how: http://t.co/1LjI0IwN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With folding wings and propeller, @Terrafugia flying-car to debut at NY Auto Show in April. http://t.co/KOzyy8qP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our WSJ Live app, featuring live video coverage, now is available on your iPhone. http://t.co/fyW9f5KR</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>See &quot;secret&quot; documents from Vatican archives that now are on public display. http://t.co/0i8OmCks</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;The consumer point-and-shoot camera has just been reinvented.&quot; @WaltMossberg #lytro http://t.co/xkn4HE6k</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nasdaq rose 5.4% in February, DJIA saw its fifth straight monthly gain. What will March bring? http://t.co/DPWTESID @marketwatch</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#USMNT ends 82-year-old curse of the Azzurri, beating Italy 1-0. @mattfutterman @wsjsports http://t.co/S6bOwDHB</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Deadly storms struck the Midwest, leaving at least 9 people dead in Illinois and Missouri. Photos: http://t.co/OWQ5ZA3c</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stocks tumble 53 pts after a cautious outlook on U.S. recovery by Fed Chairman Bernanke. The markets recap: http://t.co/Ycqeye7v</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google is expanding in NYC. The company now has 2,750 employees in the city, a 38% increase from 2010. http://t.co/7X1An5q7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How can moms forge close ties with their sons without emasculating them? Join a live chat at 2 p.m. ET. Ask Qs now. http://t.co/qWQGB1hd</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With 437 delegates at stake, we look at Romney's prospects on Super Tuesday http://t.co/btVksTro</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Student loan debt hits home for Bernanke. His son, who is in med school, to rack up $400K of student loan debt http://t.co/nXQfq3Mp</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple's market cap shot above $500 bil, making it the 6th company ever w a market cap above the half-trillion mark http://t.co/88c5mIR8</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Jordan put his Chicago-area home on the market for $29 mil. Details: 56K sq ft, 9 bedrooms, 5 fireplaces. http://t.co/ymvCLpth</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Older drivers are becoming safer, with fatal car-crash rates declining steeply for drivers 75 and older http://t.co/8stvYmxL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What’s the longest you’ve waited for a cable repairman? @gwendolynbounds will feature some of your responses during Lunch Break at noon.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You can charge your iPhone with just water. Watch how it works: http://t.co/0pcJS5xJ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The unemployment rate for people w disabilities was 12.9% in Jan, compared w a 8.7% for people w/o disabilities http://t.co/cdwhsw5h</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tiger Woods once considered dropping out of golf and becoming a Navy SEAL, a former instructor claims http://t.co/6tbwL41a</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Nasdaq Composite tops 3000 for the first time since December 2000.  http://t.co/w8Qgm1xq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Nasdaq Composite tops 3000 http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: The U.S. said North Korea has agreed to a moratorium on nuclear and missile tests. http://t.co/nnhvE26f</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BREAKING: News Corp. says James Murdoch steps down as executive chairman of News International. http://t.co/JjUEpV9O.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Of the 9 states that have held GOP nominating contests, 5 saw lower turnout than in 2008. http://t.co/vS2UktJN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Leap Day! Statistically, a baby has a 1 in 1,461 chance of being born on a Leap Day. http://t.co/lmdSCZhc</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ECB allots 529.53 billion euros to European banks in three-year refinancing operation, ahead of forecasts. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More on Romney's wins in Arizona and Michigan: http://t.co/vMOIbYSV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Mitt Romney wins Michigan Republican presidential primary, AP reports. Continuing coverage: http://t.co/jSme7hRD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With a quarter of precincts reporting in Michigan: Romney 41.1%, Santorum 38.0%, Paul 11.6%, Gingrich 6.6%. http://t.co/jSme7hRD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney wins Arizona Republican primary. Michigan still tightly contested. The latest: http://t.co/jSme7hRD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@RonBonjean We're glad to have you on.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Results from MI starting to roll in. With only 2% of precincts reporting: 41.4% Santorum, 37.6% Romney. http://t.co/qVlKUSmV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polls now closing in Michigan. Live coverage of the primaries: http://t.co/jSme7hRD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Polls will soon close in Michigan and Arizona. The latest on the Republican primaries: http://t.co/Ccd0iiZv</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Graph: DJIA closes above 13000 for first time since May 19, 2008. http://t.co/d7yCB4Mz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Republican U.S. Sen. Olympia Snowe of Maine says she won't seek re-election.  http://t.co/25mEIRYy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Dow industrials close above 13000 for the first time since May 2008.  http://t.co/vh1tV4SM</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Dow is flirting with 13000 again. The index up 24.82 points, or 0.19%, at 13005 in mid-afternoon trading. http://t.co/FyfokP1e</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Some 9/11 remains sent to a landfill says Pentagon report. http://t.co/Iq0PfN8d</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Voting continues in GOP primaries in MI and AZ. Photos: http://t.co/cvSrpuhk. Live video coverage tonight @WSJ starting 8 p.m. ET.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FDA warns of diabetes-risk in cholesterol-fighting drugs called statins. http://t.co/UvmFvwkq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: A third student died Tuesday following a shooting at a suburban-Cleveland high school a day earlier.  http://t.co/r3252R2B</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ben &amp; Jerry's, former Nirvana manager and other biz leaders to pour funds into the Occupy Wall Street movement http://t.co/TvTjpKz7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join the @WSJ's @LizRappaport for a live chat at 1 p.m. ET today on kids and allergies. Ask your questions now. http://t.co/jCcTJFyl</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>6 mil school-age kids in U.S., or 1/13, have serious food allergies. Researchers unable to explain the increase http://t.co/SQ1Go9xl</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple invited reporters to a media event expected to mark the unveiling of its latest iPad, next Wednesday in San Fran http://t.co/9cTj9P4g</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Feds are building insider-trading cases against roughly 120 individuals on and off Wall Street http://t.co/0HY6rDSe</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>When parents are stressed out, even their kids' DNA is affected. http://t.co/4hmKXcf5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>People with low levels of Omega-3s had smaller brains and scored lower on memory tests. http://t.co/uBvp5exW</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A mix between &quot;The Sopranos&quot; and &quot;The Muppet Show,&quot; puppets are covering one of the biggest corruption trials in Ohio http://t.co/IL1Wv4d3</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Smaller cities offer sports teams millions for stadium deals despite evidence that the investments rarely pay off http://t.co/jQ4HBA1y</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;(Wall Street bankers) harmed the US, and now they want to harm China.” -protestor interrupting World Bank's Zoellick http://t.co/Un9vP7TF</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Investors wanting to get in early on Facebook have sparked a 24% surge in its share price on the &quot;secondary market&quot; http://t.co/COHOlce7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Users spent an avg of 3 mins on Google+ in Jan. Compare that to 89 mins on tumblr and Pinterest, 405 on Facebook. http://t.co/I8PyCxvk</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: U.S. home prices fell 4% in the fourth quarter from a year earlier, according to S&amp;P Case-Shiller.  http://t.co/QmqUO5Ga</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: French carmaker Peugeot Citroën plans to raise roughly $1.34 billion in connection with an auto-making all... http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Durable-goods orders dropped 4% in January, falling at the fastest pace in three years.  http://t.co/WF54ENjc</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exclusive: A first listen of new @Springsteen track “You’ve Got It” from his upcoming album “Wrecking Ball”. http://t.co/TIJrL1eD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A first listen of new @Springsteen track “You’ve Got It” from his upcoming album “Wrecking Ball”. http://t.co/TIJrL1eD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eating fish and other omega-3 rich foods could help people maintain healthy brains as they age http://t.co/uBvp5exW</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The L.A. Dodgers received multiple bids worth $1.2 billion to $1.5 billion during the second round of bidding http://t.co/d4icfZTV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“The very rich are like the unemployed, except they don’t have the edifying focus of trying to find a job.” http://t.co/7iaVjRld</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>http://t.co/08qdp5iU resolved a dispute with college bookstores over prices touted by online retailer in textbook ads http://t.co/TW5BqcAX</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich to Afghanistan: “Figure out how to live your own miserable life.&quot; http://t.co/zJzXjR2x</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Moms and dads of 20-somethings are writing resumes, tracking them on LinkedIn, going along to interviews http://t.co/ZucuqqC2</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Iran and its nuclear intentions are rising on the radar screen of presidential politics. It isn't likely to fade away http://t.co/gK8231f7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>CFOs said they expect to boost spending on tech by 10% over the next 12 months, even with confidence in economy down
http://t.co/DlSr6EfZ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reader Beware: Experts belittle Dow 13000 as a media phenomenon, a lot of talk with no significance for the market. http://t.co/wXfYFo0j</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Assertive. Driven. Code ninja. Words tied to male stereotypes signal to women that a co. won't hire them for tech jobs http://t.co/8RBvhMYj</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>$89.8 bil: combined net worth of China's richest politicians, 10X the riches of U.S. Congress, Supreme Court, President http://t.co/0cLnGoWn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Iranian TV trumpets Oscar win by Iranian film as a victory over Israel. But its filmmaker sought to avoid politics. http://t.co/QIvn5iT1</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The FBI has a new spokesman. His name is Gordon Gekko. His message: insider trading is a serious crime. http://t.co/45KcHJBm</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join a live chat now with former DC schools head Michelle Rhee @m_rhee on teacher performance ratings http://t.co/b083Qn0P</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One student dies, four wounded in Ohio high-school shooting http://t.co/XVYo4yfz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NYC ranked 18,000 4th- to 8th-grade teachers based on their students' math and English test scores. Explore the data: http://t.co/OnJ5XYNf</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live Chat: Former DC schools head Michelle Rhee @m_rhee takes your Qs on teacher performance ratings today at 1p EST http://t.co/b083Qn0P</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A student vote at Texas A&amp;M could make Samantha Ketcham the 1st female cheerleader—or yell leader—in school history. http://t.co/7FHRuFoU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Germany's parliament has approved the new rescue package for Greece. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How to fix executive compensation? Base the CEO’s pay on both the company’s debt and its stock. 
http://t.co/YC325SCj</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In the U.S., carriers pay Apple about $400 every time a customer buys an iPhone with a two-year contract http://t.co/QYqPyMND</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>World Bank's on China 2030: &quot;broad consensus that China’s growth is likely to slow&quot; http://t.co/gUKeNYVE’s-bitter-pill-for-china/?mod=e2tw</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Four students were wounded Monday in a shooting at their high school outside Cleveland, and one person is in custody http://t.co/XVYo4yfz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Romney and Santorum are in a dead heat in Michigan, with the former Mass. governor ahead 39% to 37% among GOP voters  http://t.co/TRQn1uIr</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Warren Buffett's successor doesn’t know that he/she is the chosen one. http://t.co/ktbP2w9b</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Suspects arrested in an alleged plot to assassinate Russian Prime Minister Vladimir Putin, state TV reported http://t.co/DyZJLk5u</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>$25: How much less the typical American household will spend on energy this winter than last. http://t.co/rrWEgNEf</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Artist Named Best Picture http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>the Academy Award for Best Actress goes to Meryl Streep http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And the Academy Award for Best Actor goes to  Jean Dujardin http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who will be named best actor? Best actress? Best picture? Our live coverage continues. http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our live Oscars coverage continues: http://t.co/rjXCzC4w #Oscars</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our reporters are live-tweeting the Oscars. Here's a list to follow along: https://t.co/kv52rDE1 #Oscars</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's show time! See our live Oscars coverage. http://t.co/rjXCzC4w #Oscars</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're live blogging the #Oscars! Check it out: http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our reporters are live-tweeting the Academy Awards. Here's a list to follow along: https://t.co/kv52rDE1</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From the Red Carpet to the acceptance speeches, see our live coverage of the Academy Awards: http://t.co/rjXCzC4w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seth Rogen called the Independent Spirit awards &quot;completely inconsequential.&quot; Our film critic says yes and no.  http://t.co/w5uEgnrn</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hot pink sleeves, disco-worthy dresses, voluminous pockets, swirling pale coats. Simons' last collection for Jil Sander http://t.co/7fFLY4jp</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Berkshire has found a successor to Buffett. Buffett doesn't name successor; says he is not 'going anyw... http://t.co/Rvur9Yjm</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Two NATO officers in Kabul killed by Afghan policeman upset over Quran burning. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @PreetaTweets: As we'd reported yesterday, El Paso reaches a deal to sell oil-exploration assets to Apollo, etc for $71.5 billion.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hedge funds and other investors make trades guided, in part, by data from social media like Facebook and Twitter http://t.co/6ncppOBO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The S&amp;P notched its highest close since June 2008, with positive reports on home sales and consumer sentiment http://t.co/j0Gzkkb2</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How will the Oscar race shake out? Weigh in on who will win, and keep score Sunday night. http://t.co/JRB3DsAj</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gingrich: there’s a ‘right way’ to legalize gay marriage http://t.co/gxvEeuCt</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The moms of celebrities, like @Real_Shaqs_Mom, are getting into the 140-character Twitter act. http://t.co/NLSY67nM</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Swedish couple married 300 years ago, but the anniversary has never appeared on any calendar. The day: Feb. 30 1712 http://t.co/h0sCetBw</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Japanese firm suspected of losing $2.3 bil of investor money flagged as potential &quot;Japanese Madoff&quot; as early as 2009 http://t.co/yyNi47Zk</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Companies that make loans for in vitro, egg harvesting and other fertility treatments say their business is thriving. http://t.co/gFeRUolz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Regrets about love - failed marriage, rocky romance - more intense than decisions about work/education, studies find http://t.co/n6kWKR9D</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One tip for boosting smartphone battery life: cut off apps' access to GPS. See more: http://t.co/xPCjCyos</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's not a joke. Bill Maher is giving $1 million to the Super PAC supporting Obama. http://t.co/xLDIGD4f</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The teacher rankings released by New York City today take a much different approach for assessing teachers http://t.co/GxTR8lCJ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Google's newest frontier: the ocean. Anyone with a Web connection will be able to see the Great Barrier Reef, live. http://t.co/9I1gbILh</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What is @jk_rowling's new book about? Here's what she's been tweeting: http://t.co/cbCko8pU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>McDonald's en francais = McBaguette. In April, the fast-food chain will serve a baguette-based burger in France http://t.co/B4vcU20g</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More than a dozen states considering making it illegal for companies to discriminate against the unemployed http://t.co/WmaIu6fC</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From @SteveMartinToGo and @taylorswift13 to @SHAQ and @Mariobatali: The Top Celebrity Tweeters: 
http://t.co/KWnI8k0K</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This year's Academy Awards could be the biggest night yet for social media. See our social-media guide to the #Oscars http://t.co/MOVWpSgv</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The trial of a Rutgers student accused of spying on roommate's gay tryst started. The roommate later committed suicide http://t.co/XEKN7RKS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Negotiations between U.S. and N Korea had been extended to a second day. Food aid for N Korea among topics discussed http://t.co/aDLQmuPR</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NYC to release internal rankings of 18,000 teachers, measured over 3 years on ability to affect student test scores. http://t.co/wDRi49nb</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Japanese fund can't account about $2.3 billion in pension-fund assets under management, investigators found http://t.co/ti2uV26D</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can you say McBaguette? McDonald's to launch a baguette-based burger in French market http://t.co/0aD69Rjy</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>National League MVP Ryan Braun's 50-game drug suspension has been overturned by an arbitrator http://t.co/SO2cMDI0</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fans of pop stars send their idols all sorts of crazy stuff. In South Korea, it's lunch. http://t.co/Fdmpn41g</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lured into a new bank account by a gift card or frequen-flier miles? There's a bonus: a visit from the tax man. http://t.co/5wpfqfRs</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Several start-ups are piggybacking on Pinterest's wild popularity. One, http://t.co/jTOcm1vt, to display &quot;manly&quot; images http://t.co/jhDIOCgz</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can J.K. Rowling work her magic with adults? The author behind the Harry Potter series announced an adult book deal. http://t.co/mBuRO7yh</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On the airplane police blotter: slapping flight attendants, watching child porn, throwing peanuts, yelling &quot;hijack&quot; http://t.co/4CORDyuG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ECB President Mario Draghi spoke with us about the importance of austerity in Europe, the Greek bailout deal and more. http://t.co/PPuNQZ3o</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's a new obsession at the intersection of genealogy and foodie culture—reconstructing long-lost family recipes http://t.co/CPTHJzj5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Jordan sued Chinese a sportswear chain, saying it improperly uses &quot;Qiaodan,&quot; the Chinese version of his name http://t.co/G7H5yXek</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In New Hampshire, the House weighed an unusual proposal to make it illegal for state lawmakers to bully one another. http://t.co/jH6Ko1ty</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Could Michigan Democrats be swing voters in the state’s GOP presidential primary on Tuesday? The game’s afoot. http://t.co/BrmYLZhV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ECB President Mario Draghi says in an interview with WSJ that euro-zone countries mustn't backtrack on aus... http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>$13,000: listed monthly rent for 2 BR condo Jeremy Lin signed for in NYC's Downtown W Hotel. He got a better deal http://t.co/tIxycavH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Abortion, debt, economy, education, same-sex marriage. See where GOP candidates stand on the issues:
http://t.co/SLITzQCo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FDA advisers back weight-loss drug Qnexa. Patients lost about 10% of their bodyweight on average from the drug. http://t.co/YJTL9GRS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seven Marines were killed Wednesday when two helicopters collided in Arizona during night-training exercises http://t.co/SI3omP2w</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is it unfair for men and women to compete against one another—even in sports where size and strength matter little? http://t.co/DGI46aRu</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sears posted a $2.4 billion quarterly loss and said it would spin off about 1,250 stores and cut jobs. http://t.co/cEbrNkHM</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Not so fast. A bad cable may be to blame for the claim that some particles can travel faster than light speed. http://t.co/nBtglp6z</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A group of Web giants including Google agreed to adopt a &quot;do-not-track&quot; button - a move the industry has been resisting http://t.co/t5Qxgl2q</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In what could be the final GOP debate, Romney delivered a sharp performance that could help his odds in AZ, Michigan http://t.co/xHK6CBst</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our real-time coverage of tonight's GOP debate is live and lively. Add the tag #wsj to your tweets to be included. http://t.co/mdh4f1zg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We want to include your tweets in our live GOP debate coverage. Add the tag #wsj to your tweets. We'll feature here: http://t.co/YkWuRMFZ</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our real-time coverage of tonight's GOP debate starts in minutes. For live blog and social media highlights: http://t.co/mdh4f1zg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We want to include your tweets in our live GOP debate coverage. Add the tag #wsj, and we'll feature them here: http://t.co/mdh4f1zg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're covering tonight's GOP debate live, starting at 8 p.m. ET. See blog and social media highlights. http://t.co/mdh4f1zg</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. companies are dialing back their quarterly profit forecasts at the highest rate since early 2009 http://t.co/sokYpu7z</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: An FDA advisory panel overwhelmingly backed Vivus Inc.s weight loss drug Qnexa. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tech cos agree with Calif. AG on privacy rules for mobile apps. See WSJ Investigation about how those apps watch you. http://t.co/GgfkgqcN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;The biggest misconception older workers have of young people is that they want to be humored at work.&quot; http://t.co/CLCDTUr7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The average American who lives to 100 will spend $3.5 million in his/her lifetime. About $1.5 million by age 50 http://t.co/6Fm2LKGK</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>People who work in cafes are onto something: a moderate level of noise prompts more-creative thought, a study finds http://t.co/Rb1YlTw7</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Too busy to breath! Me time? Ha. Are you as busy as you think? http://t.co/yD1gNl63</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Chinese maker of soccer balls and basketballs took out the trademark on Jeremy Lin's Chinese name http://t.co/GNccdEGi</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fire these employees to win the game of business http://t.co/h5VdrBkO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The average gift from the Tooth Fairy dropped to $2.10 last year, down 42 cents from $2.52 in 2010. http://t.co/w2kbmq5e</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can you stretch your 168 hours a week to better purposes? Join a live chat with a time-management expert at 1 p.m. ET. http://t.co/4zYTBy1j</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Act moody at a restaurant? Better service. Wearing a suit at lunch? Speedier service. How waiters read your table: http://t.co/rRIjh7F8</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Buried in the Mongolian desert: the world's largest unexploited gold and copper deposits. A battle over its ownership: http://t.co/8qL16sZh</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Merlot with your White Castle slider? In Indiana, the burger joint tests wine pairings. http://t.co/kxSUmcOG</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Several of the most common and costly mistakes that investors make appear to be encoded in our genes. http://t.co/v2Twgcqp</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Every Friday, a Texas judge considers crimes involving canines of all sort - Labs, Chihuahuas - and the occasional cat
http://t.co/GdhjRRrL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chávez to have a new operation for cancer, casting Venezuela into political turmoil months after he said he was cured
http://t.co/ZRo889gT</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>China's wealthy elite are heading West for things money can't buy in China: cleaner air, safer food, better education. http://t.co/Gmt45gkq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>New national poll shows Santorum leading Romney in GOP presidential race, with support of 35% of GOP voters surveyed. http://t.co/AqboHAuN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A French photojournalist and one of the UK's best-known war correspondents were killed Wednesday in Homs, in Syria. http://t.co/sVUcYrfE</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Fitch downgrades Greece's credit rating to C From triple-C. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Kevin Rudd resigns as Australian foreign minister. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Apple’s stock surge has materially impacted the S&amp;P 500′s moves over the last few years http://t.co/w7XT9XhY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An illegal luxury basement, an affair and a Hong Kong political race gone awry. Satirists take aim at city's scandal. http://t.co/zqeH8SKq</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nutella milkshakes. Chicken w Flamin' Hot Cheetos. Hospitals hire trained chefs to revamp menus, cater to medical needs http://t.co/HuMstmfY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Johnson &amp; Johnson has picked Alex Gorsky to be its next chief executive. Meet the new CEO: http://t.co/OIc4WM7U</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Comcast is unveiling online video streaming for a selection of old TV shows and movies. DirecTV could be next. http://t.co/m402iPYo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A day after Mexico's worst prison riot, authorities said massacre was a cover for the escape of 30 drug-gang members http://t.co/syWJAWgf</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After piercing the 13000 level for the first time in almost four years, the Dow finished below that mark http://t.co/DjgBZ7k5</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pinterest clarifies stance on copyright issues, offering snippet of code to Websites that don't want material &quot;pinned&quot; http://t.co/IuZKK3dd</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rabbit ear TV antennas are cool again. Why? More online TV shows available and the chance to save on cable bills. http://t.co/onst7cPv</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Could your Facebook profile be a predictor of job performance? http://t.co/7ViLtUPY</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Best performing stocks of the year: Bank of America and Caterpillar. Worst: Verizon Communications, P&amp;G, Coca-Cola http://t.co/1RunCBKW</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Dow crosses 13000 for first time since May 2008  http://t.co/VEzybvPU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Supreme Court agreed to review affirmative action in public-college admissions http://t.co/TMVMNPkV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Skinny jeans blamed for nerve compression, digestion issues, back pain, yeast infections. Clothes create health issues: http://t.co/rOAlxEMS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. and Mexico have reached a deal to allow oil and gas drilling on more than 1.5 million acres in the Gulf of Mexico http://t.co/IIPfPOjD</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Uncertainties loom on whether Greece can stick to deal terms given deteriorating economic situation. See deal guide: http://t.co/6OyVUcyC</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Questions about the euro zone's deal to bail out Greece? Follow @djfxtrader and #fxchat for a Q&amp;A happening now.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A potential Greek deal nears. Follow @djfxtrader today for live updates on the Euro Zone crisis.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: China's central bank has cut the reserve requirement for banks by 0.5 percentage point. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Dow Jones Industrial Average closed at a 52-week high today http://t.co/QPhHoZks</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amazon is buying three large blocks in central Seattle to build 3 million square feet of office space http://t.co/uPX6vQDX</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Federal agents arrested a man who they allege planned to carry out a suicide bombing at the U.S. Capitol http://t.co/cT47WaBP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Internal Revenue Service is offering up to $15 million for some professional public relations help. http://t.co/cvy60bD1</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hollywood's biggest names—with support from Silicon Valley's deepest pockets—are racing to create new Web shows. http://t.co/xPGXVkzL</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Mitsui will pay $90 million over the Deepwater Horizon accident, the U.S.'s first settlement over the ... http://t.co/3uGRrjPS</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Talking dictionaries are giving rare languages, like Siletz Dee-ni and Matukar Panau, a new life. Listen to a sampler: http://t.co/9JCAszUA</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>J&amp;J’s McNeil Consumer Healthcare is recalling grape-flavored liquid infant Tylenol after dosing system concerns http://t.co/H3mrc4zc</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: U.S. Senate votes 60-36 to pass payroll-tax package.  http://t.co/PeZhlzLU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: House votes 293-132 to pass payroll-tax cut bill. Senate expected to vote soon.  http://t.co/PeZhlzLU</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join @BinkleyOnStyle at noon ET for a live chat about the latest trends from Fashion Week http://t.co/7wNu3A5z</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. and European officials were cautiously receptive to Iran's call for a resumption of nuclear negotiations http://t.co/ZSw9RXXw</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've pulled together highlights from the work of @WSJ writer Jeffrey Zaslow, who died last week at age 53 http://t.co/WH6Dw1QH</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Researchers say they've developed a drug-delivering, implantable microchip that could replace daily shots: http://t.co/RJ4ISo0h</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Competition is heating up in Canada's market for ice hotels. Now there are two: http://t.co/sifg3JnO</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: Consumer prices rose 0.2% in January, less than the 0.3% forecast.  http://t.co/gryWFatl</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: German President Christian Wulff announces his resignation. http://t.co/CJYfCxIo</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joseph Kennedy III, grandson of Robert F. Kennedy, to announce he’s running for Congress http://t.co/4KIbqPCV</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Instagrammers: Which of our fashion week pics did you like most? Visit the WSJ account &amp; &quot;like&quot; your faves. We'll post the top shots online.</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hall of Fame catcher Gary Carter died today after a battle with brain cancer. He was 57. http://t.co/RTBZLuVT</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The NJ assembly passed legislation allowing for gay marriage, but Republican Gov. Christie has vowed to veto http://t.co/nM53bxja</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Dow closed near a four-year high, after strong readings from labor and housing markets, progress in Europe. http://t.co/ZArqrRdX</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston had hoped to remake Judy Garland's final film. http://t.co/Mnk3sgOm</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are the computer's days numbered? http://t.co/XvVNtIDR</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking: ECB moves to shield its Greek bonds from any forced losses connected with private-sector debt talks.  http://t.co/74ReigiN</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>15% of new U.S. marriages in 2010 were between individuals of a different race or ethnicity, 2X the share in 1980 http://t.co/tTHe8rK4</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The number of Americans with debt under collection has surged over the past decade to 30 million Americans http://t.co/scVBVTnm</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dreamliner supposed to revolutionize air travel: less airsickness, jet lag, headaches. Even babies may not cry as much. http://t.co/NzZiHyE6</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>19 students arrested in a drug sting at Texas Christian University, including four members of powerhouse football team. http://t.co/jYh5s1FP</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As New York Fashion Week wraps up today, some of the hottest trends already are on the sales racks. http://t.co/R9C8lK1J</text>
    <name>Wall Street Journal</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>