<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">
  <tweet>
    <text>RT @SportsNation Vote in the Madden Cover Play-In Round - http://t.co/CUOJ3qx2 #MyMaddenCoverVote</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who would you like to see on the cover of the Madden 13 video game &amp;amp; why? Reply with #MyMaddenCoverVote and we’ll RT a few.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two days from right about ... NOW, the games will be on the TV and nobody will be allowed to speak to you. #Madness</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gruden drops some Championship knowledge on young buck Kellen Moore at #GrudenQBCamp (via @MNF) [pic]: http://t.co/2nAlhXJR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dun. Dun. DUN! NFL Free Agency begins at 4pm. Here is your guide to it all - http://t.co/5WVzrvzh</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yes. It is still totally acceptable to fill out brackets all day - http://t.co/Betu86YE</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celtics &amp; Clippers slugging it out in a tight game with less than 5 minutes to go. See who walks away the victor -&amp;gt; http://t.co/rgP3gw2o</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@DakotaStarnes we understand. Sports never sleep.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Clippers just ran their favorite play: throw the ball in the vicinity of the rim, watch Blake dunk. #LobCity</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed it, here’s D-Rose throwing it down with some anger --&amp;gt; http://t.co/u4p97GX1</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Derrick Rose = Raging Bull  …  the reigning MVP just took over this ball game.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brian Scalabrine just entered the ball game … loudest cheer of the night.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Knicks vs. Bulls … Monday night just got awesome.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Shaka Time! RT @ESPNU Right now on College Basketball Live we're talking #VCU / #WichitaSt and classic #12 seed vs #5 seed matchups!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Arsenal and Newcastle are tied at 1-1 and have just started the second half. Watch it HERE -&amp;gt; http://t.co/ushqhyHm</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Think YOU are the ultimate college sports fan? Prove it and you might get to go to the @ESPYs -&amp;gt; http://t.co/n5Z54Nwk</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here are 10 BOLD predictions about the tourney -&amp;gt; http://t.co/is7kwcsT</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How do your fill out your bracket? Any superstitions? Use the hashtag #BracketSuperstitions and we’ll RT our favorites.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;#IWishIHad a perfect bracket&quot; - Everyone.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's To Do List: Fill. Out. Brackets. -&amp;gt; http://t.co/LvvdzbCb</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;You never want to feel what I felt that day&quot; - @MagicJohnson #TheAnnouncement</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The new @ESPN_Films “The Announcement” begins now! #magic</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get all your questions about the brackets answered w/ @GottliebShow on Facebook at 9pm/ET -&amp;gt; http://t.co/oSXx889V</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need help with your bracket? Reply with a question and we'll answer it in our live Bracketology after show at 9pm/ET: http://t.co/oSXx889V</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Want to sound off on @JayBilas about the tournament? Use the hashtag #BarkAtBilas to state your opinion and we’ll RT our favorites.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The NCAA bracket is officially O-U-T, OUT. Fill yours out here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/RhbWjl7c</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @RealJayWilliams: The South Region is loaded: UK, UConn, Duke, Iowa State, Baylor, IU, Wichita St, Xavier &amp; Notre Dame.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here we go RT @ESPNHomeCourt: And your four #1 seeds for the NCAA Tournament are #Kentucky, #Syracuse, #UNC, and #MichiganSt.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@_samuelangus here is the video on YouTube! Glad you like it - http://t.co/Ch0NBrfK</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michigan State beats Ohio State for the Big Ten championship, and now ... we wait. #brackets</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The brackets aren't even released yet, but the upsets have already begun! #Vandy #FSU</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Two awesomely close games between UNC-Florida State, and Kentucky - Vandy. You might like to call this &quot;Bracket Scouting.&quot;</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snaer has 15. Barnes has 15. Florida State - UNC for the ACC Championship ... it's faaaannntastic.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UNC-FSU, Kenucky-Vandy. One game on the TV, one game here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/4peRHT4Q</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight at 9pm ET, the new @ESPN_Films &quot;The Announcement.&quot; Here is a 3 minute sneak peek -&amp;gt; http://t.co/JjoS43eC</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ladies and Gentlemen, sharpen your pencils. It's Selection Sunday.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Louisville are your Big East champs … and also prove, that no matter how ugly, a win is a win --&amp;gt; http://t.co/Xw8OPZJC</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gerald Green’s been trending for a while now. This dunk is the reason why --&amp;gt; http://t.co/9cxdP4Jo</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“There are 86,400 seconds in a day. It's up to you to decide what to do with them.” #JimmyV (via @TheVFoundation)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Louisville vs. Cincy … this game will leave Big East bruises, guaranteed.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big 12 Championship: Tigers &amp;gt; Bears … so who’ll get the No. 1 seed out of the Big 12, Mizzou or Kansas?</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mizzou and Baylor are in a good ol’ fashion Big 12 shootout. We’re also pretty sure Baylor’s uniform can glow in the dark.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming into this year, Duke had won three straight ACC Tournaments. Number four? DENIED by FSU! #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've got another potentially insane ending on our hands with FSU/Duke. Watch it here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/fVT0FPBB</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Twitterverse just got a lot more Green-y. Welcome to Twitter, Mike Greenberg! Follow the man -&amp;gt; @Espngreeny</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And with that, Tar Heel Nation breathes a collective sigh of relief. #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>N.C. State is REAL close to taking down UNC. Watch the end here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/Rd3Z5vJj</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brutal. RT @SportsCenter: @MNTimberwolves Guard @rickyrubio9 out for the season with a torn ACL http://t.co/HvZlO7w4</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Florida's basically staring Kentucky in the face &amp; saying, &quot;We ain't scared of you.&quot;</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's Agenda: 1) Watch college basketball 2) Watch college basketball 3) Eat 4) Watch college basketball</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @AdamSchefter Redskins traded three first-round draft picks and a second-round pick to St. Louis for second overall http://t.co/d5x46kM3</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuse (#2) and Kansas (#3) both just lost tournament games. If tonight is any indication, next week will be ... CRAZY!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Big time Big 12 Battle&quot; going down on @espnu right now. #Kansas #Baylor</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cincinnati just handed Syracuse their second loss of the season. Take notice, the Bearcats are making some noise.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@BoIma_FreeMan over on ESPNU!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Baylor is rocking the camo jerseys tonight. Yay or nay? -&amp;gt; http://t.co/6qSEHgDf</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who is watching more than one game at once? No more perfect time than right now - http://t.co/LZppq0hF #Madness</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rob Wilson averages 3.1 points per game for the Wisconsin Badgers, but he just dropped THIRTY against Indiana -&amp;gt; http://t.co/uzNAMaTS</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@josephmlevy You're welcome! Enjoy the action.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brandon Lloyd (@mrblloyd) and his awesome blue pants stopped by Bristol today -&amp;gt; http://t.co/s5DwwIMh</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Doron Lamb has a message for LSU -&amp;gt; http://t.co/kpbUzDAM</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need three words to describe #ChampWeek? @DickieV has you covered -&amp;gt; http://t.co/QSxabo6S</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What would you say to get Peyton on your team? Reply to @SportsCenter with #PeytonPitch and we'll RT a few.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@WJLewellyn Ole Miss 68-54: http://t.co/LoY0qqDY</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Irish, say hello to the Cards RT @ESPNHomeCourt: #Irish finally pull it off - wasn't pretty - #butawinisawin - http://t.co/BIJEQIKk</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is it going to be enough? RT @GottliebShow: Texas is going to win this game! Crazy..not that they are winning,but because they are dancing.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @dgoneil1: We are at the 8minute mark of the scoreless streak. Watching USF on offense is like watching statues. No one moves. At all.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rick Pitino and crew knock off the #GoldenEagles and live to fight another day in the Big East Tourney:   http://t.co/f8tr7k2c #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>THAT counts. We're headed to #DOUBLEOT.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What a finish. Tie game. Who wins? Get to a TV! #Cincy #Georgetown</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Raise your hand if you have been watching hoops all day!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big 12 tournament. Big East tournament. Big link to watch all the games online -&amp;gt; http://t.co/EN6DQ7NR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuse and UCONN tip-off at noon. If the game is anything like 2009, it will end at five o’clock - http://t.co/fFsefkvn</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kyrie Irving dropped 18, hit the game winner, and created this sweet poster last night -&amp;gt; http://t.co/o0gAcA31</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All-around stud performance by D-Rose AND the game-winner at the buzzer. Just icing on the cake --&amp;gt; http://t.co/VEMBbgt2</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ouch! RT @ESPNStatsInfo Kobe goes 9-for-31, missing 22 shots; tied for the most missed shots in an NBA game this season. He tied himself.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mario Lemieux finished his career with 690 goals &amp; 1,033 assists. Add one 4,700-pound statue to his stat line --&amp;gt; http://t.co/TnedDBAw</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Louisville and Seton Hall would like MSG to remove the invisible lid placed over the rim for the 2nd half.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>When the goin’ gets tough, the tough watch the game &amp; forget about it.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Holy schnikes, Lionel Messi just scored five goals in one match. That's a Champions League record -&amp;gt; http://t.co/wAer6cEw</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Yu Darvish had a pretty impressive Spring debut today. Look at his numbers -&amp;gt; http://t.co/awFgrBSs (via @ESPNDallas)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watching college hoops all day technically qualifies as working, right?</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>WHERE’S PEYTON MANNING GOIN’!? This should give you a pretty clear idea: http://t.co/aPJh3y2K</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're proud to introduce Anthony Robles (@arobles125) as our new NCAA Wrestling analyst -&amp;gt; http://t.co/9AGLUSlo</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT: @LegsESPN: #Lakers bad loss vs Detroit. Defensive breakdowns late really cost them -&amp;gt; http://t.co/zgmpdDIf</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With Princeton beating Penn, Harvard is headed to the tournament for the first time since 1946 -&amp;gt; http://t.co/gvAek3yB</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Western Kentucky, with a record of 15-18, is going dancing! They just won the Sun Belt Championship -&amp;gt; http://t.co/WgOhvaqI</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Masked Mamba decided to switch up the mask tonight -&amp;gt; http://t.co/E5ciIXeH</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“Most people have the will to win, few have the will to prepare to win.” – Bobby Knight</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One of these dudes might just be the breakout star this March --&amp;gt; http://t.co/lDmW5IOX</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First Round, check. Can the #Huskies make it 4 more for the #BigEast title? #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @page2: Baylor to debut bright -- repeat, bright -- new unis at the Big 12 Tournament: http://t.co/HIrFjlkU (via @DorseyPatrick)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jeremy Lamb already has 15 points, the same amount as the rest of the #Huskies: http://t.co/GusvDvUA #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big East Tourney all day. It’s #ChampWeek, baby. (@ Madison Square Garden for DEP vs CONN w/ 47 others) [pic]: http://t.co/r566Fwzl</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Grab a pen and paper, @ESPNLunardi guides us through his latest #Bracketology update: http://t.co/S9yqUhLQ</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed it last night, The Blake Show dunkathon continues --&amp;gt; http://t.co/ejcktln8</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If tonight is any indication, #ChampWeek is going to be insanely, ridiculously, absurdly awesome this year.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GONZAGA WITH THE LATE THREE!!!! RT: @ESPNHomeCourt: #ONIONS!! Overtime in the WCC Championship!!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If D-Rose wanted to send a message to the Pacers, he did. Look at how badly the Bulls beat Indy -&amp;gt; http://t.co/d4RWxiEW</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@SteeZoriuS Marty Brodeur, Miikka Kiprusoff, and Henrik Lundqvist</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Marc-Andre Fleury just notched his 35th win. Meaning? Flower became the 4th goalie in NHL history w/4 straight seasons of 35+ wins.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>BOOM SHAKA-LAKA! VCU is officially back in The Big Dance: http://t.co/rGt4Uw6w #ChampWeek</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Drexel's trying to snatch away a tourney bid from VCU in the last minute. Watch the end here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/JAS6fybz</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“We’re scrappier and tougher than we were last year ... We’re a little meaner too.” – Shaka Smart</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This is what Dick Vitale would sound like if his voice was one octave higher --&amp;gt; http://t.co/Q1WysMMM</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>30 days until you can yell “PLAY BALL!!!” ... no matter where you are. #OpeningDay</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You know that’s gonna leave a mark --&amp;gt; http://t.co/Yzhfj9kx</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After Kobe's recent domination with the mask, we wonder if Metta World Peace might bring back this gem -&amp;gt; http://t.co/PyAI5lx4</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From best game-winning play to best mid-major, our @JasonKingESPN is doling out some regular-season awards --&amp;gt; http://t.co/FnnumKtA</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More impressive: Rajon Rondo’s triple-double or D-Will’s 57-point game? Reply with #WeekendBaller. We’ll RT our faves.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Da Bulls up by 2 with 1:21 left RT @KNegandhiESPN: South Philly is rockin right now!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>D-Will just went NUTS and put up 57 points against the Bobcats...no big deal: http://t.co/YQWMW7rV</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>DRose with 15 at the half, but the #Bulls trail by 6: http://t.co/PFMWE48U</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Masked Mamba has 20 at the half. 18 were in the first quarter.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rondo's final stat line: 18 points, 17 rebounds, 20 assists. #WOW.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Four words: Paul Pierce is clutch.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This feels like playoff basketball right now.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Knicks have 13 turnovers, but they still lead 56-51 at the end of the first half -&amp;gt; http://t.co/A0qevxtL</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Celtics have won their last 10 home games against the Knicks. It's the C's longest current home winning streak against any opponent.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How do you silence the Cameron Crazies? GET EVEN. #UNC</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If Coach K’s looking for offense, there’s a QB with a laser rocket arm in the building. He’s been known to put up points quickly.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UNC's taking a page out of Michael Jordan's book. Don't be intimidated by the crowd. Embrace the hate.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UNC-Duke Part Deux is officially underway. If you're not by a TV, get to one or watch it online here: http://t.co/eNKkJ2PM</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Cameron Crazies are literally so loud you can't hear the P.A. Announcer.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuse just sent a message to everyone watching, “You do not want to play us in March.”</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What. A. Game. Murray State defeats Tenn. State and officially punches their ticket to the Tourney as Ohio Valley champs.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>These Duke fans are thinking, “Beat UNC!” This one fan is thinking, “Peanut Butter Jelly Time.” --&amp;gt; http://t.co/xW1VbBTO</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It looked like UConn was going to blow out Pitt. Now it's a tied ballgame. Watch the ending here --&amp;gt; http://t.co/JHUXYDhR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seven+ hours before tip-off and UNC vs. Duke is already trending. #CantWait</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LeBron passes it to Haslem, passing up the last shot. Haslem misses. Heat lose by one to THE Utah Jazz, 99-98 http://t.co/fj1kEKRe</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On the anniversary of Wilt Chamberlain's 100 point performance, the Sixers scored 105 as a team.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sixers. Warriors. Clippers. Suns. Friday nights haven't seen basketball this good since &quot;Hangin w/ Mr. Cooper.&quot; #TGIF</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @SportsCenter anchors are taking Employee Appreciation Day a little too seriously this year --&amp;gt; http://t.co/3mUSxTo3</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>For your weekend viewing pleasure, @ESPNAndyKatz provides some guidance on the top college hoops games: http://t.co/ezON2OsC</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Less than a minute into last night’s UGA-UK game, the ref got an unexpected surprise: http://t.co/WNDzhFzf</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“I couldn't have come close without my teammates' help because the Knicks didn't want me to make 100.&quot; - Wilt Chamberlain</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed it last night – DWade to LeBron for the finish --&amp;gt; http://t.co/y0BmhsG8</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What's the best alley-oop tandem in the NBA right now?</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Thunder have an unfair advantage over their opponents. It's called &quot;Kevin Durant.&quot;</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How is &quot;David Krejci&quot; NOT trending? Look at the night this dude had for the Bruins: http://t.co/HJRrVkez</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tweet a question for @JayBilas with #AskBilas. Jay will drop knowledge on you on Twitter or ON AIR during the UGA-Kentucky game.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michigan basketball is no joke. The Wolverines just won at Illinois for the first time since 1995: http://t.co/5o5mWvLP</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here’s a clip from our first studio broadcast in 1979. Safe to say, things were MUCH different back then -&amp;gt; http://t.co/ukq1kceK</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A look back at one of sports’ coolest, nastiest, and most intense rivalries -&amp;gt; http://t.co/zVYME46f</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It’s March, which means it’s REALLY time to dig into Bracketology -&amp;gt; http://t.co/8wOPn7iC</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dear March, we're ready. Bring on the Madness.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Great basketball, awesome endings. Thanks Leap Day, see you in 4 years.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Here’s photo evidence of a Masked Mamba sighting in the first half --&amp;gt; http://t.co/eVEGtxds</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bulls and Spurs trading punches all night. Chicago looks like they’ve got San Antonio on the ropes. #HeavyWeightFight</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Baron Davis circa 2007 RT @MikeHillESPN I see you @Baron_Davis dropping some SERIOUS dimes. #vintage</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Steve Novak did the championship belt after hitting a deep three to put the Knicks up after being down by 17 --&amp;gt; http://t.co/0t0U5Fzz</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Derrick Rose was 9 years old when Tim Duncan was drafted in the @NBA. Tonight, they’ll share the court. #Bulls #Spurs</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It’s senior night at the Dean E. Smith Center in Chapel Hill. UNC's Tyler Zeller looks extra hungry tonight.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@SportsNation is looking for the #BestLeapEver. Use the hashtag #BestLeapEver to nominate your favorite dunk ever. We’ll RT our favorites!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Until today, the #USMNT had NEVER beaten Italy. Clint Dempsey changed that with this goal -&amp;gt; http://t.co/RFc8sTTP</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An in depth look back at “The Malice at the Palace” -&amp;gt; http://t.co/E7Njl0xO (via @Grantland33)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>They’re officially called “friendlies”, but these dudes ball hard. #USA and #Italy are live right now -&amp;gt; http://t.co/ACCmlFcn</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watching conference hoops tournaments...on Facebook. Yep, that’s how you’ll probably spend next week -&amp;gt; http://t.co/rxWN2CxR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get used to seeing this pic of @kevinlove &amp; @blakegriffin for the next 15-20 years -&amp;gt; http://t.co/pBrFn6yX</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Leap Day -&amp;gt; http://t.co/V6oerHYA</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @NFL announced that next season will start on WEDNESDAY, Sept 5th. So that means we're only 29 weeks away. Awesome.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Attention Top 5 Teams: Do NOT come to Assembly Hall. The Hoosiers have beaten three of 'em there this year -&amp;gt; http://t.co/wF8IZ27I</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Draymond Green is making his presence FELT. He's scored the last 16 points for Michigan State.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big test for Sparty right now. Win at IU, and Team Izzo gets serious daps for a #1 tourney seed. Watch it here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/qL7Ako6S</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“Good, better, best. Never let it rest. Until your good is better, and your better is best.” – Tim Duncan</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How badly does Orlando want to keep @DwightHoward? So badly, they made a music video for him -&amp;gt; http://t.co/pOnStU13 (via @Page2)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This guy is never brought up in the NBA MVP discussion, but he probably should be -&amp;gt; http://t.co/j41hJUBK</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A former Cal QB broke the world record for longest paper plane toss. You won't believe how far this thing flies: http://t.co/y9IDAeb1</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Indy? Washington? Miami? Retirement!? What should Peyton do &amp; why? Reply with #PeytonShould. We’ll RT our favorites.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Your fantasy baseball team is like a plant. Nurture it from the very beginning, and it'll grow into a championship.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why the 2012 Daytona 500 should forever be known as the “Great American Fireball”:  http://t.co/3ct34MDI</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;I can dance. But there's a time &amp; place for that and I don't think it was right.&quot; - Derrick Rose on All-Star Dancing (http://t.co/VMdlpctD)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Awesome shot! RT @MartySmithESPN: #Winner @mattkenseth http://t.co/xoQoa8FM</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More than 37 hours later, Matt Kenseth has won the #Daytona500 --&amp;gt; http://t.co/F165C38n</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The 55,000+ follower photo.  Wow 
RT @keselowski: Fire! My view http://t.co/Bqz7DP78</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MichelleDBeadle: 40 laps to go. Asphalt on fire. Methinks being downwind of that extinguishing material would not be ideal.Wth happened!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>RT @MartySmithESPN: Danica: &quot;I don't want to ruin anyone's day or affect anyone's day, but I want to be out here and learn, too.&quot;</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FINALLY!!! Time to rev up the engines under the lights. (@ Daytona International Speedway for Daytona 500) [pic]: http://t.co/CZIZuvX1</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;Finishing races is important, but racing is more important.&quot; – Dale Earnhardt</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed it, “The Face” created “A Face” of @MichelleDBeadle -  http://t.co/g64ApdES (via @SportsNation)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A Heat vs. Thunder Finals? If you saw the All-Star Game, @johnhollinger says it should’ve “left us hungry” --&amp;gt; http://t.co/OlQiJZXk</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What’s that ONE sports-related movie you could watch RIGHT NOW? Reply with the hashtag #SportsMovie. We’ll RT our favorites.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today is the NHL’s trade deadline day. And here are 6 reasons why you should care --&amp;gt; http://t.co/2WpcTBD1 (via @Grantland33)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @ESPNStatsInfo team breaks down Ryan Zimmerman’s big, fat $100-million contract with the Nats --&amp;gt; http://t.co/DkDFfaBu</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The All-Star Game was all fun and games, right? Tell that to Kobe Bryant's broken nose --&amp;gt; http://t.co/pzzT9ZzS</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Interested in a sports break from the Oscars? How about a game-winning half-court shot? http://t.co/Jj5DLYHn (via JackMan_13)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crazy dunks. Awesome alley-oops. Boatloads of points. Oh, and dunks. #AllStarGame</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Should defense be mandatory in the NBA All-Star Game?</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bummer. RT @MartySmithESPN: The Daytona 500 is postponed until noon Monday - http://t.co/AFh0qPDi</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#replacewordinmovietitlewithdanica is trending worldwide. This is what happens when a rain delay deprives us of Daytona.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On a scale of 1-10, this @Cristiano Ronaldo goal was a 19,000 -&amp;gt; http://t.co/Ms55Xsj3</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LaMichael James is outrageously fast. Look how quickly the dude ran the 40 -&amp;gt; http://t.co/2hinnQk2</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This guy ain't kidding. RT @JordanCoury: Tune into @espn right now. Great finish between cincy and USF.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What are two words that put a frown on the face of all sports fans? Rain delay.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“The winner ain't the one with the fastest car. It's the one who refuses to lose.” - Dale Earnhardt</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whoa. Everyone meet Jeremy Evans.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kevin Love and Kevin Durant are in the Finals of the 3-Point competition. Who says big dudes can't shoot!?</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kansas wins. What a thriller. T-Minus 17 days until March Madness!!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hey College Hoops, thank you. Seriously ... thank you.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>44-32 Mizzou RT @dgoneil1: Wow. Hugely impressive first half by Mizzou. Those first 5 minutes of 2d will be huge for both teams.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big win for James Buescher RT @RoFloESPN: Great finish at Daytona! Wow. Insert your Ricky Bobby jokes here. #NASCAR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>28 points for Anthony Davis and another step closer to SEC perfection for #Kentucky:  http://t.co/dPkVHqNa</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Hokies looking to pull off an upset in Coach K's house.  Watch the last 5 minutes here: http://t.co/cfA90Yky</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're about 10 hours away from tip-off, but that hasn't stopped Husky fans from bringing it early.  It's #GameDay. http://t.co/L1yI7JM2</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UPSET IN PROGRESS - West Virginia's up on #10 Marquette late in the 2nd half. Watch the end here: http://t.co/XT8a1hpR</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How are Kyrie Irving, Ricky Rubio, John Wall, &amp; Jeremy Lin playing in the RISING STARS Game? We live in the Golden Age of Point Guard.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do Penny Hardaway, Chris Mullin, &amp; J. Cole have in common? They're all playing in the NBA All-Star Celebrity Game: http://t.co/0LkUwvKJ</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>&quot;I just wanted to fit in and make sure Kobe didn't dominate.&quot; - Michael Jordan on winning the 1998 NBA All-Star Game MVP.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What would make for the best #OfficeCombine drill? Reply with the hashtag #OfficeCombine. We’ll RT our favorites.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Maggie Meier shot hoops with the help of her sister. Sounds ordinary, but Maggie did this while in a coma -&amp;gt; http://t.co/IyzUpL9j</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>He’s 5’9 and DUNKS over anything. Even @MichelleDBeadle -&amp;gt; http://t.co/bRk2UEU2 (via @SportsNation)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All good things come to an end … it just hurts when it happens in a shootout --&amp;gt; http://t.co/eTYCtnDH</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dirk (@Swish41) reliving the moments after the Mavs won the title is absolutely fantastic -&amp;gt; http://t.co/44k2JUFT  (via @Sportsguy33)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#UpsetCity in Cincinnati.  #Bearcats take down the #Cardinals 60-56: http://t.co/JmYg566T</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ridiculous RT @SportsCenter: #SCtop10 - Hey @KingJames, we felt this dunk in the newsroom #boom #heat http://t.co/L1CdZm8g</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lin and Stoudemire have 12 combined turnovers in the half, the #Heat have 9 total.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming off the bench, Andre Dawkins just drained his 5th 3-pointer of the game: http://t.co/weT4jdN4 #Duke #FSU</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There is a chance @DickieV might suit up tonight!  (@ Donald L. Tucker Center for DUKE vs FSU w/ 67 others) [pic]: http://t.co/8GIn2MbB</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Last time the Seminoles faced the Blue Devils, they made Austin Rivers react like this -&amp;gt; http://t.co/3NUP4VST</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NBA All-Star Weekend, NFL Combine, Daytona 500. Yeah, don’t make any plans this weekend.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ahhhh. The sight of Spring Training -&amp;gt; http://t.co/PgJws0q3</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pack your bags #RG3 and Andrew Luck, you’re headed to Gruden Camp - http://t.co/oBMV9wYQ</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Memories! Knicks vs. Heat is a great reminder of Van Gundy hanging from Alonzo Mourning's leg - http://t.co/vYkutqxI</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Last night’s dunk of the night - @blakegriffin go up, @blakegriffin go boom - http://t.co/jbLkKEAt</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Thunder scored 72 points in the FIRST HALF! They have four players in double figures: http://t.co/S1m2Tm5Y</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celts-Thunder. Lakers-Mavs. You legitimately have no excuse to leave your couch tonight.</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>“Push yourself again and again. Don't give an inch until the final buzzer sounds.” – Larry Bird</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Those with arachnophobia should not view @PTI today. There will be a Durantula sighting. Watch it here -&amp;gt; http://t.co/1huf3K8s</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Thirty-two years ago today, the U.S. Hockey team made its country believe in miracles: http://t.co/5j4ufAjG</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This mascot officially gives @MCHammer a run for his money in the breakdancing department -&amp;gt; http://t.co/aL9MlutT (via @Page2)</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Multiple ballers dominated the hardwood last week. Now, we need you to determine who deserves top dog status: http://t.co/lDmW5IOX</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You might want to take notice of this team when you're filling out your bracket in two weeks: http://t.co/mEttpyjF</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>UH. OH! Could number one go down? Mississippi State is on a mission to make that happen - http://t.co/mmgnzMtO</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Binghamton won tonight. Why is this awesome? They just snapped a 27-game losing streak!</text>
    <name>ESPN</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>