<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>A day in the life of the non-League football captain who listens to Boyzone on the way to the match! http://t.co/FbO4wpzR @skytyneandwear</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>11-1 Rock on Ruby wins the Champion Hurdle at Cheltenham #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The excitement is building at Cheltenham - who are you backing on Day One?</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AP McCoy is at #Cheltenham - we'll hear from him before 12pm #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>David Craig will be at Cheltenham with the one and only Ronnie Corbett - don't miss it after 11am #SSN!</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can Rangers find a new buyer? We're live to Glasgow for the latest on First Fast Now</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amir Khan &amp;amp; Lamont Peterson are going to get it on again - their live news conference is on the way this morning #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's day 1 at #Cheltenham - we're live to the course throughout the day #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tony Jardine will be in the #SSN studio on First Fast Now to look ahead to a brand new season of #F1 .</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Napoli President Aurelio De Laurentiis will be live in the #SSN studio at 10.30am - don't miss it!!</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's day 1 of the Cheltenham Festival &amp;amp; we're live at the course from 6.45am &amp;amp; @skysportsAlexH will pick her Cheltenham tip of the day #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll have all the  build up to tonight's Merseyside Derby, plus the latest on Tiger Woods battle to be fit for the Masters #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On Good Morning Sports Fans from 6am - action from last night's game at the Emirates as Arsenal close the gap on Tottenham to 1 point #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's also an interview with one of the world's very few openly gay footballers, who tells us how life has changed since going public.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight's Special Report at 7.30pm on Sky Sports News looks at how homophobia in football is being tackled.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>George Groves pulls out of Friday's fight with Kenny Anderson with injury. More on Sky Sports News.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aston Villa reach agreement to sign Brett Holman from AZ Alkmaar in the summer when his contract with the Dutch club expires.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Read @skysportsAlexH Cheltenham Festival blog at http://t.co/UVPXKbzi - and join her for all the news on GMSF from 6am tomorrow #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight's special report looks at homophobia in football. We speak with one of only two openly gay male pros in world football. #SSN 7.30pm</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Olympic gold medallist Darren Campbell joins us in the #SSN studio shortly</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up very shortly - Paul Nicholls speaks to us live on #SSN about Kauto Star, the Gold Cup and the Cheltenham Festival</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kauto Star fit to run in Cheltenham Gold Cup #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>GB Olympic medal hope Kerri-Anne Payne joins us live in the SSN studio @ 7.45#SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus action from the World Indoor Championships as Britain's athletes claim their best-ever medals haul #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've goals from La Liga as Messi reaches another milestone, plus action from Super League as Widnes produce a stunning fightback #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up on Good Morning Sports Fans we'll have action from yesterday's Prem games as the title race is blown wide open #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tiger Woods withdraws from WGC Championship with leg injury less than four weeks before the Masters.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Team Sky's Bradley Wiggins wins final stage of Paris-Nice and secures overall victory #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bob Willis joins us in the studio later this hour to discuss the latest allegations of corruption within English cricket. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Administrator at Rangers says club have received interest from potential buyers in the Far East &amp; America. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's the best of the action from the Championship as Southampton extend their lead at the top &amp; Reading make it eight wins from eight.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reaction to yesterday's pivotal games at the foot of the Premier League including that controversial game between Bolton &amp; QPR. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Later this hour we'll hear from David Moyes and Harry Redknapp on Everton's 1-0 win over Spurs.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Time for Goals Express. Let us know your goal of the day.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Keep tweeting your goal of the day contenders from the Football League.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tweet us your goal of the day from the Football League. Watch Goals Express on #SSN from Seven.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll also speak to Neil McCann this hour after Rangers players agree to pay cuts in bid to avoid significant job losses. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - live with Gary Neville at the Reebok as we look ahead to the lunchtime game between Bolton &amp; QPR. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our #GetInvolved series continues with a pioneering scheme in Durham which brings the gym to you. WOW - Wellness On Wheels. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live news conference with Andy Flower from 8.15am ahead of England squad's departure for the two-test series against Sri Lanka. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus find out who's leading at the WGC Cadillac Championship in Miami after taming the Blue Monster with a 10-under second round 62. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's action from last night's Super League games as Warrington's unbeaten start comes to end &amp; St Helens' winless run continues. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get all the latest team news ahead of another crucial weekend in the PL including the relegation six-pointers at Bolton &amp; Wolves. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - Iain Dowie joins us on the Skypad to preview Bolton's crucial match against QPR tomorrow. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Steven Davis &amp; Allan McGregor are the latest players to agree to pay cuts at Rangers. We're at Murray Park throughout the day.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England name unchanged starting XV to play France in Paris on Sunday. Hodgson &amp; Palmer come in among replacements. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - we hear from Steven Naismith on his decision to take a 75% cut in wages at Rangers. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jake White rules himself out of running to become next England Rugby coach. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>India batsman Rahul Dravid announces retirement from international cricket. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus there's action from the Blue Monster course in Miami. World No.1 Rory McIlroy among the big names finding it difficult going. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reaction to a bad night for both Manchester clubs in the Europa League including an injury blow for City. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Steven Naismith &amp; Steven Whittaker agree to 75% wage cuts at Rangers. All the latest on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The latest on reports Lukas Podolski will join Arsenal this summer. We'll hear from his international team-mate Per Mertesacker #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today is International Women's Day we'll hear from Gail Emms, Sally Gunnell, Beth Tweddle &amp; Lucy Alexander #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Trial set for 30th of March for Ranger's administrators to try &amp; claim a sum of £3.6m which is held by owner Craig Whyte's solicitors #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - more on the financial crisis at Rangers as administrators warn there could be a number of redundancies tomorrow #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Australia beat Sri Lanka by 16 runs in deciding match of ODI tri-series final. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live at the High Court &amp; Murray Park this hour for the latest on the financial crisis at Rangers. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Badminton silver medallist Gail Emms joins us in the studio this hour as we discuss ways of inspiring more women to participate in sport</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - Mick Dennis of the Daily Express reviews the morning's papers with much of the focus on the future of Robin Van Persie.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Australia dismissed for 231 in third &amp; deciding ODI tri-series final against Sri Lanka. Best of the action on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>International Women's Day: Hear from bobsleigh brakewoman Serita Shone on her recovery after October's horrific crash in Germany. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Messi becomes first player to score five goals in a single CL game. All the goals from Barcelona's rout of Bayer Leverkusen on #GMSF</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's International Women's Day. We hear from some of the most inspiring &amp; influential women within sport throughout the morning. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mario Balotelli fined one week's wages by Manchester City for breach of club discipline.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join in with International Women's Day tomorrow on SSN. Find out more here:
http://t.co/n7wNi6Ji</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers administrators looking to sell the club in the next few days &amp; rule out European competition next season. More on SSN tonight.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former Rangers director Paul Murray to make offer for club before March 16 deadline #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers' second-largest shareholder Dave King believes club's liquidation is 'inevitable' #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>F1 fans - with the new season only ten days away you won't want to miss Red Bull boss Christian Horner live in our studio at 9:30! #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>League One Manager of the Month nominees - Chris Powell (Charlton), Danny Wilson (Sheffield United) &amp; Karl Robinson (MK Dons) #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And fans of #WWE - we're joined by @zackryder at 4.30pm. Send your questions for him to @SimonThomasSky and @TheRealKirstyG #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Also this morning, all the goals from the Football League along with the Champions League action and reaction #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>League One Manager of the Month nominees revealed on #SSN very shortly</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking news - Wales captain Sam Warburton will miss Six Nations game against Italy on Saturday. Gethin Jenkins to captain side.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking news - Sky sources: Rangers players Gregg Wylde and Mervan Celik to leave club.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking news - Sky sources: Rangers administrators reject players' wage proposal.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lewis Moody about to talk to us about his retirement on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wolves midfielder Karl Henry out for 3-4 weeks with hamstring injury</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lewis Moody retires from all forms of rugby. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Worth a follow - @skytyneandwear - for dedicated sports coverage &amp; news from the area #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Find out what happened when @mcilroyrory replaced @CaroWozniacki to play Maria Sharapova! Amazing pictures coming up on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dean Holdsworth, Paolo Di Canio &amp; Phil Parkinson shortlisted for League Two Manager of the Month #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>News on the hunt for Fabio Capello's successor on #SSN this morning, along with the latest from Chelsea and Rangers</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>League Two manager of the month nominations coming up in a few minutes on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>30 mins until Special Report featuring an explosive interview with Bernie Ecclestone, and a former Grand Prix winning driver in the studio.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Just over an hour to go until tonight's Special Report F1 Countdown 7.30pm Sky Sports News. Not to be missed!</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers players fail to agree wage cuts with administrators. Talks to resume tomorrow after players issue final proposal.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Find out if Sven Goran Eriksson would be interested in the Chelsea managerial vacancy after 5pm on #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The F1 boss also talks about Bahrain and the future of the Melbourne Grand Prix. Not to be missed. 7.30pm Sky Sports News HD.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On tonight's Special Report at 7.30pm we hear Bernie Ecclestone's thoughts on Lewis Hamilton &amp; Pussycat Doll Nicole Scherzinger.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And @mcilroyrory is the new world number one. We'll show you how he won the Honda Masters - and how he rose to the top #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Good morning! We've got the latest on Chelsea's managerial situation on #SSN this morning &amp; more reaction to Andre Villas-Boas' sacking</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Super League action and today's Rugby Union Premiership games on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Avram Grant tells us what he makes of the AVB sacking - hear the interview #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll be live at Stamford Bridge this afternoon for even more on the sacking of #AVB - Sports Sunday #SSN for all the big name reaction</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who will follow AVB in the permanent job at Chelsea? The bookies have been busy already - more reaction throughout the day #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Graeme Souness, Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Redknapp on the sacking of AVB - all on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AVB lasts less than a full season at Chelsea - where now for the Blues? Reaction on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>ANDRE VILLAS-BOAS SACKED - REACTION RIGHT NOW #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Huge breaking news this hour Chelsea sack Andre Villas-Boas #SSN now for the latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>HUGE BREAKING NEWS FROM THE PREMIER LEAGUE #SSN RIGHT NOW</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A manager is sacked in League One - details right now #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's Premiership Rugby is underway - we're bringing you updates from Welford Road and beyond on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lots more live sport about to get underway - join Julian Warren &amp; Natalie Sawyer on Sports Sunday #SSN 1pm</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Championship action this afternoon - but can West Ham get a win at Cardiff? Find out on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Final day of F1 testing - we'll bring you the sights &amp; sounds from Barcelona #SSN this afternoon</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Three Premier League games today - it's about to get rolling &amp; we'll update you all the way on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What a finish between Australia &amp; Sri Lanka at the Gabba - we'll bring you the big hitting action on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can Rory McIlroy become the World Number 1 today? We'll keep you up to date with his progress on Sports Sunday #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus, see Wladimir Klitschko get his 50th knockout - as brother Vitali says he wants to fight David Haye next #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Goals from yesterday's games on #SSN this morning along with all the build-up to today's matches</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mikael Lustig &amp; Andre Blackman make Celtic debuts at Aberdeen today. Full team news on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live at Ibrox &amp; Fratton Park this hour for the latest on the situation at Rangers &amp; Portsmouth. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fabricio Coloccini &amp; Tim Krul sign new long-term contracts at Newcastle. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live news conference from Newcastle coming up from 9.30am - stay tuned #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You may have seen the film, so why not try it for yourself. Dodgeball is the focus of our #getinvolved series. Details coming up this hour</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And we've got the latest from Florida where Justin Rose is co-leader after two rounds of the Honda Classic. Has Tiger Woods made the cut?</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's last night's action from the Championship, Super League &amp; Rugby Union Premiership. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get all the latest team news ahead of today's games including Arsene Wenger on the importance of Arsenal's lunchtime trip to Anfield. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations to Millwall's Josh Wright. He wins our goal of the week poll with 42%.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers administrators say club needs to save £1million per month.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers statement coming up shortly.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The FA to wait until the end of the season to appoint a new England manager. All the details on SSN Afternoon Report.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Andy Murray through to Dubai Championship final after beating Novak Djokovic 6-2 7-5. All the action on SSN Afternoon Report.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sheffield Wednesday appoint Dave Jones as manager on three-and-a-half-year deal.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sri Lanka beat Australia by nine runs to reach three-match final of ODI tri-series. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coventry given temporary transfer embargo after late filing of club accounts. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up shortly Iain Dowie is on the SkyPad to preview Saturday's lunchtime game between Liverpool &amp; Arsenal. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Arsenal checking on fitness of Robin van Persie &amp; Thomas Vermaelen ahead of trip to Liverpool. Arsene Wenger coming up. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wayne Rooney fit to return against Tottenham on Sunday - hear from Sir Alex Ferguson in the next hour. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tony Gale joins us in the studio shortly to preview the weekend's Premier League games. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mist delays start on day two of final round of F1 pre-season testing in Barcelona. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak to Kauto Star trainer Paul Nicholls shortly following news the two-time Gold Cup winner is a major doubt for Cheltenham. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Daniel Christian takes hat-trick for Australia in ODI tri-series against Sri Lanka. See it on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus there's action from the first round of the Honda Classic in Florida. A win for Rory McIlroy will secure him world no.1 ranking. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's all the latest on the financial turmoil at Rangers, Portsmouth &amp; Port Vale. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get all the latest team news ahead of a pivotal weekend in the Premier League. We'll hear from 13 PL managers throughout the day. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Dave Jones in advanced talks with Sheffield Wednesday.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers administrators will not announce any redundancies today #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Portsmouth unlikely to receive any further parachute payments or other League funding #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Portsmouth administrators claim club may not be able to fulfil season's fixtures. #SSN now for the very latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former England international Alan Mullery joins us on set just after 10.15am to review last night's game against the Netherlands. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up we're live in Barcelona for the latest from the final round of F1 pre-season testing. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check out the freakish goal from the recent friendly match between Maccabi Haifa &amp; Dynamo Kiev. It's coming up at the end of the hour #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Action from last night's international football on the way including a goal for David Silva in Spain's 5-0 win over Venezuela. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus there's the goals from Windsor Park as Michael O'Neill suffers defeat to Norway in his first game as Northern Ireland boss. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We hear from an emotional Chris Coleman after Wales' defeat to Costa Rica in the Gary Speed memorial match. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reaction to England's defeat to Netherlands on #GMSF including Scott Parker's thoughts on the captaincy &amp; injury updates</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sheffield Wednesday sack Manager Gary Megson. More on #SSN at ten.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll be live to Wembley for more reaction to news Scott Parker has been named England captain for tonight's game with the Netherlands #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nobby Solano on his best goal, best team mate and best opponent. #NUFC  http://t.co/NZTgY88k @skytyneandwear</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>South Africa beat New Zealand by six wickets in second ODI to take unassailable 2-0 lead in three-match series. Action on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak to Frank Warren shortly following the WBC's decision to hand Dereck Chisora an indefinite ban. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Paul McCarthy joins us around 7.30am to review the pick of the papers. Jose Mourinho's sighting in London has caused a stir. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus see all 36 goals from last night's League 1 &amp; 2 games including a nine-goal thriller between Gillingham &amp; Hereford. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reaction to Dereck Chisora's indefinite ban by the World Boxing Council coming up on #GMSF</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dereck Chisora given indefinite ban by World Boxing Council.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Updates from all League 1 &amp; League 2 fixtures tonight on Sky Sports News. Team News also from 7pm.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Following on from Stuart Pearce, Joe Hart news conference coming up on Sky Sports News #ssn.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stuart Pearce press conference now on Sky Sports News #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eoin Morgan &amp; Graham Onions dropped from England test squad for tour of Sri Lanka - James Tredwell &amp; Samit Patel called-up #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Six time world swimming champion Mark Foster in the #SSN studio now</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus, Andre Villas-Boas accepts he could be sacked before the end of the season. More on that on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stuart Pearce will name his England captain today - who do you think it should be? Build-up to tomorrow's Netherlands game on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England beat Pakistan by 5 runs in third twenty20 international. See how they did it on SSN tonight.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Just 20 minutes to go until tonight's Special Report 'The Taxman's War On Football'. Not to be missed! #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aston Villa striker Darren Bent ruled out for up to three months with ankle injury.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight's Special Report investigates 'The Taxman's War on Football' with ex-Pompey Chief Exec Peter Storrie in the studio at 7.30.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fulham sign former Real Madrid midfielder Mahamadou Diarra until end of season subject to visa #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's reaction to yesterday's games, including the Steel City derby, and more classic goals from Messi &amp; Ronaldo in Spain #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Good morning! Join us on #SSN for action from Liverpool v Cardiff, Arsenal v Spurs, Norwich v Man Utd &amp; Stoke v Swansea</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chris Samba interview coming up shortly on #ssn.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Liverpool fans - Virgin Trains spokesman joins us in a few minutes to give an update on today's travel problems #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And we've got build-up to the League Cup Final, North London derby &amp; today's other games #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On #SSN this morning - yesterday's Premier League &amp; Football League goals, as Manchester City go five points clear at the top</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Supporters advised to check http://t.co/qd8hp84n for more details - updates also on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>An engineering train has derailed on the main line between Liverpool &amp; London. Fans advised to travel from Crewe, Stafford or Stoke #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congratulations to Millwall's Josh Wright. Winner of the Goal of the Day on #GoalsExpress</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Josh Wright's strike is proving to be the most popular goal of the day so far. #GoalsExpress</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Goals Express coming up at seven. Let us know your Goal of the Day from the Football League or SPL. #goalsexpress</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If you're at a Football League or SPL match today, tweet us if you think you've seen the Goal of the Day. #goalsexpress</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our #getinvolved feature on referees is on throughout the morning, roughly at quarter to the hour #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And have you ever considered becoming a referee? Watch this week's #getinvolved feature to find out what it takes, from 7.45am on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Morning all. We're building up to today's football in England &amp; Scotland on #SSN, along with the Six Nations matches.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Christopher Samba joins us on the phone shortly following his move to Anzhi.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Samba joins Anzhi Makhachkala for fee in region of £12million on four-year deal. More on #SSN sky channel 405.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Blackburn's Christopher Samba joins Russian side Anzhi Makhachkala.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Arsenal's Andrey Arshavin rejoins Zenit St Petersburg on loan until end of season.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Next on #SSN it's Mick Foley! #wwe</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up: QPR Manager Mark Hughes on facing his former club Fulham.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Keep tweeting your questions to Mick Foley. We'll read the best ones out later. #SSN #wwe</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>North London Derby preview coming up on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Harry Redknapp says the FA have not been in contact about the England job. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sri Lanka beat Australia by three wickets in latest match of ODI tri-series - action on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wolves appoint Terry Connor as manager until end of the season. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alan Curbishley joins us on the Skypad next hour to preview Sunday's north London derby at the Emirates. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>At 1115 former West Ham, Norwich and England striker @Dean36ashton10 will be in the studio speaking to @adamleventhal.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>WWE star Mick Foley is in the studio for a chat this afternoon. Send us your questions for the man known as the 'hardcore legend' #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're live at Murray Park next hour to get the latest on the financial crisis at Rangers. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tony Gale in the studio around 8.30am to preview this weekend's Premier League fixtures &amp; also Sunday's League Cup final. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up next hour we speak to Toro Rosso driver Daniel Ricciardo as F1 testing continues in Barcelona. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live to Barcelona after the break as the second round of F1 pre-season testing reaches its final day. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Shaun Custis joins us in the studio at 7.30am for a round-up of the morning's sports pages. Much of the focus is on AVB &amp; Chelsea #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus there's the latest from the WGC Match Play - Lee Westwood reaches the third round for the first time but Tiger Woods is out #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Action from the Championship also as Leicester win at Pride Park to extend Derby's winless run to seven games. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sir Alex Ferguson admits he got it wrong &amp; Tony Pulis is forced to defend his team selection. Reaction to last night's Europa League #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Manchester Utd team v Ajax: De Gea, Rafael, Jones, Smalling, Fabio, Nani, Park, Cleverley, Young, Berbatov &amp; Hernandez</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kell Brook is in the studio now looking ahead to his fight with Matthew Hatton.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sunderland striker Fraizer Campbell included in England squad to play Netherlands. Micah Richards is recalled. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England make four changes to team to play Wales. Parling, Dickson &amp; Morgan make first starts, Tuilagi also comes in. Full details on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England team announcement for Six Nations game against Wales coming up at 10.15am. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stuart Pearce names his #England squad today for Euro 2012 warm-up against Netherlands. Watch announcement live on #SSN from 11.30am</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mick Dennis reviews the morning's sports pages just after 7.30am. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers players &amp; staff are due to be paid today. We'll be live at Ibrox this hour for all the latest. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Olympic gold medal hope Jessica Ennis joins us in the studio for a chat at around 
7.45am - not to be missed. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus there's action from last night's CL games which both featured late winners. See how Basel continue to upset the odds #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celtic 20 points clear at top of SPL after win over Dunfermline. Mulgrew's opener described as a wonder goal by Lennon. See it on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roberto Mancini says Carlos Tevez could be playing again in two to three weeks. Hear from the Man City boss on #GMSF</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cardiff manager Malky Mackay has signed a contract extension until June 2016.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live to Ibrox later this hour for the latest on the financial crisis at Rangers. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plus all the goals from last night's football league action as West Ham return to top of Championship after an eventful win at Blackpool.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Andre Villas-Boas confident Chelsea can reach CL quarter-finals despite 3-1 loss to Napoli. Action &amp; reaction from 1st leg in Naples #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stay with us for the Chelsea team news. Could be very interesting tonight. John Terry already ruled out.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chelsea's John Terry to have operation tomorrow and expected to be out for up to six weeks #ssn for latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reports coming out of Italy: John Terry will miss Chelsea's Champions League match against Napoli tonight with knee injury #ssn for latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pakistan win the toss &amp; choose to bat. Regular updates from Dubai on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England make four changes for fourth ODI against Pakistan. Briggs &amp; Buttler make debuts, Bresnan &amp; Dernbach also come in. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Roberto Mancini coming up later this hour as he looks ahead to Man City's Europa League second leg against Porto. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pre-season testing has resumed ahead of the 2012 Formula 1 season - we're live in Barcelona after the break #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up next hour we hear from Mercedes Team Principal Ross Brawn as we get a first look at their new car for the 2012 F1 season. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On-loan striker Saido Berahino scores two sensational goals on home debut for Brentford. Last night's League 1 action on the way. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Darren Lewis joins us in the studio for a round-up of the morning's papers. AVB's future at Chelsea a topic on many of the back pages. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're live in Barcelona next hour as pre-season testing resumes ahead of the 2012 Formula 1 season. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll also hear from Jose Mourinho on his fears about the freezing conditions in Moscow ahead of Real Madrid's tie against CSKA. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Andre Villas-Boas confident his future at Chelsea is secure ahead of tonight's CL round of 16 tie at Napoli. Hear from AVB on  #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Huddersfield appoint Simon Grayson as new manager on three and a half year deal.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join us for tonight's Special Report at 7.30pm to see how local girl Perri Shakes-Drayton is preparing for this summer's Olympics</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Andre Villas-Boas news conference coming up shortly on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dereck Chisora has given his verdict on the brawl with David Haye. &quot;I've let my family, my team and worst of all the sport I love down&quot;</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Interview with David Haye's trainer and manager Adam Booth coming up on #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dave Haye says he will assist boxing authorities with any investigation following brawl with Dereck Chisora #ssn for latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On tonight's Special Report at 7.30pm Perri Shakes-Drayton looks ahead to what could be an eventful year as she countsdown to London 2012</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kevin Blackwell has applied for the vacant Huddersfield manager's job - he's talking to #SSN in a few moments</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Niall Quinn leaves Sunderland #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If you're an Android phone user, you can download the Sky Go app from this morning &amp; watch Sky Sports channels on the move #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Good morning! We've got the latest on the fallout from the Dereck Chisora &amp; David Haye's brawl - plus, another Lionel Messi masterclass...</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've got reaction from Chisora's promoter Frank Warren and Robert Smith from the British Boxing Board of Control #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll be speaking to a German Police spokesman shortly for the latest on their investigation into the Chisora/Haye brawl. Stay tuned to #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chisora detained by German police at Munich Airport - more reaction on SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A reminder you can see the post-fight brawl between Haye and Chisora on SSN this morning</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>German Police to interview Haye &amp; Chisora today as a part of an official investigation into the events of last night's post-fight brawl</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Also  - Rangers lose to Kilmarnock, a KP century helps England win ODI series v Pakistan &amp; we've got goals from the football league #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On #SSN this morning - we've got sensational footage from Munich after Derek Chisora &amp; David Haye brawl in the post-fight press conference</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Notts County sack Martin Allen. More on that and goals from the football league and SPL on SSN Goals Express now.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Leeds appoint Neil Warnock as manager</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We look at synchronised swimming as part of our #getinvolved series today. Tune in from 7.30am to find out more about the sport #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're building up to FA Cup fifth round clashes on #SSN - plus, more on Portsmouth after they are docked 10pts for going into administration</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SPL deny Rangers permission to sign Daniel Cousin #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>West Ham's Ravel Morrison admits FA charge following comments on Twitter.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sheffield Wednesday chairman Milan Mandaric says he has no interest in becoming involved with Rangers #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Portsmouth owe money to West Brom, Wolves, Bristol City - along with Football League and Portsmouth Council #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Updates on Portsmouth's situation on #SSN throughout the day. We'll bring you news on their points deduction as soon as it's confirmed</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Portsmouth go into administration #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Martin O'Neill views on Arsenal coming up now on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And see what happened when boyband McFly took on Saracens on the pitch - and in a bush tucker trial!</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reaction to all three Europa League games on #SSN this morning - plus, more on Rangers' problems &amp; David Beckham on the England job</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Man City complain to UEFA alleging Mario Balotelli was racially abused by Porto supporters - more on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Throughout the night on #SSN we'll have Europa League reaction plus Phil Taylor's superb 9 dart finish.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Darts action coming up from 10pm #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll hear from Sir Alex Ferguson this hour on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ally McCoist interview coming up on Sky Sports News.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carl Froch will be live in the #SSN studio at 4.30pm - fight fans, don't miss it</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Craig Whyte tells #SSN when he expects the club to come out of administration - full details on Afternoon Update</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Strong comments on the way #SSN from Andre Villas-Boas on his relationship with the players &amp; Abramovich</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What's happening at Chelsea? Andre Villas-Boas is on the way #SSN this afternoon</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stevo will be in the #SSN studio to look ahead to a big weekend of Rugby League on Sky Sports - join us at 2.30pm</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big breaking Rugby News on the England Coach's job #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ferguson, Mancini &amp; Pulis look forward to a big evening of Europa League football #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>More fallout from our exclusive on the future of the Olympic Stadium - find out who's said what #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Administrators for #Rangers call news conference for 3.30pm today at Ibrox. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak to Leyton Orient chairman Barry Hearn shortly on the future of the Olympic Stadium. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live at Ibrox in the next hour as administrators plan to speak to the Rangers players today. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up after the break Bill Bradshaw reviews the morning's papers including the reaction to Arsenal's defeat at AC Milan. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Architect Steve Lawrence revealed as complainant to EU which helped derail West Ham's original bid to move into Olympic Stadium. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Arsenal's hopes of reaching Champions League quarter-finals virtually over after 4-0 loss to AC Milan. All the action &amp; reaction on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From 10pm we'll hear from Alex Salmond MSP on the deepening crisis at Rangers</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lee Clark says he's perplexed and shocked to be sacked by Huddersfield.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alastair Cook scores second century in a row to help England set Pakistan 251 to win the second ODI in Abu Dhabi. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tottenham midfielder Tom Huddlestone ruled out for the rest of the season with an ankle injury. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll be speaking live to Portsmouth chief executive David Lampitt on the club's financial problems later this afternoon. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking news - Sky Sources: Huddersfield sack Lee Clark. More on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nick Easter signs three-year deal at Harlequins. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chris Robshaw to captain England for the remainder of the Six Nations. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England taking on Pakistan in the second ODI in Abu Dhabi. England currently 61-0 after winning the toss. Score updates on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's deadline day at the RFU for applications to become the new England head coach. Updates on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A big night of Champions League football too. Arsenal take on AC Milan at the San Siro - we hear from Arsene Wenger #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We'll have the latest on Rangers' financial crisis throughout the day #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up shortly we speak to Rob Burrow ahead of Leeds Rhinos' World Club Challenge against Manly on Friday. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live at Manchester City training ground after the break for the latest on Carlos Tevez. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>West Ham midfielder Ravel Morrison charged by the FA over comments made on Twitter. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England name unchanged team for second ODI against Pakistan. England have won the toss &amp; will bat. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chris Smalling, Phil Jones &amp; Nani return to Man Utd squad for game at Ajax. No place in squad for Dimitar Berbatov or Ryan Giggs. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The reaction to Rangers' financial plight keeps coming - we speak live to former midfielder Trevor Steven just after 10am. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak to Roger Hannah of the Scottish Sun later this hour as we discuss the implications of Rangers going into administration. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Some great goals in the Football League last night - check out the cracker from Swindon's Billy Bodin in their win over Crawley. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Patrick Barclay joins us live in the studio shortly to review the best of the morning's sports pages. SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Also hear from Rangers manager Ally McCoist as he sends out a rallying cry to supporters after SPL champions enter administration. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>92 goals scored in Champions League, Football League &amp; Scottish Cup last night. See them ALL on #GMSF</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Strathclyde Police confirm Rangers game with Kilmarnock on Saturday will go ahead.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Interviews for job to begin within the next 48 hours. More on Sky Sports News channel 405.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sky Sources: Wolves shortlist for manager's job includes Alan Curbishley, Steve Bruce &amp; Neil Warnock.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers go into administration #SSN now for the latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Standby for pictures of Carlos Tevez arriving at Manchester airport #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Edinburgh Court of Session give Rangers until 3.30pm today to appoint an administrator  #SSN for all the latest developments</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>HMRC launch application to put Rangers into administration - more details on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sri Lanka &amp; India tie in latest ODI tri-series match in Adelaide. Watch the thrilling action on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carlos Tevez is due back in the UK today. If you spot him send us a picture or video to u2us@skysports.com #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Live to Ibrox shortly as PFA Scotland Chief Executive Fraser Wishart discusses the implications should Rangers enter administration. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We hear from Kevin Phillips about the Martin O'Neill factor at #Sunderland. 
For the full interview go to http://t.co/Zs5X9xzH</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're also live at Fratton Park as we get an update on the latest financial turmoil to hit Portsmouth. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up shortly we're live at Manchester City's training ground as we await the return of Carlos Tevez. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Steve Curry joins us just after 7.30am for a roundup of the morning's papers. Plenty of copy focuses on Tevez's return to City. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Valentine's Day! Let us know if romance has affected your plans on a busy night of football in any way. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's also the latest from Rangers as the SPL champions file notice of intention to enter administration. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hear from Carlos Tevez on #GMSF as the controversial striker prepares to return to Man City today. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers owner Craig Whyte tells SSN that the club's tax bill could potentially reach £75m</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers owner Craig Whyte on intention to take club into administration: &quot;This is the best way to take the club forward.&quot; More on #SSN now</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Exclusive interview with Rangers owner Craig Whyte coming up in a few moments on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Join us at 7.30pm for our special report on one of European football's most successful players - AC Milan's Clarence Seedorf.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're about to speak with Carlos Tevez's advisor Kia Joorabchian on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carlos Tevez: Mancini treated me like a dog. Full interview coming up in a few minutes on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's also more on Mick McCarthy's sacking at Wolves and, from 6pm, a lengthy interview with Carlos Tevez #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A very busy night at #SSN. The latest on Portsmouth &amp; Rangers taking steps towards administration throughout the night</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rangers serve notice to go into administration #SSN for the latest</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Striker Daniel Cousin agrees to join Rangers until the end of the season #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's Super League on the way. We'll hear LIVE from the Leeds camp ahead of their World Club Challenge meeting with Manly on Friday. #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up in the next few minutes we'll hear from Wolves chief executive Jez Moxey on the reasons behind Mick McCarthy's sacking.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aston Villa defender Richard Dunne out for eight weeks with a broken collar bone #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>AC Milan's Clarence Seedorf is the subject of tonight's Special Report. Tune in from 7.30pm to hear his secret to staying at the top! #ssn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wolves sack manager Mick McCarthy #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England:  Cook   Pietersen  Trott   Bopara   Morgan   Kieswetter   Patel   Broad  Swann  Anderson   Finn</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>England win the toss &amp; choose to bat in first ODI against Pakistan in Abu Dhabi. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plenty of talking points from the Premier League over the weekend. Alan Curbishley joins us in the studio just after 10.30am. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak to Spanish expert Guillem Balague in the next hour as we preview this week's return of the Champions League. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up - we're live at the Liverpool training ground for all the latest after the controversial weekend defeat at Man Utd. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Paul McCarthy joins us shortly for a review of the morning's sports pages - he can also give us an update on Carlos Tevez. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zambia celebrating after penalty shootout win over tournament favourites Ivory Coast in Africa Cup of Nations final. Action on the way #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's also action from La Liga where Cristiano Ronaldo scored his sixth hat-trick of the season to help Real Madrid open a 10-point lead</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mick McCarthy apologised to Wolves supporters after 5-1 derby defeat by West Brom at Molineux. All Sunday's Premier League goals on the way</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Man City restore two-point lead at the top with win at Villa &amp; could have Tevez available for title run-in. Hear from Mancini on #GMSF</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Martin Offiah on #SSN now for Super League review.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Big developments in the #Suarez controversy &amp; the #Tevez affair - full details at 6pm #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carlos Tevez wants to return to Manchester City &amp; play a part in the title run-in: full details #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wolves lose the Black Country derby 5-1 - hear from Mick McCarthy &amp; Roy Hodgson #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Four Super League games underway - updates from all of them #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Suarez-Evra affair reaches Government level - find out who's said what #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Manchester Utd respond to Liverpool's apologies in the Suarez-Evra case - full details #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Liverpool MD Ian Ayre says club was misled by Luis Suarez &amp; criticises him for failing to shake Patrice Evra's hand - more now on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Luis Suarez apologises for not shaking Patrice Evra's hand - latest on #SSN now</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today's racing at Exeter abandoned due to frozen track #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're about to speak with Liverpool legend John Barnes on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We speak live with PFA chairman Clarke Carlisle in a moment to discuss yesterday's events at Old Trafford #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And it's the black country derby between Wolves &amp; West Brom - all the build-up on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're looking ahead to today's Super Sunday clashes - as Manchester City try to regain top spot against Aston Villa #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A busy morning on #SSN as we reflect on yesterday's drama at Old Trafford. We've got goals from the Premier and Football league too #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now on #SSN it's Goals Express. The best of the action from the Championship and the SPL. Tell us your goal of the day.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>MUFC to play LFC: De Gea Rafael Ferdinand Evans Evra Valencia Carrick Scholes Giggs Rooney Welbeck</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LFC to play MUFC: Reina Johnson Agger Skrtel Enrique Gerrard Spearing Henderson Downing Kuyt Suarez #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Luis Suarez starts for Liverpool against Manchester United #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Scotland unaffected so far - but if that changes, we'll bring you the latest #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Postponement update: All on in Prem, 10 on in Championship, 3 on in League One &amp; 3 on in League Two. Updates on #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our #getinvolved sport this morning is orienteering. Find out more about at 11.45am - and let us know whether you're interested! #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Despite the efforts of Peterborough &amp; West Ham fans trying to clear the London Road pitch of show, their game has been postponed #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Peterborough are appealing for supporters to help clear their pitch. They need around 300 people to help as soon as possible #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So far we've lost 11 games to the weather - 1 in the Championship, 4 in League One &amp; 6 in League Two. Pitch inspections at other grounds too</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've also got the latest in our #getinvolved series from around 7.45am #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Good morning! We're looking ahead to today's big games, including Man Utd v Liverpool. We've got all the latest on postponements too #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tomorrow on Sky Sports News from 7am find out how you can get involved in an unusual sport. #getinvolved</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crystal Palace v Doncaster postponed due to frozen pitch.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ryan Giggs signs a one-year contract extension at Manchester United #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Harry Redknapp news conference coming up on #SSN - along with interviews with Sir Alex Ferguson &amp; Arsene Wenger</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Birmingham's Chris Hughton, Charlton's Chris Powell &amp; Torquay's Martin Ling win respective Football League Manager of Month awards #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tony Gale in the studio after the break to talk about the weekend's fixtures #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Martin Kaymer's just scored a hole-in-one at the Dubai Desert Classic - tune in to #SSN to see it</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And thanks for all who voted in yesterday's poll for who you want as England manager. The top three: Redknapp 61%, Mourinho 14%, Pearce 8%</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's also the England job latest, reaction to Amir Khan's world title rematch &amp; an interview with Milan Mandaric on his future in England</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A huge week for football so far - now it's time for the games! We're previewing tomorrow's 8 Prem games, including Man Utd v Liverpool #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amir Khan's rematch with Lamont Peterson arranged for May 19 in Las Vegas. Reaction on SSN Through the Night.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amir Khan is live in the studio very shortly on SSN.</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ryan Jones replaces suspended Bradley Davies at lock for Wales against Scotland in Six Nations on Sunday. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Former World Welterweight champion Ricky Hatton joins us live in the studio just after 
4.15pm - don't miss it. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#SixNations chat coming up as Dewi Morris &amp; Stuart Barnes join us live on set. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coming up shortly Stevo joins us for a look back at the opening weekend of Super League XVII &amp; a look ahead to the second round of games</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FA say next manager does not have to be English but would be &quot;preferable&quot;. All the details from FA news conference coming up. #SSN</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Stuart Pearce takes temporary charge of England for Netherlands game. FA begin drawing up shortlist of candidates for new manager tomorrow</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Harry Redknapp interview on #SSN at 11am - tune in</text>
    <name>Sky Sports News</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>