<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>If you've signed up for #BracketInsanity (http://t.co/63FJxhTD), what's the name you came up with for your bracket entry?</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With Fab Melo out, are you changing your picks in #BracketInsanity? Head over to the game and make your picks - http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuses' Fab Melo ruled ineligle for NCAA Tournament - http://t.co/LBaSMnWU</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Adjust those brackets! More to come on http://t.co/SsRfxVlB. RT @Cuse: Center Fab Melo to miss NCAA tourney http://t.co/9AbzQia3</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Source tells SN's @SeanDeveney: Magic want Lakers back in Dwight Howard mix - http://t.co/sQ3bdOmN</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sidney Crosby to play on Thursday - http://t.co/lDwDWTK4</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Darrin Horn out at South Carolina - http://t.co/rFQfcysY</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Georgia Tech dismisses Glen Rice Jr. from team - http://t.co/9Odm80T4</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Donald Trump takes another shot at A-Rod - http://t.co/K82siRZG</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SMU fires Matt Doherty after six seasons - http://t.co/qhUu22kj</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>No. 16s play in the other game with @WKUSports (http://t.co/FlJUW2mI) &amp; @MVSUDevilsports (http://t.co/xWR0NpqW) #BracketInsanity #FirstFour</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In the battle of No. 14s, it's @ICGaels (http://t.co/aDWXvP55) vs. @BYUathletics (http://t.co/IDTmki3T) #FirstFour #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Don't call it the play-in game. Tonight is the #FirstFour. A brief primer here - http://t.co/lWtQ7cis</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Still haven't printed your bracket? What are you waiting for? Get yours here (PDF link) - http://t.co/W14KB4Ua</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cowboys, Redskins take major salary cap hits. What's your reaction to this devastating penalty just before free agency? http://t.co/vLC0E8gz</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How likely is your team to cut down the nets? @tsnmike presents his annual ranking from No. 1 (UK) to 68 (Vermont) - http://t.co/i8oUkttM</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With the First Four starting tonight, now's the time to jump into #BracketInsanity, SN's new tourney challenge - http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reports: Randy Moss agrees to deal with San Francisco 49ers - http://t.co/SPyGoo5d</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A closer look at the football penalties handed down today at North Carolina, including a one-year postseason ban - http://t.co/kHcaNMzI</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nationals will serve up 'Strasburgers' this season, which weigh eight pounds - http://t.co/uqZtAc9u</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kentucky ends season on top of AP poll -  http://t.co/fSbrh3tB</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The NCAA has announced a one-year postseason for North Carolina football and a reduction of scholarships. Details to come shortly.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Although Tiger Woods' game isn't what it used to be, he still has 'it,' writes @david_c_steele - http://t.co/KhVC0Qge</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Do you prefer the BCS-style postseason or the NCAA Tournament? David Whitley makes his choice known - http://t.co/B7PYWaxL</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The field of 68 is set, but SN's experts have narrowed it down to seven contenders. Make your picks accordingly - http://t.co/VQYHllIz</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need help filling out your NCAA Tournament bracket? Follow the first-round trends - http://t.co/OekhPWhO</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The latest NFL mock draft from @RUSSLANDE is live. How does the Redskins' trade change things? Find out here - http://t.co/rxvHHacf</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need a printable bracket this morning? We've got you covered (PDF) - http://t.co/V7aj11Wa</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Midwest is led by North Carolina. Can the preseason No. 1 fulfill their Final Four destiny? @tsnmike's pick - http://t.co/3jkmO1tO</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuse is the top seed in the East, but will it even advance past the Sweet 16? @tsnmike makes his East Region pick - http://t.co/7MLawd2g</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Michigan State make the Final Four out of the West Region? @tsnmike has the answer here - http://t.co/wP0GqNBe</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The South Region is headlined by top-seeded Kentucky. @tsnmike offers a closer look - http://t.co/LHLzJnwl</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Need help making your picks? Here are a few ways we can help you out. Click each team for their own breakdown - http://t.co/Pxy46qzR</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What's your first order of business this morning? Getting in SN's tourney challenge, #BracketInsanity - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#BracketInsanity is here. With the Field of 68 officially unveiled, it's time to play SN's game on Facebook - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get the full bracket here - http://t.co/Pxy46qzR And then play our game on Facebook - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did these teams get snubbed? Drexel, Northwestern, Miami, Seton Hall, Oral Roberts, Miss. State - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kansas is the No. 2 seed in North Carolina's region - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ohio State is the No. 2 seed in Syracuse's region. - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bubbles around the country popping: Iona a surprise inclusion as the No. 14 in the #FirstFour game - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Missouri is the No. 2 seed in MSU's region. Dangerous teams (No. 7 Florida, No. 8 Memphis) too - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If seeds hold, Duke could face Kentucky in the Elite 8, 20 years later. - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd  #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Defending champion UConn gets a No. 9 seed, could potentially face top-seeded Kentucky - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The top four seeds in the field of 68: Kentucky (S), Syracuse (E), UNC (MW) and Mich St. (W) - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The overall No. 1 seed: @UKCoachCalipari's Kentucky Wildcats - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Waiting for the Field of 68 to be revealed? Head over to Facebook and sign up for #BracketInsanity, our new game - http://t.co/VMFEp9qd</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eight hours from the NCAA Tournament selection show, @ryan_fagan tells you who's in and who's out. #BracketInsanity http://t.co/oYbM5J3X</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Remember Lamar coach Pat Knight's meltdown? http://t.co/q8KNXaRg That team is Tourney-bound. #BracketInsanity http://t.co/J8JnMjhN</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Florida loses, but proves its mettle against Kentucky #BracketInsanity http://t.co/r0jADY7L</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bad news for Timberwolves fans from @ChrisMannixSI: Ricky Rubio tore his left ACL. http://t.co/VD9oW0Cf</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sidney Crosby will not play on Sunday http://t.co/XNWU3gLL</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Redskins paid a steep price to snag #RG3, but @vinnieiyer says it was time for them to step in the fire. http://t.co/oobrOTAK</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Saturday's tournament week action is under way. Check out @ryan_fagan's freshly updated Field of 68: http://t.co/9tHzNjmf</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dale Earnhardt Jr. adds Juan Pablo Montoya's Daytona car to junk car collection - http://t.co/sihqVtob</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>North Carolina knocked off Maryland in the ACC Tournament, but John Henson injured his wrist. Get the update here - http://t.co/7o5o4Ltx</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Detroit Lions' Ndamukong Suh cited for speeding in Portland - http://t.co/OPszHMS0</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Homicide charges stand against former Viking's wife - http://t.co/AaMnyQhI</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Crosby still says Sunday return is possible; Who will he play with? http://t.co/x20TGPob</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>While you watch the conference tourneys, start your #BracketInsanity game group and share w/ friends on Facebook http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Magic want 'replica' of Carmelo package for Dwight Howard - http://t.co/JJPGbzFo</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Bruce Weber fired at Illinois - http://t.co/vHM4Wmk1</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>As first reported by @PKlee_IlliniHQ and confirmed by others, Illinois has fired coach Bruce Weber. Story to come on http://t.co/SsRfxVlB</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@RyanMHolloway Thanks for pointing that out. We'll make a change there.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>From the Big East tourney, @ryan_fagan examines whether South Florida's loss to the Irish will cost them a bid - http://t.co/S5P7AEAZ</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SN's @tsnmike has you covered at the Big 12 tourney in KC. He tackles this question: Has Texas done enough to get in? http://t.co/OIp7vHyc</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Field of 68 update from @ryan_fagan: A good night for Colorado State, Texas and N.C. State. Sorry, Northwestern - http://t.co/321Ch5VJ</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cincinnati knocks off Georgetown, 72-70. More to come from @ryan_fagan shortly on http://t.co/SsRfxVlB after that 2 OT thriller.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Be sure to follow @ryan_fagan for updates from the Big East tourney which currently has Cincinnati and Georgetown headed to overtime, 54-54.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Suspended Auburn player at center of point-shaving probe - http://t.co/pQWSfS05</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ex-Tigers soccer player/homecoming queen @MoIsom89's quest to make LSU football team a story of hope - http://t.co/kZAvIsKL</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wisconsin recruiting Maryland transfer QB Danny O'Brien, writes @Matt_HayesSN - http://t.co/mWYEgFwB</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Syracuse knocks Connecticut out of Big East Tournament. Get @ryan_fagan's quick take on the early game at MSG - http://t.co/cJtlrz4J</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LeBron James, Dwyane Wade recruit Peyton Manning to play for Miami Dolphins - http://t.co/nszge0FI</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lakers players reportedly want to bring back triangle offense - http://t.co/hmd55v6Q</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wednesday's auto bids: LIU (http://t.co/1grV3iaB), Lehigh (http://t.co/FtnI5lfH) and Montana (http://t.co/B4FmtJX5) #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Russ Smith is involved in everything, which is great for Louisville, writes @ryan_fagan - http://t.co/TkfYdJYW #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jose Canseco banned from Mexican League over doping claim; slugger insists on Twitter (@JoseCanseco) he's clean - http://t.co/KaPbWc73</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If you can only watch game around lunch, which are you picking: UConn/Syracuse (noon ET) or Baylor/Kansas State (12:30 ET)? #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With more bids handed out and more bubbles bursting, @ryan_fagan updates his Field of 68 - http://t.co/dLTV9jxW #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The crucible: A year later, Max Pacioretty (@MaxPacioretty67), NHL changed by Chara hit. A story by @jessespector - http://t.co/GEnpMjSK</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A little bit of #BracketInsanity at The Garden as @ryan_fagan watches UConn advance. Play SN's bracket game now: http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Packers QB Aaron Rodgers surprises Miss America at Bucks game - http://t.co/JcxYPpgA</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Police recover Paternoville marker, expect charges - http://t.co/jqJSL4JG</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>If you aren't lucky enough to be watching the Big East tourney right now, let @ryan_fagan take you to the Garden. He's there, tweeting.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>On the @sn_nfl video page, we've got a number of highlights from today's news conference. Watch them here - http://t.co/1ntal9Xv</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>While you listen to Peyton Manning's news conference, get nostalgic with this gallery of Manning through the years - http://t.co/D7Ha4ADx</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did you catch Kobe Bryant's mask last night? Must-see photo if you missed it - http://t.co/LHWSow51</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@MortChristenson It's around, just in a different form! Two ways to get it: http://t.co/jNnfvfho or on iPad at http://t.co/Aor0epfz</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After you check out @ryan_fagan's latest Field of 68, don't forget to start your #BracketInsanity group - http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Late last night, @ryan_fagan updated his Field of 68 as a few bubble teams stepped up with wins - http://t.co/JjBTTHtS #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>With Peyton Manning's expected release at noon, @CliftonBrownSN tackles the important question: Where will the QB land? http://t.co/gtsx99E0</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Where will Peyton Manning land if he leaves the Indianapolis Colts? Seven possible destinations http://t.co/OLxff33E</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why was @AntDavis23 SN's Player of the Year? @tsnmike explains his choice in this video with @njcoz - http://t.co/B2VHhdWH</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@FletcherKTBS That's actually part of what Moss brings to the table as a receiver: his Bedazzler.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>When you sign up for #BracketInsanity, you're asked who this year's Cinderella will be, so who's your pick? http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Chris Bosh returns to Miami Heat after grandmother's funeral - http://t.co/66MWKePc</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Randy Moss reportedly dazzles Saints at workout, according to @JayGlazer - http://t.co/jErB9pep</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In case you missed the noon tipoff, Connecticut beats DePaul 81-67 - http://t.co/1ui8Vjdr</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's a new No. 1 atop @RUSSLANDE's draft board. Move over Andrew Luck, make room for RG3 - http://t.co/8SycJTj0</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Drew Brees called out by former Saints player on bounty issue - http://t.co/hu8ksTUt</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cash for big hits under Gregg Williams with Washington Redskins - http://t.co/JLKkxyI8</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Patrick Ewing, Clyde Lovellette, Phil Ford among those who will enter National Collegiate Basketball Hall of Fame - http://t.co/tyYtTVFS</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Charles Barkley, Cedric Maxwell: Bounties were part of NBA, too - http://t.co/lnaD2jG3</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What happens when @CrossmanMatt takes @Braves closer Craig Kimbrel to dinner @PFChangs? You get this conversation - http://t.co/PMCmt647</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LSU women's soccer player Mo Isom to try out for football team - http://t.co/8XQ4CHjR</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sidney Crosby symptom-free, cleared for contact - http://t.co/ouWTewC1</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Make sure you follow @ryan_fagan for updates from the Garden as the Big East tourney starts ... now. UConn vs. DePaul up first.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@AntDavis23 wins POY, @CoachBillSelf wins COY. Get SN's awards: http://t.co/Uz6ftWi5 Then play #BracketInsanity: http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Before today's games start, be sure to check out @ryan_fagan's latest field of 68 - http://t.co/NHc89LpU</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Complete SN First Team All-Americans: @AntDavis23, @Money23Green, @Jared_Sully0, @Trobinson0, @SiP03 - http://t.co/xZC0cym3 #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SN's player of the year is @UKAthleticsNews' Anthony Davis @AntDavis23. @tsnmike has more on @UKCoachCalipari's star - http://t.co/B2VHhdWH</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's award day in college hoops. @KU_Hoops' @CoachBillSelf is SN's Coach of the Year. Find out why from @tsnmike - http://t.co/Vb6EHiXW</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watching conference championships tonight? Take notes of your Cinderellas and start a #BracketInsanity group now - http://t.co/To0IFndi</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Syracuse violated its drug policy with at least 10 players since 2001 - http://t.co/JvCKo030</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Plea withdrawal denied, Dykstra facing four years in prison - http://t.co/0qGJ14Cq</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kentucky again a runaway No. 1. Syracuse, Kansas still No. 2/3 - http://t.co/XwdLeTSi</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The @FantasySourceBB crew has a daily newsletter to get you ahead of owners in your league. Have you signed up yet? http://t.co/8GKygWn1</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gregg Williams to meet with NFL in bounties scandal - http://t.co/zPXvuX8x</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@officialajhawk no longer has his lengthy hair. Find out why it's gone. (Hint: It's for a really good cause) - http://t.co/XohgMmgD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Red Sox clubhouse sex abuse scandal grows - http://t.co/rHy48AvI</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>SN's @tsnmike sits down with @UKCoachCalipari, who says: 'I've got maybe the best job in basketball' - http://t.co/6BHeFVzX #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@apuestaentodo First game that comes to mind recently is Kobe's 61 against the Knicks in '09.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Meanwhile, @SeanDeveney was on hand for Rajon Rondo's incredible triple-double amid a week of trade talk - http://t.co/WyWU7guX</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It was an incredible night for point guards in the NBA. Deron Williams dropped a franchise-record 57 for the Nets - http://t.co/o2PLFVqz</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Arian Foster, Houston Texans agree to five-year contract - http://t.co/wf1whEwF</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Track the automatic bids this week here - http://t.co/J63S2BlC And set up your #BracketInsanity group now - http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did you see @ashevilledogs @MSURacers @gocreighton @BelmontMBB get their bids? Will any cause #BracketInsanity? http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rockies pitcher Alex White faces DUI charge http://t.co/wIq1BJSk</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>There's just one week until Selection Sunday. Have you signed up for #BracketInsanity? Set up your group: http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Donald Sterling allegedly consulted prostitute on Clippers basketball issues http://t.co/j5BZ53Yb</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>NFL investigation reports ex-Saints coordinator Williams ran bounty program. $1K for cart-off, $1.5K for &quot;knockout&quot; - http://t.co/07yszxAi</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@sleuth Thanks. We're working hard to backfill with some great pieces of our history.</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ex-Bronco Perrish Cox acquitted of sexual assault -http://bit.ly/yfKyQu</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's official: MLB expands playoff field to 10 teams with addition of two wild cards - http://t.co/5612CeLT</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Deion Sanders' wife sues former football star for $200 million - http://t.co/tEBlhF5B</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Don Garber: Orlando now on MLS' expansion radar - http://t.co/fsjOG5iz</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Southern Illinois fires hoops coach Chris Lowery - http://t.co/HT8b7KdD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Knaus surprised and saddened by penalties levied by NASCAR - http://t.co/DLogm6Vr</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Allen Iverson not broke, after all - http://t.co/sJw5nJoW</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@SeanDeveney is at #SSAC where he wrote about the presentation of a research paper on buildling an NBA winner - http://t.co/sunpq3BC</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch: Devin Setoguchi's shootout fail - http://t.co/5DwLFq8U</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who's ready for spring football? Check out previews for the BCS conferences from @Matt_HayesSN and @SN_Greenberg - http://t.co/tKPnoxYM</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We've been getting a number of questions about the MLB Yearbook, so we posted a reminder about the change in things - http://t.co/RIcsGc6z</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Start your day w/ some MLB nostalgia &amp; check out these archived Street and Smith's covers (also on our FB Timeline) - http://t.co/Wa6DYOsQ</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In honor of our game's launch (play here: http://t.co/63FJxhTD), we want your March Madness title pick. Tag it #BracketInsanity</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's March and we're ready for Madness. Sign up for our #BracketInsanity game. Set up groups, invite friends - http://t.co/63FJxhTD</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. Olympic team establishes itself as CONCACAF favorite, writes @BrianStraus - http://t.co/VkO2WUZs</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fantasy baseball 2012: Time to prep for your draft with the @FantasyFastball crew. Get everything you need - http://t.co/QlEfkMRh</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Peyton Hillis reportedly contemplated retirement, CIA career - http://t.co/OOC8ssgq</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Just in time for your lunch consumption: @RUSSLANDE's first post-NFL Combine Mock Draft. Lots of big moves - http://t.co/KMLiEJQi</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Luke Scott admittedly took pleasure in Red Sox’s pain last season - http://t.co/Q7auipB5</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bobby Valentine admits error in criticism of Yankees - http://t.co/LuDuHrIg</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In an interview with @sportsguy33, Obama says he knew about Jeremy Lin before everyone else - http://t.co/2GhmUrj7</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Do you agree with @tsnmike's take on March Madness or are you on @Matt_HayesSN's side of the argument?</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Our first post-Combine NFL mock draft from @RUSSLANDE will be live shortly. Who do you think made the biggest jump in Indy? #nfldraft</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You got a temporary reprieve from #Linsanity, but he was back at it with 19 points/13 assists vs. the Cavs last night - http://t.co/ebv1bgxq</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's the end of an area: The Steelers are letting Hines Ward go. Should he retire or move on to another team? http://t.co/6sC5IkGA</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kobe Bryant cleared to play, leads Lakers to rout of T-wolves. Did you see his mask last night? http://t.co/6YA9VzRN</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>President Barack Obama gives college football playoff thumbs up - http://t.co/ALNOHAra</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>U.S. beats Italy, 1-0. Be sure to check out @BrianStraus' feed for additional analysis - http://t.co/cpl6LLhl</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Top hoops recruit Shabazz Muhammad (@phenom15balla) visiting Duke next, says no clear leader - http://t.co/bq57uzzg</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>San Diego TV anchor suspended for derogatory Danica Patrick comment - http://t.co/CMCuEHY5</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@SeanDeveney's latest mock draft is live. The No. 1 pick to the @bobcats? @AntDavis23 - http://t.co/4kAJLaC7</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Name change: Marlins’ Mike Stanton now known as Giancarlo Stanton - http://t.co/zI9aJrDw</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Today, Facebook rolled out &quot;Timeline&quot; for Pages. We've added the 10 greatest performances ever (on the right side) - http://t.co/IeLp6hGg</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>MLB to announce 2012 playoff expansion on Thursday - http://t.co/AMvICvUF</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Derek Jeter, Alex Rodriguez respond to Bobby Valentine’s criticism - http://t.co/0LH0ojzL</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Which QB would you rather have: Peyton Manning or Matt Flynn? @vinnieiyer's answer might surprise you - http://t.co/LXGzuEw6</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gary Bettman rips Bryant Gumbel for David Stern comments - http://t.co/udr8nIxR</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Report: Saints likely to use franchise tag on Drew Brees if long-term deal can't be reached by Monday - http://t.co/NyeQFK0C</text>
    <name>Sporting News</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>