<tweets>
<tweets class="java.util.ArrayList">

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives Trial Twist: Nicollette Sheridan's Battery Claim Against Marc Cherry Thrown Out! http://t.co/c8mqW1s9</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Next Justin Bieber? One Direction on Taking Simon Cowell's Advice and Being the New...Pink? http://t.co/bz8N4EZd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Boom! Battleship's New Trailer Has Rihanna, Taylor Kitsch and Brooklyn Decker Fighting Aliens http://t.co/ndWgJzWl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Was Bachelor Ben the Worst Bachelor Ever? http://t.co/Tjh8nZQu</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Biel looks smokin' on the cover @WMag! http://t.co/KZdPcKhO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian goes blonde for a day. You like? PHOTO: http://t.co/4lI14FwL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bye-Bye, Bear Grylls! Discovery Terminates Relationship With Man vs. Wild Star http://t.co/r85R1XTn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennie Garth and Peter Facinelli Split! http://t.co/o0JpcKZZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Breaking! Jennie Garth and Peter Facinelli Split! http://t.co/Y3CkKCJs</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Christina Aguilera Teases Adam Levine About Past Celebrity Fragrance Diss http://t.co/eWPdPoH2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Faith Hill Skips Makeup, Goes Au Naturel! http://t.co/Uf5xcITs</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>One Direction’s debut album &quot;Up All Night&quot; went straight to #1 and #2 on iTunes album chart today!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ryan Gosling as Walt Disney? Fake Movie Poster Spawns Very Real Desire http://t.co/Ydds5D3o</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why Are Channing Tatum and Jonah Hill Talking About Matthew McConaughey's &quot;Exceptional Junk&quot;? http://t.co/7qgTvo1t</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Beyoncé Takes Baby Blue Ivy Out for a Stroll http://t.co/nngvdZc1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lea Michele &amp; Cory Monteith: Real-Life Romance on the Rocks? http://t.co/or8jnZV4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Liam Hemsworth &amp; @MileyCyrus at the #HungerGames premiere! PHOTO: http://t.co/2N48HSac</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are Bachelor's Ben Flajnik and Courtney Robertson Still Together Now?! http://t.co/xVZHfHRP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Kristin Cavallari Rocks a One-Piece in Cabo! PHOTO: http://t.co/wGG6Mu6V</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Shiloh Jolie-Pitt rocks tuxedo shirt! So cute! PHOTO: http://t.co/Mss6HSws</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Biel flaunts her GIANT engagement ring at a Lakers game! PHOTO: http://t.co/L8xYgROd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zahara Jolie-Pitt rocks blue hair during her day out with Angelina! PHOTO: http://t.co/VzwdcF7r</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check Out Kristen Stewart as Vampire Bella in Breaking Dawn—Part 2! http://t.co/AzOaqVRl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tina, Beyonce &amp; Blue Ivy = 3 generations of awesome laides! PHOTOS: http://t.co/zWj3FBbM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Glee's Heather Morris Nude Pics Hit Web, Apparently Leaked by Phone Hackers http://t.co/SpLh8xue</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rihanna bares exposed breasts in racy, see-through top! PHOTO: http://t.co/mPcX5RQT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do you think of Elizabeth Banks neon minidress? PHOTO: http://t.co/poKuSZe8 #hungergames</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Selena Gomez is a party girl on the set of her new movie! PHOTO: http://t.co/XRiDH9bs</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Liam Hemsworth &amp; @MileyCyrus at the #HungerGames premiere! PHOTO: http://t.co/2N48HSac</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Lawrence Talks Hunger Games Premiere Jitters: &quot;I Feel Like a Shaking Chihuahua&quot; http://t.co/BXPngVic</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Are Bachelor's Ben Flajnik and Courtney Robertson Still Together Now?! http://t.co/SwqhnLIg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Miley Cyrus Talks Hunger Games: &quot;The Hardest Part for Liam Was Being Away From Me!&quot; http://t.co/Efry3dPq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Voice Recap: Second Battle Round Gives Gritty, Emotional and Powerful Performances http://t.co/FEwOWYWC</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Bachelor Finale: Courtney or Lindzi? Who Did Ben Really Pick?! http://t.co/9KHZzYCK</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What do you think of Jennifer Lawrence's gold Prabal Gurung #HungerGames dress? http://t.co/RCgMg8MX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Liam Hemsworth (in D&amp;G) and Miley Cyrus (in Pucci) make a fab couple at the #hungergames! http://t.co/NdLnvRqq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Lawrence is glittering in gold Prabal Gurung! You like? #HungerGames</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now chatting with Jennifer Lawrence at the #HungerGames premiere! http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Miley Cyrus is rocking skimpy Pucci at the #HungerGames premiere! http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Now chatting with Josh Hutcherson at the #HungerGames premiere! http://t.co/vSV9vyVt http://t.co/eGG7mjjz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Madonna Shares Photos of Bruises, Cuts and a Fat Lip! http://t.co/SKAUcKAr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Elizabeth Banks in neon Versace is talking to us now! WATCH: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames #ERedCarpet</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check out @ElizabethBanks' little red dress! What do you think: http://t.co/Hq4JdQfs? WATCH: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones' Family Brings Singer's Ashes to Private Memorial in England http://t.co/JNRSKgTm</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're about to interview @ElizabethBanks, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth &amp; Jennifer Lawrence any minute! http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're talking to Cody Simpson at the Hunger Games premiere now! #Eredcarpet #HungerGames http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Donald Sutherland on Jennifer Lawrence: &quot;She should change her name to Jennifer Lawrence Olivier&quot; http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're talking to Donald Sutherland at the Hunger Games premiere! #Eredcarpet #HungerGames http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Kristin Cavallari Rocks a One-Piece in Cabo http://t.co/wGG6Mu6V</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>OMG! Rue (@amandlastenberg) is so CUTE! Watch: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames #ERedCarpet</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Isabelle Fuhrman's sparkly Oscar De La Renta dress is so cute! WATCH: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames #ERedCarpet</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fun fact! Jennifer Lawrence's #HungerGames mom already played her mom in the TV show Cold Case! WATCH: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #Eredcarpet</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kalia Prescott is decidedly Team Peeta! No hesitation. Watch live: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames http://t.co/29hwpFzF</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Robert Pattinson's Bel Ami Set to Steam Up Summer (Watch Out, Kristen Stewart!) http://t.co/n0dEvKgo</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're chatting up Portia at the #HungerGames premiere! Watch live: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #ERedCarpet http://t.co/FeQCUoML</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>District 8 Tribute Sam Tan and his hot brother are the first to arrive! Watch live: http://t.co/vSV9vyVt #HungerGames http://t.co/AabB2d1Q</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Hunger Games Premiere Live Red Carpet Begins! Who Looks Great? http://t.co/n14pb7Sq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who are you most excited to see on the Hunger Games black carpet tonight?! #Eredcarpet #HungerGames http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And we're LIVE at the Hunger Games premiere! #Eredcarpet #HungerGames http://t.co/vSV9vyVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Heidi Klum and Denise Richards Help Daughters Sell Girl Scout Cookies http://t.co/P92wMpwk</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Look who we'll be seeing at the #HungerGames premiere! RT @KrisJenner:  U two look gorge!! http://t.co/qy9fJ6FO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In less than an hour we'll be live on http://t.co/lnEx8u1q at the #HungerGames premiere! http://t.co/HEop6j7E</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Cover-Up?! Does Voicemail Expose New Information in Nicollette Sheridan's Case? http://t.co/nNFcXvbG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Donald Trump's Sons Defend Killing Animals on African Safari: We Have &quot;Utmost Respect for Nature&quot; http://t.co/TUWGnkbn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>@mandymayekawa Yep! Starting in just an hour and a half!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>We're just a couple hours away from the #HungerGames premiere! Tweet us your questions for the cast and we'll ask them on the #ERedCarpet!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nina Dobrev looks so cute at PaleyFest! PHOTO: http://t.co/nHhW8I3t #TVD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Blake Lively and Ryan Reynolds: What Did They Pack for a Picnic Together? Lotsa PDA! http://t.co/zYWHDJXy</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Biel flaunts her GIANT engagement ring at a Lakers game! PHOTO: http://t.co/L8xYgROd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian Responds to Jon Hamm's Slam http://t.co/rFlwy8NF</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First Look: Check Out Kristen Stewart as Vampire Bella in Breaking Dawn—Part 2! http://t.co/AzOaqVRl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check Out Josh Duhamel's Brand-New Mohawk—Do You Like? http://t.co/CLnf1o9o</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: New Glee Character With a Rocky Past! Plus New Girl, Vampire Diaries and More! http://t.co/jY3bGjaW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Emma Stone &amp; Andrew Garfield sneak a kiss on the streets of NYC! PHOTO: http://t.co/mENyQfd4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Glee's Heather Morris Nude Pics Hit Web, Apparently Leaked by Phone Hackers http://t.co/SpLh8xue</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>In 5 hours we'll be LIVE from the #HungerGames premiere! Are you ready?! #ERedCarpet http://t.co/jRWimau1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mega Feud Alert! Piers Morgan Rips Madonna and Kate Moss—Who's &quot;Vile&quot; and Who's a &quot;Con Artist&quot;? http://t.co/bc9jqUrv</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zahara Jolie-Pitt Rocks Blue Hair During Day Out With Angelina http://t.co/VzwdcF7r</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Lawrence and Lenny Kravitz's Hunger Games Prep: Hand-to-Hand Combat and Gold Eye Shadow? http://t.co/GZXCcZd8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Aniston and Justin Theroux Land in L.A. http://t.co/GziZf5c7</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tonight we are Live From the #ERedCarpet at the #HungerGames premiere with @iamCattSadler &amp; @AshlanGorse! It all starts at 8 ET / 5 PT!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How Liam Hemsworth and Josh Hutcherson Became Hunger Games Hunks! http://t.co/Vm9AVEWP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rihanna Dares to Bare Exposed Breasts in Racy, See-Through Top http://t.co/mPcX5RQT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eva Longoria Suffers Dance Injury on Desperate Housewives Set http://t.co/KscJJGOE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Justin Bieber Dead? Nah, Just Twitter's Latest Hoax Victim http://t.co/4bfxEzSs</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Demi Lovato Lashes Out at Cyberbullies: &quot;Must Suck to Be Born Without a Heart&quot; http://t.co/UNx0vZjr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry Dishes on the Royal Family: Queen Elizabeth Is Funny! http://t.co/x0FNUFuK</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Weekend Wrap-Up: Halle Berry Engagement Confirmed, Marie Osmond Laughs Off Accident http://t.co/fCotJJzQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives' Biggest Surprise Ever: Find Out Who Died—and How! http://t.co/wQJ0uHxq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Revenge: A &quot;Major&quot; Death, a Wedding and a Love-Triangle Deal Breaker?! Spoilers From the Cast! http://t.co/ZTFw8eeL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>West Coast! Tune in NOW for all-new episodes of @Khloe_Lamar and @IceLovesCoco!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Leonardo DiCaprio Gets Social at SXSW http://t.co/lsGk1JF1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Khloé &amp; Lamar Recap: The Trouble With Turkey? http://t.co/2CsBJEZW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston's Daughter Bobbi Kristina Tells Oprah Winfrey: I Have to Carry on My Mom's Legacy http://t.co/MYupYqt8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrity Apprentice Boardroom Shocker! Donald Trump Does a Double Take http://t.co/FSju28Ki</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Walking Dead Blows Our Minds With Most Colossal Shocker Yet http://t.co/BNSGjRx4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>East Coast! Tune in NOW for all-new episodes of @Khloe_Lamar and @IceLovesCoco!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Curly Sue Child Star Alisan Porter Gets Married http://t.co/cqvTtHdS</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Revenge: Daniel's in Danger and Four Other Things to Know About the Show's April Return! http://t.co/q8YZQoVt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Marie Osmond Laughed So Hard During Performance...She Peed Herself on Stage! http://t.co/9eN0tQis</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Patrick Schwarzenegger Recovering After Minor Ski Accident http://t.co/EFsFDZcr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Matthew McConaughey Moves Back to Texas: Is He Done With Hollywood? http://t.co/blaGTu2A</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did Eddie Murphy's A Thousand Words Bomb Bigger Than John Carter? http://t.co/M8eBpQ1z</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Vampire Diaries: Five Things to Expect From Thursday's Epic &quot;1912&quot;! http://t.co/74lc0ujD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jonah Hill Pokes Fun at His Oscar Nom, Acts Like a Six-Year-Old on Saturday Night Live http://t.co/D7YoQ7wn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will The Hunger Games Be Better Than Twilight? http://t.co/QYHFx9dU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>It's Official! Olivier Martinez Confirms Engagement to Halle Berry, Clears Up Ring Rumors http://t.co/CTm24rkb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart Goes Topless in On the Road Trailer http://t.co/7xB9k66h</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry Runs for Charity in Rio...and Pokes Fun at Bro Prince William During the Race http://t.co/NOJUhEJT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coco is on a health kick, but will Ice get on board? Find out on a new @IceLovesCoco tomorrow at 10:30/9:30c! http://t.co/ohEN3AeM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Meryl Streep Breaks Out Oscar to Introduce &quot;Real Deal&quot; Hillary Clinton at Women in the World Summit http://t.co/mwdSXT6v</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Madsen Busted for Child Cruelty http://t.co/BkeXoVnw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Lamar play basketball out of the country? Find out on an all-new @Khloe_Lamar, tomorrow, 10/9c! Sneak peek: http://t.co/GvxNDwBk</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Andy liked our idea! RT @royalefataIe: @bravoandy Can we bring back Dina to #RHONJ in last chance housewife? #sxswbybravo</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Fashion Police's Guess Me From Behind: Spring Break Slacker http://t.co/WoyP56VU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brad Pitt's Tale: &quot;Incredibly Sweet,&quot; Says Costar http://t.co/Bk1CJRNK</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Week in Review: Kirk Cameron Confounds, Pregnant Snooki Engaged, Pregnant Jessica Simpson Gets Naked! http://t.co/4wSGdRzR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bruce Springsteen Raises the Roof at the Apollo; First Show Since Clarence Clemons' Death http://t.co/Z84ctvbH</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Week in Pictures: Globetrotting With Prince Harry, Sarah Jessica Parker, Taylor Swift, Meryl Streep &amp; More! http://t.co/ESo5GflP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mayday, Mayday! Love Boat Cruise Ship Headed to Scrap Yard http://t.co/YJ2AvCK8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol's Jeremy Rosado: &quot;Jennifer Lopez Told Me She Wanted to Keep Me!&quot; http://t.co/s6E6pgJF</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Coolio and Son Locked Up in Same Las Vegas Jail! http://t.co/tcedxy6C</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ray J Talks Whitney Houston's Death: &quot;I'm Able to Look at Life in a Whole Different Way&quot; http://t.co/PUxYKsY1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is Lamar leaving the country to play basketball? Find out how on a new @Khloe_Lamar, Sunday at 10/9c! http://t.co/GvxNDwBk</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Hunger Games Boy Battle! Are You Team Peeta or Team Gale? http://t.co/72g4PoBz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Final Stop: Prince Harry Touches Down in Rio http://t.co/no6w0ts1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston: Hairstylist Talks Seeing Singer in Hotel Room, Comforting Bobbi Kristina http://t.co/7uJ93eLa</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Ice get on board with Coco's new health kick? Find out on a new @IceLovesCoco, Sunday 10:30/9:30c! VIDEO: http://t.co/ohEN3AeM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Salty Language, SAMCRO's Struggles and Season Five Scoop: Sons of Anarchy at PaleyFest http://t.co/AmB3CBsb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Notorious B.I.G.: Sean &quot;Diddy&quot; Combs, Li'l Kim and More Pay Tribute on 15th Anniversary of His Death http://t.co/0A6fH2nU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Madonna's &quot;Girl Gone Wild&quot; Teaser: Watch Now! http://t.co/uRJHLoW5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Harry Potter Author J.K. Rowling's Billionaire Status Disapparates http://t.co/12W4MteS</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A looks back at Eddie Murphy's best roles! PHOTOS: http://t.co/ep6B8vK5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives Producer: Nicollette Sheridan Was &quot;Emotional,&quot; Late &quot;50 Percent of the Time&quot; http://t.co/QTXdenuv</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ex–Queens of the Stone Age Bassist Pleads Not Guilty in SWAT Standoff http://t.co/AkWFahdI</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Movie Review: John Carter Is Way Better Than It Looks http://t.co/AXC06Dl4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dick Van Dyke on his new 40-year-old wife: &quot;I'm not a loner. I have to have a life partner. I found the perfect one.&quot; http://t.co/hh8EAoYm</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cameron Diaz the New Face of Tag Heuer Watches—Check Out Her First Ad! http://t.co/W7HX7RHj</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>15 years after Notorious B.I.G.'s death, his music still lives on: http://t.co/LcJh2UBf #RIPBIG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dick Van Dyke Marries His 40-Year-Old Makeup Artist http://t.co/Y3sN1zT0</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Colin Firth Racks Up Another Old-Timey Acting Honor http://t.co/uqSf9hJP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>John Mayer's Granumola Returns, Singer Taking &quot;Indefinite Break From Live Perfoming&quot; http://t.co/5VQlZSTf</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So Much for the Right Stuff: Dennis Quaid and Wife Divorcing http://t.co/4ax0mp1u</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Now: Rihanna Strips Down for New Armani Jeans Ad http://t.co/WZJM0O9z</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Scout Willis' Scandalous, TMI Tweets Were &quot;Hoax&quot; for School Project http://t.co/444dOHxQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Martha Stewart Welcomes Her Second Grandchild! http://t.co/pbhRidfC</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Biel Finally Shows Off Her Massive Engagement Ring With Justin Timberlake! http://t.co/vobyqqDR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>South by Southwest: Five Things to Know About the Texan Film Festival http://t.co/6FVUtWVx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Carrie's Sex and the City Townhouse on Sale for Big Bucks http://t.co/PcKeXw81</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Heidi Klum Opens Up About Split With Seal: &quot;I Feel Like I'm in the Eye of the Tornado&quot; http://t.co/UWkS8HiE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hunger Games: Five Things You Need to Know About the Making of the Movie http://t.co/qeUYbOQM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: A New Girl Romance Twist! Plus Gossip Girl, Bones, The Office and More! http://t.co/noXz4Q30</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan Is a Redhead Again—Do You Like? PHOTO: http://t.co/Fs7ulADf</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Well Zac Efron is looking EXTRA handsome today! PHOTO: http://t.co/9UhMFVtf</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rihanna Topless in New Twitpic: Check It Out! http://t.co/o1OOD6MR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hangover 3: Still Nothing Official! http://t.co/duqLL4P9</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart Rocks Sexy Mini for Paris Date Night! (With Robert Pattinson, of Course) http://t.co/3qJVlZAc</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Russell Brand Wears Deep V-Neck, Katy Perry Got Out Just in Time http://t.co/dZmgui7I</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki's Engagement: Details on Her Custom $55,000 Ring and How Jionni Proposed! http://t.co/IfaLClGW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Johnny Depp in 21 Jump Street Movie: &quot;Even the Crew on Set Didn't Recognize Him!&quot; http://t.co/BtdgdrBX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#Glee Is Shooting a Full-Episode Tribute to Whitney Houston! http://t.co/JhU8Qxun</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Trial: Eva Longoria and Other Housewives Will Not Take the Stand http://t.co/ZbeGh3Q1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan Is a Redhead Again—Do You Like? http://t.co/Fs7ulADf</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol Elimination: Who Lost the Battle of the Sexes? http://t.co/TJBch42y</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eva Longoria and Eduardo Cruz: It's Over http://t.co/ZCX2yKyT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Seeing @LindsayLohan go back to red hair feels like such a victory for all of us! http://t.co/qlalLsfr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki and Jessica Simpson: How Much Money Will They Make Off of Their Babies? http://t.co/jHH2gCFM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sneak Peek! Whitney Houston's Family Talks to Oprah: &quot;The Handwriting Was on the Wall&quot; http://t.co/mYn67hIq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives Spoiler Bomb: Major Character Getting Killed Off This Sunday! (Find Out Who!) http://t.co/VtfxUVhh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Curses! American Idol's Phil Phillips Rushed to the Hospital http://t.co/uu2ktBkq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hulk Hogan Sex Tape a Best-Seller? Adult Video Honcho Thinks It Could Be! http://t.co/meq8HphA</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Well Zac Efron is looking EXTRA handsome today! http://t.co/AG7Biiyx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sooo cute! RT @LaurenConrad: Just fell in love... http://t.co/BGSlUjrE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Love Hewitt: Which Body Part Does She Say Has &quot;Always Served Me Well?&quot; http://t.co/0m1x6ZjP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives' Marc Cherry: I &quot;Tapped&quot; the Side of Nicollette Sheridan's Head http://t.co/yflh68qe</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brad Pitt's New Orleans Charity Gala Will Feature Rihanna, Sean Penn, Sheryl Crow and More http://t.co/iFQPeWTi</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>.@JustinBieber's Auctioned-Off Pet Snake Gets New Home—But Winning Bidder Is Spewing Venom http://t.co/uMZSabtJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Voice's Adam Levine Launching Men and Women's Fragrances! http://t.co/YKXxULjC</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart Rocks Sexy Mini for Paris Date Night! (With Robert Pattinson, of Course) http://t.co/3qJVlZAc</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rihanna Topless in New Twitpic: Check It Out! http://t.co/o1OOD6MR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Megan Fox: Tattoo Removal Is &quot;Incredibly Painful&quot; http://t.co/sFxPyc2U</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston's Final Conversation With Dionne Warwick: &quot;She Had Everything in the World to Live For&quot; http://t.co/dwMZWPHw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>She's got that #ShilohSwag! http://t.co/XeRfSwQF</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston's Will and Five Other Last Wishes of the Stars http://t.co/4dR95lsj</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>First Look: Johnny Depp and Armie Hammer in The Lone Ranger http://t.co/3nAKUED0</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mila Kunis is perfection. Always! (photos by @Terry_World) http://t.co/ye3K4V4F</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Teen Mom's Amber Portwood Denies Missing Drug Test and Violating Probation http://t.co/QpS6aHuS</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 2 teaser trailer will debut in
theaters with The Hunger Games March 23!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Emma Roberts Debuts Darker 'Do: Bye-Bye, Blond! http://t.co/pTyiOpxp</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check out Johnny Depp as Tonto and Armie Hammer as the Lone Ranger! Are you excited?! http://t.co/C3Nz5RsW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Robert Pattinson &amp; Kristen Stewart leave Paris together. PHOTO: http://t.co/UTHVZXEN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones' Daughters &quot;Greatly Comforted&quot; by Fans' &quot;Support and Love&quot; http://t.co/kr1s5thK</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Giuliana Rancic Returns to Host Miss USA Competition! http://t.co/bjjXH8et</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kate Middleton Helps the Queen Kick Off Her Diamond Jubilee in Style http://t.co/IUxVutE3</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: Is Justin Bieber Coming to How I Met Your Mother? Plus, Death on a CW Favorite! http://t.co/PI6P1Wfr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki's Baby Daddy: Five Things to Know About Her Fiancé Jionni LaValle http://t.co/2UozWXPj</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Suffering for Fashion: Kate Moss Billboard Crashes Down on Pedestrians, Sends Them to Hospital http://t.co/qdOCkwJd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ali Fedotowsky Breaks Silence on Split From Roberto: &quot;We Were Unhappy More Than We Were Happy&quot; http://t.co/zPHe7oLU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki's Engagement: Details on Her Custom $55,000 Ring and How Jionni Proposed! http://t.co/IfaLClGW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Before The Hunger Games: Pay Tribute to These Killer Flicks http://t.co/YlKE7uq8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston's Will: Everything Goes to Daughter Bobbi Kristina http://t.co/i02yyVTg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Simpson isn't the only celeb to go naked preggers. See Christina Aguilera, Britney Spears and more! PHOTOS: http://t.co/PIzY559s</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brad and Angelina's kids make dog-walking look badass! You gotta see Shiloh's swag! PHOTO: http://t.co/xTXgTxTz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How cute is baby Adele? PHOTO: http://t.co/MJeRFQTn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ashley Olsen Will Never Act Again: &quot;I Don't Have to Be a Pretty Face&quot; http://t.co/sgxLTPC1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki Defended: &quot;It's Not Like She's 16 and Pregnant,&quot; Says Jersey Shore Costar http://t.co/MoVm0bW4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Jessica Simpson Poses Nude—Plans &quot;Nontraditional&quot; Name for Baby Girl http://t.co/CNLX5ek9</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol's Top 13 on Performing Whitney and Stevie! Plus, Who &quot;Can't Stand&quot; Each Other? http://t.co/xhm9vjcx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ali Lohan Chops Off Her Hair—Check It Out! http://t.co/dBEp3B8m</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian + Kanye West = Besties! PHOTO: http://t.co/7Za8ubqq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Marni for @HM prelaunch madness w/ @e_fashionpolice host @georgekotsi! #MarniatHM http://t.co/Yys6EJHy</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart works her leopard-print minidress! PHOTO: http://t.co/7hxXImoM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Survivor: One World Insider: The &quot;Single Dumbest Move Ever in This Game&quot;...and the Biggest Bigot http://t.co/dGyuBVIQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check out that #ShilohSwag! http://t.co/rDxK7CV4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sandra Bullock and Brett Ratner Slam Hookup Rumors http://t.co/9MFpQXbi</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol Recap: Ladies Sing Whitney Houston—Who Dared to Do &quot;I Will Always Love You&quot;?! http://t.co/9DPmPt03</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Felicity Huffman Reacts to Desperate Housewives Trial, Gets Hollywood Star With William H. Macy http://t.co/ZlETspAt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Cute Alert! Brad and Angelina's Kids Make Dog-Walking Look Cool http://t.co/xTXgTxTz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki's Engagement: Details on Her Custom Ring and How Jionni Proposed! http://t.co/IfaLClGW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston's Will: Everything Goes to Daughter Bobbi Kristina http://t.co/i02yyVTg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kanye West Banishes Fashion Editors From Paris Runway Preview http://t.co/zw23oTbG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So True? So False? Is Russell Brand Moving On With Katy Perry Look-Alike Zooey Deschanel? http://t.co/L8lVeavD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki Defended: &quot;It's Not Like She's 16 and Pregnant,&quot; Says Jersey Shore Costar http://t.co/MoVm0bW4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hulk Hogan Sex Tape: Shop It at Your Own Risk http://t.co/mjsbCSl4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Parks and Recreation: Are Leslie and Ben in Trouble? Amy Poehler Drops Some (Worrisome) Scoop! http://t.co/LBCP0zUP</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan Called Teri Hatcher &quot;Meanest Woman in the World,&quot; Says Desperate Housewives' Marc Cherry http://t.co/zKc4Kuu5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rush Limbaugh Boycott Rocked as Canadian Band Rush Pulls Music From Show http://t.co/VIekZUnd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Christie Brinkley Fires Back, Claiming Ex-Husband Peter Cook's Allegations Are &quot;Delusional&quot; http://t.co/CEO6l8My</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Simpson isn't the only celeb to go naked preggers. See Christina Aguilera, Britney Spears and more! PHOTOS: http://t.co/PIzY559s</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ashley Olsen Will Never Act Again: &quot;I Don't Have to Be a Pretty Face&quot; http://t.co/sgxLTPC1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones to Be Cremated, Funeral Set for This Week http://t.co/GyahDgoZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Which Fashion-Challenged Pop Star's Daughter Is Rocking a Sartorial Rainbow? http://t.co/4oSUu0xQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lily Collins Talks Kristen Stewart, Snow White Rivalry http://t.co/LLpGScK8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Do you think we'll get a naked pregnant cover for Snooki like we did for Jessica Simpson? PHOTO: http://t.co/DkVSuvXm</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Tila Tequila to Enter Rehab Following Her Recent Hospitalization http://t.co/oD0D2uIO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How cute is baby Adele? PHOTO: http://t.co/MJeRFQTn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Aww! Which Grammy Winning Superstar Was Rocking Out at Age Four? http://t.co/1X85j9aO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rush Limbaugh Defended by Bill Maher in Wake of Sandra Fluke Scandal…Wait, What?! http://t.co/YP522Q8T</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jessica Simpson goes naked in @ELLEmagazine! Loves It or Too Much? http://t.co/jj3AQp4J</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki makes her pregnancy and engagement official: http://t.co/HejstYLa</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Poll: Is It Better to Be an Honest Hater (Like Kirk Cameron) or Give Good Lip Service? http://t.co/n501vC4q</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Jessica Simpson Poses Nude—Plans &quot;Nontraditional&quot; Name for Baby Girl http://t.co/CNLX5ek9</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry Takes Jamaica: Quotes Bob Marley, Hugs the PM—but What's the One Thing He Won't Do? http://eonli.ne/yZw0A5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jason Segel Naked Again! He's &quot;Happy to Get That Thing Out at All Times,&quot; Says Emily Blunt http://t.co/mN9kVL7C</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>How Hot Is The Hunger Games Cast? Check Our Their Best Red Carpet Looks http://t.co/MzT91NNg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Real Housewives' Tamra Barney Is Engaged! http://t.co/uvUjJ0HO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: A Once Upon a Time Reunion? Plus, Walking Dead, Vampire Diaries and More http://t.co/s50gbQEG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Splitsville Alert! Did David Arquette Call It Quits With Girlfriend Christina McLarty? http://t.co/ke5W4PRG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ali Lohan Chops Off Her Hair—Check It Out! http://t.co/dBEp3B8m</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mariska Hargitay Talks Hosting Saturday Night Live: I'm Funnier Than You Think! http://t.co/ZREPxKCq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Now: New Girl's Zooey Deschanel &amp; Co. Dish on Tonight's Episode! http://t.co/y61uOYKY</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki's Plans for &quot;Tight-Fitting&quot; Wedding Dress http://t.co/Sf1Jkazo</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Testimony: Death of Nicollette Sheridan's Edie Approved by ABC Months Before Fight http://t.co/9mNFgmnx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hunger Games Sneak: Watch Jennifer Lawrence's Katniss Meet Lenny Kravitz's Cinna http://t.co/VjQptz1C</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bachelor: Women Tell All Postmortem: Ashley Hebert Dishes on Courtney's Tears, Lindzi's Chances and More! http://t.co/cjqwxD6W</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Take it from @Snooki, there's nothing like a leopard-print poncho to cover a baby bump! PHOTO: http://t.co/JekBF9D8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>66-Year-Old Debbie Harry Mistaken for 25-Year-Old Lindsay Lohan by Photographers http://t.co/gbU2WwgN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones Funeral: Monkees Bandmates Not Attending Service to Avoid &quot;Media Circus&quot; http://t.co/57pDqA5W</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Why Are Stars Like Christina Hendricks and Olivia Munn Still Getting Their Phones Hacked?! http://t.co/p1BDEaW6</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Vanessa Hudgens is rocking her blonde wig for her new movie role. You like? http://t.co/0sXvw4KZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hail, Mary! Tim Tebow Wanted for The Bachelor! http://t.co/UFuZrONe</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kirk Cameron Defends Himself: &quot;I Spoke as Honestly as I Could...[I] Love All People&quot;; GLAAD Doesn't Buy It http://t.co/nr8ColGe</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So True? So False? Did Tina Fey Skip Saturday Night Live to Avoid Lindsay Lohan?! http://t.co/sawXmTnD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Do you miss sexy Megan Fox? http://t.co/kXnfWDpE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Linda Cardellini Welcomes a Baby Girl—Guess Her Pretty Name! http://t.co/xrVpCorD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Housewives Trial: Nicollette Sheridan Feared &quot;Retribution&quot; From Marc Cherry http://t.co/M6EtmM8a</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Eddie Murphy is a man of many roles. Which Eddie Murphy movie is your fave? PHOTOS: http://t.co/726Q2YVv</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Who's Favored to Win American Idol Already?! http://t.co/PqG9mMj4</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry &quot;Races&quot; Usain Bolt: Guess Who Won? http://t.co/vMsiUWMV</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Now: Nikki Reed and Paul McDonald's New Music Video—Are They Making Beautiful Music? http://t.co/Ujqlxqkz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Megan Fox goes all Taylor Swift sparkle dress on us! What do you think of this look? PHOTO: http://t.co/BnaUNMn2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Uh-Oh: What Might Terra Nova's Cancellation Mean for Other Bubble Shows? http://t.co/cNUJjAJb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ashton Kutcher Reconnects With Demi Moore After Rehab http://t.co/yGaYPVUd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alright, Prince Harry, you can just stop right now. You are the cutest. Game over. PHOTO: http://t.co/frXGyOz3</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Smash Scoop: Guess Which Surprising Star Is Going to Sing! http://t.co/UEnQHEby</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Just @ddlovato looking glam in NYC! http://t.co/oYPRZa6w</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Kirk Cameron-Rush Limbaugh Controversy Scorecard: Who's in Worse Trouble? http://t.co/DEVJfGlg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Robert B. Sherman, Legendary Disney Tunesmith Behind Mary Poppins, Dies at 86 http://t.co/Z3sowB0P</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Naked Alert! Watch Miley Cyrus Punk Her Hunger Games Boyfriend Liam Hemsworth http://t.co/KFAEK4L1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hunger Games: Catching Fire Script Delivered to Suzanne Collins! http://t.co/VxZPgAwX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Rush Limbaugh vs. Peter Gabriel: &quot;Appalled&quot; Singer Pulls Music After Sandra Fluke Rant http://t.co/pTqomxmn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: Meet the Parents on The Vampire Diaries! Plus, Revenge, Supernatural and More http://t.co/zC91JiZR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lady Gaga Surpasses Twitter Milestone—How Many Little Monsters Does She Now Have? http://t.co/bRyXE4Tg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>All About The Hunger Games! The Ultimate Guide to Who's Who in the Cast http://t.co/5bxiSoax</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki: Is Anyone Making Sure She Steers Clear of Bars? http://t.co/2ugW2kqH</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki Flashes Engagement Ring, Baby Bump Still in Hiding http://t.co/DBbYuyeN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Miley Cyrus has an interesting jogging outfit. PHOTO: http://t.co/MerrFdnO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>David &amp; Brooklyn Beckham are twinsies! PHOTO: http://t.co/WgUJDter</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Forget Angelina Jolie's right leg! Daughter Vivienne rocks some red lips on girls' day out! PHOTO: http://t.co/L52EinYh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This is what Vanessa Hudgens as a &quot;crazy party girl&quot; looks like: http://t.co/8HDoEsxl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian donates money to charity for wedding gifts received! http://t.co/e9t0XfJb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki Is Engaged! http://t.co/MBlRwJ6k</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mug Shot of the Day: Why Is Teen Mom Jenelle Evans in Jail This Time? And Should She Be Smirking? http://t.co/dlvRSD0l</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Jason Segel Return for The Muppets Sequel? http://t.co/x5MOhob2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Terra Nova Canceled by Fox...Will It Find Another Network? http://t.co/GftPKbDE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Elizabeth Berkley Pregnant With First Child! http://t.co/emr0iFaz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Voice Recap: Kelly Clarkson, Miranda Lambert and More Lend the Mentors a Hand! http://t.co/mZBRCZGA</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Bachelor: Women Tell All Special: Confronted Courtney Gives a Tearful Apology http://t.co/bSCk1rzt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ringer First Look: See Sarah Michelle Gellar as a Stripper! http://t.co/mSOj6ubh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Paula Deen and Brother Sued for Sexual Harassment by Restaurant Employee http://t.co/ivHRvaRQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Housewives Marc Cherry: Felicity Huffman and Eva Longoria &quot;Were Relieved&quot; About Sheridan's Character Leaving Show http://t.co/FxWc2CpR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Walking Dead: Get Scoop on Final Jaw-Dropping Episodes! http://t.co/V8FSjCPo</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Pippa Middleton's First On-Camera Interview! http://t.co/pyyjDthT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Desperate Trial Update: Nicollette Sheridan Gets Testy; Marc Cherry Defends Killing Off Edie http://t.co/HHBP4SlO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>David &amp; Brooklyn Beckham are twinsies! PHOTO: http://t.co/WgUJDter</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki Flashes Engagement Ring, Baby Bump Still in Hiding http://t.co/DBbYuyeN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did Whitney Houston and Jermaine Jackson Have an Affair? La Toya Jackson Talks http://t.co/7Rbxh9yI</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian Makes Donation to Charity for Wedding Gifts Received http://t.co/e9t0XfJb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mug Shot of the Day: Why Is Teen Mom Jenelle Evans in Jail This Time? And Should She Be Smirking? http://t.co/dlvRSD0l</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Horror Story Cast Drops Scoop on Season Two, Magic Towels and the Friday Night Lights Movie! http://t.co/yjFOkuOG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>This is what Vanessa Hudgens as a &quot;crazy party girl&quot; looks like:  http://t.co/8HDoEsxl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kirk Cameron Backlash: Alan Thicke, Craig Ferguson, Debra Messing, More Slam Gay Hate Speech http://t.co/OFBNUnPL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Demi Moore Back in Los Angeles Following Rehab Stint and Caribbean Vacay http://t.co/g3tRnKa6</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Bachelor's Courtney Robertson Faces the Fire During Women Tell All Special! http://t.co/Ht6iRhev</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sandra Fluke Fallout: Patricia Heaton Returns to Twitter, Apologizes for Bashing Georgetown Student http://t.co/wih6QvtJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Jackson Songs Stolen in Massive Hacking Case http://t.co/yiCMMlxX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: An Unlikely Friendship on Smash! Plus, Scoop on How I Met Your Mother and More! http://t.co/mKJg60tz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry looking adorbs in the Bahamas! http://t.co/sU1j3J3T</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Forget Angelina Jolie's Right Leg, Daughter Vivienne Shows Off Quite a Pout on Girls' Day Out http://t.co/L52EinYh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>LeAnn Rimes and Eddie Cibrian Ex Brandi Glanville Play Nice at Soccer Game http://t.co/Qlzql1vn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Miley Cyrus has an interesting jogging outfit. PHOTO: http://t.co/MerrFdnO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki Is engaged! Do you have advice for future #MrSnooki? http://t.co/uRy0ruhT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Christina Hendricks and Olivia Munn are the latest victims of alleged cellphone hacks and photo leaks http://t.co/N6qGJODQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Live: Nicollette Sheridan Back on the Stand for Desperate Housewives Trial http://t.co/Hi1EE0gh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Prince Harry's Royal Good Time: Booze, Miss Bahamas Make for Successful Diamond Jubilee Trip http://t.co/vDGld2L5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pregnant Snooki Is Engaged! http://t.co/MBlRwJ6k</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Weekend Wrap-Up: Lindsay Lohan Takes On SNL, Christina Hendricks Gets Hacked http://t.co/I0noj7UG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ooh La La! Robert Pattinson and Kristen Stewart Flash Their Joie de Vivre in Paris http://t.co/cRXSL3jL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Hunger Games Primer: What You Need to Know http://t.co/G7jHiSik</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Walking Dead Shocker! Did You See That Death Coming? http://t.co/YaK1Hlc2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Celebrity Apprentice Recap: Who Got Trumped? http://t.co/YekDddUY</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ronnie Montrose, Guitarist and Bandleader, Dies http://t.co/30dokQqZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>West Coast! Sundays on E! Starts now with new episodes of @Khloe_Lamar and @IceLovesCoco!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Christina Hendricks and Olivia Munn Latest Victims of Alleged Phone Hacks and Photo Leaks http://t.co/yesDysdh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Khloé &amp; Lamar Recap: Baby Talk, Handcuffs and Dress Socks, Oh My! http://t.co/8f2NEjmA</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>East Coast! Sundays on E! Starts now with new episodes of @Khloe_Lamar and @IceLovesCoco!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Pippa Middleton Completes Cross-Country Marathon in Sweden for Charity! http://t.co/9TbuwisU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jack White's &quot;Love Interruption&quot;: Watch the Saturday Night Live Performance Now! http://t.co/KB6tKYPQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Star Wars Designer Ralph McQuarrie Dies at Age 82 http://t.co/zSs3ghzW</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan the No. 1 Saturday Night Live Host of the Season?! http://t.co/Edzulac1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Close Call! Rapper Young Buck Dodges 11 Bullets Fired at His SUV http://t.co/whSDmg2J</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gasp! Jessica Simpson Ditches Her Heels...For Flats! http://t.co/DEZY6LuI</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan on Saturday Night Live: A Good Sport, But Was She a Good Host? http://t.co/qR9zGxPL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kirk Cameron: Homosexuality Is &quot;Detrimental and Destructive&quot;; GLAAD Says &quot;He's Out of Step&quot; http://t.co/J2VUd530</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>And the First Blockbuster of 2012 Is...? http://t.co/AJtCnWnD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Oprah's Big Get: First Sit-Down Interview With Whitney Houston's Daughter Bobbi Kristina http://t.co/fVVmdgz0</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lamar gets goofy with Khloe in an all-new episode of @Khloe_Lamar tomorrow @ 10/9c! Here's a sneak peek: http://t.co/u6Rgz8zq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Which TV Icon Is Selling His Flintstone-Approved Home? http://t.co/AYb2wNGd</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Find out why Ice &amp; Coco's trip doesn't go planned in an all-new episode of @IceLovesCoco tomorrow @ 10:30/9:30c! http://t.co/oWnZHzgg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Saddle Up! Lamar Odom Back on Dallas Mavericks, Set to Play Tonight http://t.co/zvstcnJ1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Week in Review: Pregnant Snooki, Jennifer Garner's Baby, RIP Davy Jones, New Dancing With the Stars Pairings http://t.co/1gajqwWw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Horror Story Season Two Scoop: Three More Castmembers Confirmed to Return! http://t.co/E8TqqKPM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Birthday, Jessica Biel! Justin Timberlake's Fiancée Turns 30! http://t.co/lkBGGI5N</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Week in Pictures: Salma Hayek, Olivia Wilde, Kristen Stewart &amp; More Have It Made in Their Shades! http://t.co/QQCNsh5d</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hunger Games Stars Teases Film's &quot;Twists&quot; and &quot;Additions&quot; http://t.co/WnKAGTpx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim, Kourtney and Khloé Kardashian Named in $5 Million QuickTrim Diet-Pill Suit http://t.co/6PhmDtcg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amber Portwood Denied! Judge Refuses to Let Her Participate in Teen Mom Reunion in NYC http://t.co/YN3mjzaJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Bang! Kaley Cuoco Engagement Called Off http://t.co/scyJU2hw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan Ordered to &quot;Calm Down&quot; After Outburst on the Witness Stand http://t.co/7LdwfAhc</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Is Vanessa Minnillo Covering a Baby Bump?! http://t.co/SrS1lavZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Alex O'Loughlin in Treatment, Taking a Break From Hawaii 5-0 http://t.co/iPfz8es1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Leonardo DiCaprio and Girlfriend Erin Heatherton's Hollywood Date Night http://t.co/JRzUKdK5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Coco’s romantic trip go sour? Find out in an all-new episode of @IceLovesCoco on Sunday at 10:30/9:30c! http://t.co/QTRnxuOV</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Random Feud Alert: What's Julianne Moore's Problem With Jessica Simpson?! http://t.co/E8UBJGfL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Check Out Oscar Winner Jean Dujardin Getting a Hero's Welcome at Home http://t.co/QAjWxEOo</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Get a sneak peek of Rob’s new sock line in an all-new episode of @Khloe_Lamar, Sunday at 10/9c!  VIDEO: http://t.co/u6Rgz8zq</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Khloé Kardashian Odom's Transgender Assault Case: Will They Work It Out? http://t.co/D4h7sWAA</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>After Lil Wayne's a No-Show, Jimmy Kimmel Interviews...Weezy's Double? http://t.co/unolANio</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan and Audrina Patridge's Bling Ring Burglar Cops Plea, Gets Jail http://t.co/p7xuGQZF</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Demi Moore's Post-Rehab Vacation Spot Revealed! http://t.co/9sR0PmCt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Natalie Portman takes Aleph for a hike! So cute! PHOTO: http://t.co/7xdKFXW8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Vanessa Hudgens: &quot;Crazy Party Girl,&quot; Ready to &quot;Let Loose&quot; With Selena Gomez in New Movie http://t.co/f9bPFcKk</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Taylor swift brings her magical self to Perth, Australia! http://t.co/nuzmVCFk</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>You rocked it! http://t.co/yY6MRqq0 RT @KendraWilkinson: I just chose a sparkly green dress to wear 2night. Might be over the top</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Horror Story Scoop: Zachary Quinto Returning for Season 2! http://t.co/x9JUbBJz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Birthday Dr. Seuss! http://t.co/rnWFIOVR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones Funeral: Service Will Take Place in Florida, Public Memorials to Be Held in New York and England http://t.co/wZg1NCS9</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>FX confirms Zachary Quinto will be joining season 2 of American Horror Story as a lead! Yay! #AHS</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol Backstage: Hear From the Top 13! Plus, Randy Jackson Thinks Who Tried Too Hard? http://t.co/BSN8IuUI</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lamar Odom to Play for Dallas Mavericks' D-League Team http://t.co/gAPXoRom</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Commando Queen! Cheetah Girl Adrienne Bailon Suffers Major Wardrobe Malfunction in Sheer Dress http://t.co/G0uRD6FJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Katie Holmes &amp; Tom Cruise are so cute in @VanityFair's Oscar party photo booth! http://t.co/IECe75dT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Blake Lively Shuts Down Unwanted Beau: Alleged Stalker Ordered to Stay Away for Three More Years http://t.co/4aj82MGx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki Hides Baby Bump in Baggy Clothes http://t.co/IFlIXa36</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kendall, Kylie and Kris Jenner Strike a Pose on America's Next Top Model http://t.co/Otk0ypAN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Live: Nicollette Sheridan Back in Court for Desperate Housewives Showdown http://t.co/o8L4H6IS</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Future Rock Star? Brad Pitt and Maddox Go Guitar Shopping http://t.co/4UgU84KL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nick Cannon Health Scare: Autoimmune Disease &quot;Like a Lupus Type of Thing&quot; http://t.co/cdXYHeru</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Hunger Games Sneak Peek: Watch Katniss Shut Up the Gamemakers With Her Skills http://t.co/mP9QZqHD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: Psych's Going Ghost Bustin'! Plus Revenge, One Tree Hill, Justified and More! http://t.co/Ydu8mlrG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wiz Khalifa and Amber Rose Engaged—Get a Load of Her Rockin' Rock! http://t.co/ggHKp0zn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Ashley Tisdale Dyes Her Hair a Trendy Hot-Pink http://t.co/MrxQCZFQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Katy Perry Spotted With New Man—Has She Moved On From Russell Brand?! http://t.co/cYOgVpzb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zac Efron Cops to Condom-Dropping: Now Watch Him Blush! http://t.co/lZJjWdPD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Janet Jackson Officially Passes on The X Factor http://t.co/W9Zwrfr1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart at Paris Fashion Week: Does She Look Hotter Glammed Up or Dressed Down? http://t.co/Pv6B28z0</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol's Mass Elimination: Top 13 Revealed! (But Were There Any Surprises?) http://t.co/DaFKiBAw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Project Runway All Stars: Designers Had to Light Up the Runway...Literally http://t.co/x7mnHHam</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones Video Flashback: Monkees' Frontman Talks Singing &quot;Daydream Believer&quot; at Karaoke Bars?! http://t.co/B9qyaRJX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan's Desperate Housewives Death: Had Marc Cherry Been Plotting It for Months? http://t.co/ug5EVSam</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Justin Bieber's New Wax Figure Revealed for His Birthday http://t.co/HOzJAHIj</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Brad Pitt and George Clooney Take Their Gay-Friendly Bromance to the Stage for Same-Sex Marriage Play! http://t.co/V7xA9U96</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lamar Odom Will Not Join Dallas Mavericks for Friday Game Against New Orleans Hornets http://t.co/8xC3X7zE</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Huge Walking Dead Spoiler Alert! AMC Accidentally Leaks Major Character's Death on DVD Ad http://t.co/iSmYbizx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart looks so awesome in Paris! PHOTO: http://t.co/zWj3FBbM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan Testimony Begins: Marc Cherry Said &quot;We Won't Be Killing Off&quot; Edie Britt http://t.co/b4YyIWrN</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Mad Over Mad Men Ads? AMC Addresses 9-11 Controversy http://t.co/Ty740S8j</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Demi Moore No Longer in Rehab, Now on &quot;Vacation&quot; http://t.co/c0pvbi41</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Bachelor's Courtney Robertson Models Wedding Dresses—and Buys One?! http://t.co/7grIxNTJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Wiz Khalifa and Amber Rose Engaged—Get a Load of Her Rockin' Rock! http://t.co/ggHKp0zn</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Michael Jackson Impersonator? Daughter Paris Slams Reports of a King of Pop Pretender on Recording http://t.co/OzwomcdZ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones Death: Marcia Brady, Er, Maureen McCormick Remembers Monkees Star http://t.co/LiUMhcnl</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Davy Jones Autopsy: Heart Attack Cited as Cause of Death for Monkees' Frontman http://t.co/XXONf6HL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Love how fab @LadyGaga looks at Harvard launching her Born This Way Foundation! http://t.co/RJkpgxyr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Will Emma Watson Play Alexis Neiers in Sofia Coppola's Bling Ring Flick? http://t.co/XFUV21Cz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can you believe how grown up our little Biebs is?! Happy 18th Birthday, @justinbieber! http://t.co/e04ubrb0</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Awwww! RT @RealWizKhalifa: She Said Yes!!! http://t.co/jNPOKgme</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Congrats Wiz and Amber Rose! RT @DaRealAmberRose: He has made me the Happiest Woman in the World!!!! http://t.co/XnRBC1rQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Justin Bieber Now &quot;Legal,&quot; Cracks Cougar Jokes and Plays Punk'd Prank on Taylor Swift! http://t.co/Ae1wmZ4p</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Katy Perry Spotted With New Man—Has She Moved On From Russell Brand?! http://t.co/cYOgVpzb</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Amazing Race Death Case: Deceased Producer's Assistant Cops to Drugs http://t.co/jh0qbDMr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zac Efron Cops to Condom-Dropping: Now Watch Him Blush! http://t.co/lZJjWdPD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Gwyneth Paltrow Loves Steve Martin, but Is the Feeling Mutual? http://t.co/7EjHZXaj</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Watch Live: Nicollette Sheridan Heading to Court for Desperate Housewives Showdown http://t.co/RHP1IFFR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan Talks &quot;Regret,&quot; Future Oscars and What's Off-Limits for Saturday Night Live http://t.co/KF0WGpja</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan Court Case: Are the Other Desperate Housewives Out to Get Her? http://t.co/9TfyNkuG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hunger Games: What Made Jennifer Lawrence Cry? http://t.co/6hNVhlIC</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Colin Firth's Flight Turbulence: Fight Breaks Out Aboard Actor's Plane http://t.co/PqxmLIeM</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: Holy Homewreckers on Smash! Plus a True Blood Wedding, Revenge and New Girl http://t.co/gEhPh1up</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy Birthday to both @JustinBieber &amp; @keshasuxx!! Two of our faves! http://t.co/9qkGJ9Xm</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy 18th Birthday, Justin Bieber! http://t.co/U4JvvBmr</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki &amp; Jionni: Anatomy of a Jersey Shore Romance...and Pregnancy! http://t.co/I9vAqSqL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reese Witherspoon Talks Rihanna and Chris Brown at Domestic Abuse Conference http://t.co/9UUKS6Vt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy 7th/28th birthday Mark Foster! @fosterthepeople http://t.co/Pmoiw1uD</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki Is Pregnant! http://t.co/gksHjEUQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Khloé Kardashian Odom and Kris Humphries' Rift Explained: What He Told Her When They First Met http://t.co/E238NAl2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can you spot Snooki's baby bump?! PHOTO: http://t.co/aFssmlRT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Zac Efron is the cutest in Brazil! PHOTO: http://t.co/bKk270OC</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Garner and Ben Affleck's Baby Boy Gets a Name! And It's... http://t.co/zcKxyXv1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Star Trek Sequel: &quot;Overwhelming Schedule, but in All the Right Ways,&quot; Says Zachary Quinto http://t.co/U5QxxukJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Nicollette Sheridan Breaks Down in Court as Desperate Housewives Trial Gets Underway http://t.co/46HpoiXG</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lady Gaga Goes to Harvard With Oprah Winfrey, Launches Born This Way Foundation http://t.co/NeaSsom8</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki &amp; Jionni: Anatomy of a Jersey Shore Romance...and Pregnancy! http://t.co/I9vAqSqL</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Give us your baby name suggestions for #MamaSnooks! http://t.co/VpEeFHXY</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Monkees' Davy Jones: Watch Now as He Talks About Jockeying to Fame http://t.co/K9LQLUc7</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What kind of advice would you give #MamaSnooks?   http://t.co/VpEeFHXY</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>George Clooney Totally Cool With Gay Rumors: &quot;Who Does it Hurt?&quot; http://t.co/vhitpwJ3</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Monkees React to Davy Jones' Death: Mike Nesmith &quot;Won't Abandon Him to Mortality&quot; http://t.co/iV15ajYR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Happy 28th Birthday to @FosterThePeople's Mark Foster! Or is it his 7th bday? #leapday http://t.co/ssZQPpBR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Survivor's Ethan Zohn Gets Stem-Cell Transplant: &quot;Today I Leap Into a Healthy New Body&quot; http://t.co/EHZrzsIX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So close! RT @justinbieber: almost legal</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Heart of Gold! Meryl Streep Donates $10,000 to Viola Davis' Favorite School http://t.co/aybMjing</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Angelina Jolie's Glam Fashion Tour: Which Look Was Best? http://t.co/4Qyk57Ja</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Monkees' Davy Jones Dead: Mickey Dolenz, Eva Longoria, Will Smith and More Tweet Respects http://t.co/yOVCgvzf</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Whitney Houston Card Controversy: Target Yanks Card Over &quot;Offensive&quot; Bobby Brown Joke http://t.co/o0YW8UkR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>The Avengers New Trailer: Five Things We Learned About Iron Man, Hulk, Thor and More http://t.co/v4GTlZbU</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Reese Witherspoon Talks Rihanna and Chris Brown at Domestic Abuse Conference http://t.co/9UUKS6Vt</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>John Mayer's Music Emerges From Shadows, Album Release Date Set http://t.co/SwEVI6Kc</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Can you spot Snooki's baby bump?! PHOTO: http://t.co/aFssmlRT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>So True? So False? Is Tatum O'Neal Back in Rehab After a Cocaine Relapse?! http://t.co/1HBeM9o5</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Monkees Star Davy Jones Dead at 66 http://t.co/KBdNvVej</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>#HungerGames Premiere Contest: And the Winner Is... http://t.co/wyfcJgOp</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>John Mayer's new album &quot;Born and Raised&quot; to be released May 22! http://t.co/bhwtkxrx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Garner and Ben Affleck's Baby Boy Gets a Name! And It's... http://t.co/zcKxyXv1</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Snooki Is Pregnant! http://t.co/gksHjEUQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Joke's on Her! Lindsay Lohan Proves She's Game in SNL Promo http://t.co/zU1kA4Vh</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Khloé Kardashian Odom and Kris Humphries' Rift Explained: What He Told Her When They First Met http://t.co/E238NAl2</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Does Oscar Winner Octavia Spencer Have the Write Stuff? http://t.co/WTaV4Pqm</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Any other year we'd be celebrating @JustinBieber's bday today! Guess we'll just have to hold off on his big 1-8 one more day!</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Revenge Creator: &quot;[Spoiler Alert] Will Never Kiss!&quot; But Guess Which Love Triangle Is So On? http://t.co/7jo5rLxY</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Spoiler Chat Daily: Hot New Character on Glee! Plus Scoop on How I Met Your Mother, Fringe and More! http://t.co/DkFh8ntR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Céline Dion Won't Go On and On: Singer Cancels Las Vegas Shows Due to Virus http://t.co/KMEImr0i</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Everyday is another chance for Taylor Swift to look even cuter! PHOTO: http://t.co/m4onEeFX</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Charlie Sheen's Anger Management Gets Premiere Date http://t.co/hQK38v38</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Garner and Ben Affleck Welcome a Baby Boy! http://t.co/rlcIubyQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kelsey and Camille Grammer Settle Custody War http://t.co/ZPdDyShx</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jean Dujardin brings his Oscar home to France! PHOTO: http://t.co/Rr2B8A5j</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lamar Odom Going Through &quot;Tough Situation,&quot; Will Miss at Least Two More Games http://t.co/dC5bwrdO</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kim Kardashian Poses Without Makeup—Check It Out! http://t.co/BM31l9Yz</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Madonna's A-List Bash a Truly Hot Ticket: Just Ask Jack Nicholson, Sandra Bullock, Leo DiCaprio &amp; More http://t.co/iJeku8va</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>J.Lo &amp; Casper bring the sexy! PHOTO: http://t.co/bvcsppxe</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Parenthood Finale: A &quot;Surprise&quot; for Joel and Julia, and Dax Shepard Reveals Another Kristen Bell Freakout! http://t.co/99Pj6CTK</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Did Angelina Jolie Steal Jennifer Aniston's Right Leggy Look? http://t.co/uObZ70Rg</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Lindsay Lohan Prepares for Saturday Night Live: &quot;I Still Need to Prove Myself&quot; http://t.co/komGbmsQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Katy Perry Transformed! Sexy Star Is Unrecognizable on Interview Cover http://t.co/jsv4KmOv</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Teen Mom 2 Final Finale Reunion Recap: Beef Hot Dogs Hurt My Feelings http://t.co/j9xNriii</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Dancing With the Stars: New Cast Promises Plenty of Skin! http://t.co/6ONiLaKw</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>What Does Taylor Swift Have in Common With Little Sophia Grace &amp; Rosie? http://t.co/cFDnqYmv</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>American Idol Top 13 Guys Perform; Steven Tyler Reenacts Jennifer Lopez's Rumored Oscar Slip http://t.co/mW4od9r6</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Hi-Yo Action! Johnny Depp's Lone Ranger Finally Starts Shooting http://t.co/QwCvXLWB</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Katherine Heigl's Beef With Utah Lawmakers http://t.co/2RliUq8x</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Uma Thurman Shows Off Her Super Cute Baby Bump http://t.co/g6jHu3EJ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Sacha Baron Cohen Slammed by Arab Americans: Where's the Outcry Over the &quot;Blatant Stereotype&quot;? http://t.co/hZliAjBR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Angelina Jolie's Leg: Joan Rivers Goes Out on a Limb With &quot;Fake&quot; on Fashion Police http://t.co/D2K4m6Na</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Angelina Jolie's Leg: Oscar-Winning Poser Didn't Want to Mock Angie—or Get Punched by Brad Pitt http://t.co/8VBkJtAV</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Like father, like son! How cute are Brad Pitt &amp; Knox's matching looks?! http://t.co/fEGUbZW0 #pittstyle4life</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Garner and Ben Affleck Welcome a Baby Boy! http://t.co/rlcIubyQ</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Jennifer Garner and Ben Affleck Welcome a Baby Boy! Congrats! http://t.co/qfU49F0W</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>Kristen Stewart and Robert Pattinson's Oscar Weekend: PDA-fest or Totally Not? http://t.co/hZMJmSAR</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

  <tweet>
    <text>A full gallery of @JustinBieber &amp; @SelenaGomez being the cutest?! Yes, please! PHOTOS: http://t.co/upDE6BBT</text>
    <name>E! Online</name>
  </tweet>

</tweets>
</tweets>